<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apprentices on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apprentices on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:58:42 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/apprentice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Indian Air Force Apprentice Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iaf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:58:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iaf-apprentice-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Indian Air Force Apprentice 2026 के तहत 144 ITI टेक्निकल ट्रेड पदों पर भर्ती जारी की गई है। प्रशिक्षण Base Repair Depot, Chandigarh में होगा। आवेदन 30 दिसंबर 2025 तक स्वीकार किए जाएंगे। 17 से 35 वर्ष आयु के योग्य उम्मीदवार ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। चयन प्रक्रिया में लिखित परीक्षा, साक्षात्कार, मेडिकल जांच और मेरिट सूची शामिल है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC NR Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nr-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 11:44:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nr-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Northern Railway has released the Act Apprentice Recruitment 2025 for 4116 posts across multiple clusters. Eligible candidates with 10th pass and ITI (NCVT/SCVT) can apply online. The selection will be based on a merit list prepared from 10th and ITI marks. The application process begins from 25 November 2025 and continues till 24 December 2025. No written exam or interview will be conducted. Interested candidates must check the eligibility, age limit, application fees, and required documents before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RITES Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rites-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 15:23:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rites-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>RITES Limited has released the Apprenticeship Notification for 2025-26, offering a total of 252 positions for Graduate, Diploma, and ITI apprentices across engineering and non-engineering trades. The selection is purely merit-based without any written exam or interview. Eligible candidates must register on the NATS/NAPS portal and upload all required documents through the official RITES Application Form by 05 December 2025. Candidates must meet the qualification, age, and percentage criteria as per the notification, and only those who submit complete documents within the deadline will be considered for the final merit list.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Nov 2025 16:07:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/bob-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has released the official notification for 2700 Apprentice posts under the Apprentices Act, 1961. The online application process started on 11 November 2025 and will continue till 01 December 2025. Candidates having a Graduation Degree in any discipline can apply through the official website bankofbaroda.in or via the BFSI SSC portal. Selection will be done through an Online Exam, Document Verification, and Local Language Test. Selected candidates will receive a monthly stipend of ₹15,000 during the 1-year apprenticeship training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAI Graduate &amp; Diploma Apprenticeship Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/aai-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 15:39:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/aai-apprentice-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Airports Authority of India (AAI) has announced the AAI Apprentice Recruitment 2025-26 for 20 posts of Graduate and Diploma Apprentices under the Apprentices Act, 1961 at RCDU/FIU/CRSD &amp;amp; E&amp;amp;M Workshop, Safdarjung Airport, New Delhi. Candidates who have completed their BE/B.Tech, BCA, B.Sc, B.Com, BA, BBA, or Diploma (Mechanical, Automobile, EEE, ECE, Instrumentation, Material Management) after 2021 are eligible to apply. The apprenticeship duration will be 1 year, with a monthly stipend of ₹15,000 for graduates and ₹12,000 for diploma holders. Selection will be based on merit and document verification, and applications can be submitted through the NATS portal (nats.education.gov.in) till 24 November 2025. Preference will be given to candidates from the Delhi/NCR region.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ONGC Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ongc-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 12:38:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ongc-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Oil and Natural Gas Corporation Limited (ONGC) has released the official notification for Apprentice Recruitment 2025 under the Apprentices Act, 1961. A total of 2743 vacancies have been announced across India in various sectors such as Northern, Western, Eastern, Southern, Mumbai, and Central.Eligible candidates with ITI, Diploma, or Graduate qualifications can apply for trades like Fitter, Electrician, Computer Operator, Lab Chemist, Mechanical Executive, Accounts Executive, and others. The online application process began on 16/10/2025 and will continue till 06/11/2025 through the official ONGC Apprentice portal – ongcapprentices.ongc.co.in. Selection will be based on merit of qualifying exam marks, and no examination fee is required. Selected apprentices will receive a monthly stipend up to ₹12,300 during the 12-month training period.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NLC India Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/nlc-india-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 17:22:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/nlc-india-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>NLC India Limited has released the notification for 163 Apprenticeship Training slots at Barsingsar Project, Rajasthan. Eligible ITI, Diploma, Graduate and Non-Engineering candidates can apply online from 03 October to 23 October 2025. Selection will be based on marks in the qualifying examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC NWR Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nwr-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Oct 2025 11:47:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-nwr-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>North Western Railway (NWR) Jaipur has released the official notification for 2162 Act Apprentice vacancies under the Apprentices Act 1961 for the year 2025-26. The online application process will start from 03 October 2025 and will remain open till 02 November 2025 at rrcjaipur.in. Candidates must have passed 10th Class with at least 50% marks and hold an ITI certificate in the relevant trade (NCVT/SCVT) to be eligible. The age limit is set between 15 to 24 years with relaxation applicable for SC, ST, OBC, PwBD, and Ex-Servicemen as per government rules. Selection will be done on the basis of a merit list prepared from the average of 10th and ITI marks, without any written exam. The application fee is ₹100 for General/OBC/EWS candidates, while SC/ST, PwBD, and Female candidates are exempted from fees. This recruitment provides an excellent opportunity for ITI qualified youth to gain practical training and build their career with Indian Railways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRDO Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/drdo-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 18:09:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/drdo-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The DRDO Apprentice Recruitment 2025 has been officially announced by the Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO) for 195 apprentice vacancies at the Research Centre Imarat (RCI), Hyderabad. The recruitment includes Graduate Apprentices (40 posts), Technician/Diploma Apprentices (20 posts), and ITI Trade Apprentices (135 posts) under the Apprenticeship Act, 1961. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online from 27th September 2025 to 28th October 2025 through the official DRDO website. Selection will be based purely on academic merit followed by document verification, and no written exam will be conducted. Candidates with ITI, Diploma, or Graduation in relevant disciplines can apply. This is a great opportunity for freshers to gain valuable hands-on training and experience in India’s premier defence research organisation. Applicants are advised to carefully check the eligibility criteria, age limit, application process, and important dates before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC ECR Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ecr-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 16:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ecr-apprentice-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>East Central Railway (RRC/ECR), Patna has announced the Apprentice Recruitment 2025 for 1149 vacancies across multiple divisions and workshops. Eligible candidates with 10th (50% marks) and ITI in relevant trades can apply online from 26 September to 25 October 2025. Selection will be based on merit, followed by document verification and medical fitness.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Canara Bank Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/canara-bank-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 16:38:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/canara-bank-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Canara Bank invites online applications for 3500 Graduate Apprentice positions under the Apprentices Act, 1961 for FY 2025-26. Graduates in any discipline from a recognized university are eligible. Candidates must register on the NATS apprenticeship portal before applying on the Canara Bank website. Selection is based on shortlisting, local language test (if applicable), and document verification. Application dates are 23rd September to 12th October 2025, and fees are ₹500 for general/OBC/EWS while SC/ST/PwBD candidates are exempted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Bank Apprentice Admit Card 2025 Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/indian-bank-apprentice-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 10:20:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/indian-bank-apprentice-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Bank has invited online applications for the engagement of 1500 Apprentices under the Apprentices Act, 1961 for the financial year 2025–26. Candidates who hold a graduate degree in any discipline and have passed on or after 01 April 2021 are eligible to apply. The age of applicants must be between 20 to 28 years as on 01 July 2025, with relaxation applicable for reserved categories. The application process is online, and the registration window is open from 18 July 2025 to 07 August 2025. Selected candidates will undergo one year of apprenticeship training at various Indian Bank branches across the country. The selection will be based on a written examination followed by local language proficiency verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Oil IOCL Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-pipelines-division-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:34:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-pipelines-division-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>IOCL has invited online applications for 537 Apprentice vacancies in its Pipelines Division under Advertisement No. PL/HR/ESTB/APPR (2025)-2. The application window is open from 29th August 2025 to 18th September 2025. Candidates with 12th Pass, ITI, Diploma, or Graduation qualifications can apply for various posts such as Technician Apprentice, Trade Apprentice (HR/Accountant), and Data Entry Operator. The selection will be purely merit-based on educational marks, followed by document verification and medical examination. There is no application fee for this recruitment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC NCR Prayagraj Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-ncr-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Sep 2025 18:57:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-ncr-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Cell (RRC), North Central Railway, Prayagraj has invited online applications for 1763 Act Apprentice vacancies under the Apprentices Act 1961. Eligible 10th + ITI pass candidates can apply from 18th September to 17th October 2025 at rrcpryj.org.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL NR Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-nr-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 09:43:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-nr-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL), Marketing Division – Northern Region, has announced 523 Apprentice vacancies for 2025. The application window is open from 12 September to 11 October 2025. Eligible candidates with ITI, Diploma, or Graduation qualifications can apply online. Selection will be based on merit, document verification, and medical examination, with no application fee for any category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIC Housing Finance Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/lic-hfl-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 20:27:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/lic-hfl-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>LIC Housing Finance Limited (LIC HFL) has announced 192 Apprentice vacancies for graduates under a 12-month apprenticeship program. Candidates aged 20–25 years can apply online from 02/09/2025 to 22/09/2025. Selection will be through an online exam, document verification, and interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECIL ITI Trade Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ecil-iti-trade-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:33:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/ecil-iti-trade-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>ECIL ITI Trade Apprentice Recruitment 2025: Electronics Corporation of India Limited (ECIL), Hyderabad has announced 412 Apprentice vacancies in various ITI trades. Eligible candidates from all over India, including females, can apply online from 01/09/2025 to 22/09/2025. Selection will be based on ITI merit and document verification, and training will begin on 01/11/2025 at ECIL Hyderabad, Telangana.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Naval Dockyard Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/naval-dockyard-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 16:07:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/naval-dockyard-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Naval Dockyard, Mumbai has released a notification for 286 Apprentice vacancies in various ITI and Non-ITI trades under the Apprentices Act 1961. Both male and female candidates from all states can apply online between 25th August 2025 and 12th September 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://applicationportal.in/&#34;&gt;https://applicationportal.in/&lt;/a&gt; No application fee is required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC WCR Apprentice Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrc-wcr-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2025 09:33:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrc-wcr-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Cell (RRC), West Central Railway has announced 2,865 Apprentice vacancies under Notification No. 01/2025. The online application process will run from 30th August to 29th September 2025. Candidates must have passed 10th Class with at least 50% marks along with an ITI certificate (NCVT/SCVT) in the relevant trade. The age limit is 15 to 24 years with relaxation as per rules. Selection will be purely based on merit (10th + ITI marks). Application fee is ₹141 for UR/OBC/EWS and ₹41 for SC/ST/PwBD/Women. Interested candidates can apply online through the official website wcr.indianrailways.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RCFL Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rcfl-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Aug 2025 16:59:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rcfl-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rashtriya Chemicals and Fertilizers Limited (RCFL) has announced 325 Apprentice vacancies for Graduate, Technician, and Trade categories. Eligible candidates with Graduation, Diploma, or 12th qualification can apply online till 12th September 2025. Selection will be done on a merit basis (marks in qualifying exam), with no written test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC SR Apprentices Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrc-sr-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 18:54:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrc-sr-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Cell, Southern Railway (RRC SR) has released the official notification for Apprentice Recruitment 2025, offering a total of 3518 apprenticeship slots across various workshops and divisions including Perambur, Golden Rock, Podanur, Chennai, Salem, Madurai, Palakkad, and Trivandrum. Eligible candidates who have passed 10th (50% marks), 12th with Science (for MLT trades), or ITI in relevant trades can apply online from 25 August 2025 to 25 September 2025. The selection will be based on a merit list prepared from academic and ITI marks. Apprentices will receive a stipend of ₹6,000–₹7,000 per month during training. This engagement is purely for apprenticeship training under the Apprentices Act, 1961, and does not guarantee direct employment, though preference will be given in future railway recruitments to candidates who complete the training successfully.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOB Indian Overseas Bank Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/iob-indian-overseas-bank-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:35:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/iob-indian-overseas-bank-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Overseas Bank has announced the Apprentice Recruitment 2025 for 750 vacancies across various states and UTs. Applications will be accepted online from 10 August to 20 August 2025 through the BFSI SSC portal, with the online exam tentatively scheduled for 24 August 2025. Graduates aged 20–28 years are eligible, with relaxations as per government norms. Selection will be based on an online test, local language proficiency, and document verification. Stipend ranges from ₹10,000 to ₹15,000 depending on posting location.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC Central Railway Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrc-central-railway-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 12:54:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrc-central-railway-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>RRC Central Railway is inviting online applications for 2,418 Apprentice posts under various trades in Mumbai, Bhusawal, Pune, Nagpur, and Solapur divisions. Eligible candidates must have passed 10th with at least 50% marks and possess an ITI certificate in the relevant trade. The application window is open from 12 August to 11 September 2025. Selection will be based on merit from Class 10 and ITI marks. A stipend of ₹7,000 per month will be provided during the 1-year training. Apply only through the official website rrccr.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC Eastern Railway Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-eastern-railway-form-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:05:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/rrc-eastern-railway-form-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Cell (RRC), Eastern Railway, Kolkata has released the official notification for Apprentice Recruitment 2025 for a total of 3115 trade-wise vacancies. The recruitment is open for various divisions and workshops including Howrah, Sealdah, Asansol, Malda, Liluah, Jamalpur, and Kanchrapara. Candidates who have passed Class 10th and possess an ITI certificate in the relevant trade are eligible to apply. The age of the applicant should be between 15 and 24 years. The selection will be based purely on merit, considering the marks obtained in 10th and ITI – no written exam will be conducted. Applications must be submitted online through the official RRC ER website within the prescribed dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy Skilled Tradesman &amp; Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-tradesman-skilled-apprentice-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:44:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-tradesman-skilled-apprentice-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Navy is inviting applications for 1266 Tradesman Skilled Apprentice posts under the 2025 recruitment drive, including backlog vacancies. The online application process will run from 13 August 2025 to 02 September 2025. Both male and female candidates who meet the eligibility criteria can apply through the official website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL Southern Region SR Apprentice Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-southern-region-sr-apprentice-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 14:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/iocl-southern-region-sr-apprentice-2025/</guid>
      <description>IOCL Southern Region has announced 475 Apprentice vacancies for Trade, Technician, and Graduate disciplines across Tamil Nadu &amp;amp; Puducherry, Karnataka, Kerala, Andhra Pradesh, and Telangana. The application process will be open from 08 August 2025 to 05 September 2025 through the NAPS/NATS portal. Candidates will be selected based on merit, with no written exam or interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway SWR Apprentices Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/railway-swr-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:02:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/railway-swr-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Cell (RRC), South Western Railway (SWR), Hubballi has invited online applications for 904 Apprentice posts in various trades across its divisions — Hubballi, Bengaluru, Mysuru, and Central Workshop Mysuru. Candidates who have passed 10th class with 50% marks and hold a valid ITI certificate in the relevant trade can apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ICF Apprentice Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/railway-icf-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:00:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/railway-icf-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Integral Coach Factory (ICF), Indian Railways has released a notification for the recruitment of Apprentices for the year 2025. A total of approximately 1010 vacancies are available across various trades like Fitter, Electrician, Welder, Painter, Carpenter, Machinist, and MLT. The recruitment is open for both Fresher and Ex-ITI candidates. Applicants must have passed Class 10th or 12th, and ITI is required for certain trades. The selection will be based on merit, without any written exam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway BLW Apprentices Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/railway-blw-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 20:53:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/apprentice/railway-blw-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Banaras Locomotive Works (BLW), Indian Railways, has released the official notification for the 47th Batch Act Apprentice Recruitment 2025. A total of 374 apprentice posts are available for both ITI and Non-ITI candidates. The trades include Fitter (137 posts), Carpenter (3), Painter (General) (7), Machinist (82), Welder (G&amp;amp;E) (56), and Electrician (89). For ITI posts, candidates must have passed Class 10th with at least 50% marks and hold an ITI certificate in the relevant trade from NCVT/SCVT. For Non-ITI posts, only 10th pass with 50% marks is required. The application process is completely online through the official website blw.indianrailways.gov.in. Interested candidates must apply before the last date as mentioned in the notification.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
