<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scholarships on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scholarships on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 09:39:55 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/scholarship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HDFC Scholarship 2025-26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/hdfc-ecss-scholarship-2025-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Nov 2025 09:39:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/hdfc-ecss-scholarship-2025-26/</guid>
      <description>HDFC Bank Parivartan’s ECSS Scholarship 2025-26 is a financial assistance programme aimed at helping meritorious students from economically weaker sections continue their education without interruption. The scholarship is open for school students (Class 1 to 12), as well as those pursuing diploma, ITI, polytechnic, undergraduate, and postgraduate courses. Under this initiative, eligible students facing financial challenges, family crises, or risk of dropout can receive support of up to INR 75,000. The programme ensures that bright and deserving students get equal opportunities to pursue their academic goals and build a successful future.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Platinum Jubilee Asha Scholarship 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/sbi-asha-scholarship-program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 10:58:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/sbi-asha-scholarship-program/</guid>
      <description>SBI Platinum Jubilee Asha Scholarship 2025 is a national-level scholarship launched by the SBI Foundation under its CSR initiative to support meritorious students from economically weaker families. Under this scheme, students from Class 9 to Postgraduate level can get financial aid up to ₹20 lakh per year. The aim is to help bright students continue their education without financial burden. Eligible students can apply online through the official website sbiashascholarship.co.in from 19 September 2025 to 15 November 2025. The scheme covers school, college, medical, and professional courses with 50% reservation for girl students.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIC Golden Jubilee Scholarship 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/lic-gjf-golden-jubilee-scholarship-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Sep 2025 10:18:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/lic-gjf-golden-jubilee-scholarship-2025/</guid>
      <description>The LIC Golden Jubilee Scholarship 2025 provides financial support to meritorious students from Economically Weaker Sections (EWS) for pursuing higher education in India. The scheme covers courses after Class 10 and 12, including Medical, Engineering, Graduation, Vocational, Diploma, and ITI programs. Scholarships are of two types: General Scholarship and Special Scholarship for Girls, with amounts ranging from ₹15,000 to ₹40,000 per annum. Selection is merit-based and income-sensitive, and the scholarship is credited directly to the student’s bank account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Azim Premji Foundation Scholarship 2025 – Online Application Begins</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/azim-premji-scholarship-form-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:45:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/azim-premji-scholarship-form-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Azim Premji Scholarship 2025 is a flagship initiative of the Azim Premji Foundation aimed at supporting girl students from disadvantaged backgrounds to continue their higher education. Under this program, eligible students receive ₹30,000 per year for the entire duration of their first undergraduate degree or diploma course (2–5 years) at recognized government or private colleges across India. To qualify, the applicant must have passed Class 10 and 12 as a regular student from a government school or college and secured admission in the first year of a UG or diploma course for the 2025–26 academic session. The scholarship is open to students from select states and union territories including Arunachal Pradesh, Assam, Bihar, Chhattisgarh, Jharkhand, Karnataka, Madhya Pradesh, Manipur, Meghalaya, Mizoram, Nagaland, Odisha, Puducherry, Rajasthan, Sikkim, Telangana, Tripura, Uttar Pradesh, and Uttarakhand. The application process for the Scholarship Cohort 2025 will begin on 10 September 2025, and candidates must submit documents like a passport-size photograph, Aadhaar card, and signature image. Importantly, there is no application fee, and students are advised to beware of fraud or impostors.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Reliance Foundation Scholarships 2025-26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/reliance-foundation-scholarships-2025-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 18:54:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/reliance-foundation-scholarships-2025-26/</guid>
      <description>Reliance Foundation Scholarships 2025–26 support talented Indian students pursuing Undergraduate (UG) and Postgraduate (PG) programs. Scholarships provide financial aid up to ₹2,00,000 for UG and ₹6,00,000 for PG students, along with mentorship, networking, workshops, internships, and volunteering opportunities. Eligible students must be first-year learners in full-time regular courses, meet academic criteria, and complete a mandatory online aptitude test. Last date to apply: 4th October 2025 via the official Reliance Foundation Scholarships portal.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
