<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scholarships on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scholarships on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:03:07 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/scholarship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>LIC Golden Jubilee Scholarship 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/lic-gjf-golden-jubilee-scholarship-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 11:03:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/lic-gjf-golden-jubilee-scholarship-2025/</guid>
      <description>The LIC Golden Jubilee Scholarship 2025 provides financial support to meritorious students from Economically Weaker Sections (EWS) for pursuing higher education in India. The scheme covers courses after Class 10 and 12, including Medical, Engineering, Graduation, Vocational, Diploma, and ITI programs. Scholarships are of two types: General Scholarship and Special Scholarship for Girls, with amounts ranging from ₹15,000 to ₹40,000 per annum. Selection is merit-based and income-sensitive, and the scholarship is credited directly to the student’s bank account.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HDFC Scholarship 2025-26</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/hdfc-ecss-scholarship-2025-26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 09:43:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scholarship/hdfc-ecss-scholarship-2025-26/</guid>
      <description>HDFC Bank Parivartan’s ECSS Scholarship 2025-26 is a financial assistance programme aimed at helping meritorious students from economically weaker sections continue their education without interruption. The scholarship is open for school students (Class 1 to 12), as well as those pursuing diploma, ITI, polytechnic, undergraduate, and postgraduate courses. Under this initiative, eligible students facing financial challenges, family crises, or risk of dropout can receive support of up to INR 75,000. The programme ensures that bright and deserving students get equal opportunities to pursue their academic goals and build a successful future.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
