<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Apprentices on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Apprentices on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:00:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>ICF Apprentice Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/railway-icf-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 14:00:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/railway-icf-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Integral Coach Factory (ICF), Indian Railways has released a notification for the recruitment of Apprentices for the year 2025. A total of approximately 1010 vacancies are available across various trades like Fitter, Electrician, Welder, Painter, Carpenter, Machinist, and MLT. The recruitment is open for both Fresher and Ex-ITI candidates. Applicants must have passed Class 10th or 12th, and ITI is required for certain trades. The selection will be based on merit, without any written exam.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHPC Apprentice Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/nhpc-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 11:40:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/nhpc-apprentice-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>NHPC Limited has announced 361 Apprentice vacancies for the year 2025 under Graduate, Diploma, and ITI categories. Candidates from Engineering, Commerce, Management, Law, and Technical trades can apply. The application process begins on 11 July 2025 and ends on 11 August 2025. This is a one-year apprenticeship program and selections will be based on academic merit. No written test or interview will be conducted.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway BLW Apprentices Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/railway-blw-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 20:53:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/apprentice/railway-blw-apprentices-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Banaras Locomotive Works (BLW), Indian Railways, has released the official notification for the 47th Batch Act Apprentice Recruitment 2025. A total of 374 apprentice posts are available for both ITI and Non-ITI candidates. The trades include Fitter (137 posts), Carpenter (3), Painter (General) (7), Machinist (82), Welder (G&amp;amp;E) (56), and Electrician (89). For ITI posts, candidates must have passed Class 10th with at least 50% marks and hold an ITI certificate in the relevant trade from NCVT/SCVT. For Non-ITI posts, only 10th pass with 50% marks is required. The application process is completely online through the official website blw.indianrailways.gov.in. Interested candidates must apply before the last date as mentioned in the notification.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
