<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>scheme on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in scheme on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:19:46 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/jobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Agriculture Supervisor Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-agriculture-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:19:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-agriculture-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Agriculture Supervisor Recruitment 2026 has been released by the Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) for 1100 posts under the Agriculture Department. Eligible candidates with B.Sc. in Agriculture or equivalent qualification can apply online through the SSO portal from 13/01/2026 to 11/02/2026. The selection process includes an offline OMR-based written examination scheduled on 18/04/2026, followed by document verification as per rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Female Supervisor Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-female-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:19:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-female-supervisor-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Supervisor Female Direct Recruitment 2026 has been announced by the Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) for the Women &amp;amp; Child Development Department, Rajasthan. A total of 72 posts are available exclusively for female candidates. Selection will be done on the basis of CET (Graduation Level) 2024 score, and the pay scale will be as per Rajasthan Pay Matrix Level-7.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Medical Officer, Veterinary &amp; Various Posts Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/up/uppsc-medical-officer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 11:16:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/up/uppsc-medical-officer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC Direct Recruitment 2025 has been released under Advertisement No. D-6/E-1/2025 to fill 2158 Group B Gazetted posts in various departments of Uttar Pradesh. The recruitment covers Medical Officer, Veterinary Officer, Drug Inspector and AYUSH related posts including Ayurveda, Unani and Homoeopathy. Interested and eligible applicants can apply online via the OTR based registration process from 22/12/2025 to 22/01/2026. The selection procedure will consist of a Screening Test followed by an Interview in accordance with UPPSC guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NABARD Development Assistant Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-development-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 13:02:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-development-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD) has released the Development Assistant Recruitment 2026 notification for a total of 162 posts, including Development Assistant and Development Assistant (Hindi). The recruitment is open to graduates who meet the prescribed eligibility criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSE Group A, B &amp; C Posts Vacancy 2026 - Exam City</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cbse-group-a-b-c-posts-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:11:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cbse-group-a-b-c-posts-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>CBSE has released the Direct Recruitment 2026 notification for 124 vacancies across Group A, B and C posts including Assistant Secretary, Assistant Professor, Accounts Officer, Superintendent, Junior Translation Officer, Junior Accountant and Junior Assistant. Eligible candidates can apply online from 02 December to 22 December 2025. Selection will be based on Tier-1 and Tier-2 examinations, followed by an interview or skill test as per the post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Multi Tasking Staff MTS Vacancy 2025- Self-Slot Booking </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-mts-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 12:03:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-mts-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Multi-Tasking Staff (MTS) and Havaldar Recruitment 2025. Eligible 10th pass candidates can apply online for these posts. The selection includes CBT and Physical Test (for Havaldar). Check complete details including eligibility, age limit, application dates, and how to apply.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Boiler Inspector Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-boiler-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 18:35:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-boiler-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released the Boiler Inspector Recruitment 2026 notification for 05 posts. Candidates with a degree in Mechanical, Production, Power Plant, or Metallurgical Engineering along with relevant experience are eligible to apply online. The selection will be based on academic qualifications and work experience. Interested applicants should apply online through the official BPSC website within the prescribed dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Deputy Director (Fire Service) Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-deputy-director-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:48:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-deputy-director-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released the notification for Deputy Director (Fire Service) Recruitment 2026. A total of 14 vacancies are available under this recruitment. The online application process will be open from 13 January 2026 to 03 February 2026. Candidates must hold a Bachelor’s degree in Science or Engineering, along with recognized fire service training and a minimum of 12 years of relevant work experience. The selection will be based on educational qualifications, work experience, and interview. This recruitment offers a senior-level career opportunity for experienced fire service professionals.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC State Fire Officer Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-additional-director-cum-assistant-state-fire-officer-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 17:19:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-additional-director-cum-assistant-state-fire-officer-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC has released the Additional Director-cum-Assistant State Fire Officer Recruitment 2026 notification for a total of 04 posts. Candidates must possess a Bachelor’s degree in Science or Engineering or a recognized Fire Officer qualification along with minimum 15 years of experience in the fire service. The selection process includes a written examination and an interview. Eligible candidates can apply online from 13 January 2026 to 03 February 2026 through the official BPSC website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Factory Inspector Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-factory-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 16:37:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-factory-inspector-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC Factory Inspector Recruitment 2026 has been released for a total of 17 posts under the Labour Resources Department, Bihar. Candidates with a degree in Engineering, Technology, or Medicine (MBBS) from a recognized university are eligible to apply. The online application process starts on 12 January 2026 and ends on 02 February 2026. Selection will be based on academic merit, and interested candidates can apply through the official BPSC website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NCERT Non-Academic Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ncert-non-academic-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:46:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ncert-non-academic-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>NCERT Non-Academic Recruitment 2025 is released for 173 posts by the National Council of Educational Research and Training. The recruitment will be carried out through direct recruitment. Applications will be accepted online, and candidates can apply within 21 days from the publication date in Employment News. Selection will be based on Written Test, Skill Test or Interview as per the post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Assistant Conservator of Forests ACF Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-acf-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 15:40:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-acf-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC Assistant Conservator of Forests (ACF) Recruitment 2026 is announced for 12 posts under the Bihar Forest Department. Eligible graduates can apply online from 12/01/2026 to 02/02/2026. Selection will be based on written exam, physical test and interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Stenographer Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-stenographer-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 13:16:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-stenographer-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSC Stenographer Recruitment 2026 has been released by the Bihar Public Service Commission for a total of 15 posts. Candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2) and possess knowledge of Hindi shorthand, typing, and computer operation are eligible to apply. The online application process will start on 12/01/2026 and the last date to apply is 02/02/2026. Selection will be based on a written examination followed by a skill test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Junior Engineer Vacancy 2025 - Application Status</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-je-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:19:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-je-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Boards (RRBs) have released the indicative notice for RRB JE Recruitment 2025 under CEN No. 05/2025. A total of 2570 vacancies are announced for Junior Engineer (JE), Depot Material Superintendent (DMS), and Chemical &amp;amp; Metallurgical Assistant (CMA) posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 31 October 2025 to 30 November 2025. Detailed information on application fees, qualifications, and selection process will be available in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Group D / Level 1 Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-group-d-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-group-d-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Boards have released the indicative notice for Level-1 / Group D Recruitment under CEN 09/2025 to fill around 22000 vacancies across various RRB regions. These posts fall under Level-1 of the 7th Pay Commission with a starting pay of ₹18000 per month along with allowances. The online application process will begin on 21 January 2026 and will remain open till 20 February 2026 on the official RRB application portal. Candidates between 18 and 33 years of age as on 01 January 2026 who meet the prescribed educational qualifications will be eligible to apply. Complete details regarding post-wise eligibility selection process syllabus and medical standards will be available in the detailed notification published by the respective RRBs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Constable Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UP Police has released the Constable Recruitment 2025 notification for 32,679 vacancies across multiple units such as Civil Police, PAC, Special Security Force, Female Battalion, Mounted Police and Jail Warder. Applicants must have passed Intermediate (12th) from a recognized board. The prescribed age limit is 18 to 22 years for male candidates and 18 to 25 years for female candidates, with category-wise relaxation as per government norms. The recruitment process consists of a written test followed by PST, PET, document verification and medical examination. The online application window will be open from 31/12/2025 to 30/01/2026, making it one of the largest police recruitments in Uttar Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSSSC Lekhpal Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsssc-lekhpal-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsssc-lekhpal-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UPSSSC Lekhpal Recruitment 2025 offers 7994 vacancies under the Revenue Department, Uttar Pradesh. Applicants must have passed Intermediate (10+2) and qualified in UPSSSC PET 2025. The online application process will remain open from 29 December 2025 to 28 January 2026, and selection will be based on the main examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC CGL Tier - II  Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-combined-graduate-level-exam-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jan 2026 10:16:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-combined-graduate-level-exam-2025/</guid>
      <description>SSC CGL 2025 में आवेदन करने के लिए उम्मीदवार के पास किसी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से स्नातक डिग्री होना आवश्यक है। जूनियर स्टैटिस्टिकल ऑफिसर पद के लिए 10+2 स्तर पर गणित में न्यूनतम 60% अंक या स्नातक डिग्री में सांख्यिकी एक विषय होना चाहिए। स्टैटिस्टिकल इन्वेस्टिगेटर ग्रेड-II के लिए भी स्नातक में सांख्यिकी अनिवार्य विषय होना चाहिए। रिसर्च असिस्टेंट (NHRC) और अन्य सभी पदों के लिए किसी भी स्ट्रीम में स्नातक डिग्री मान्य है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UCO Bank Generalist &amp; Specialist Officer Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uco-bank-generalist-specialist-officers-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 18:09:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uco-bank-generalist-specialist-officers-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>UCO Bank has released the notification for recruitment of Generalist and Specialist Officers for a total of 173 posts. The online application process starts from 13 January 2026 and will continue till 02 February 2026. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website. The selection process may include a written examination, screening, and interview as decided by the bank.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Office Attendant Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-bank-office-attendant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 16:00:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-bank-office-attendant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India has released the RBI Office Attendant Recruitment 2025 notification for 572 posts. Candidates who have passed 10th class and are undergraduates (graduates not eligible) can apply online from 15/01/2026 to 04/02/2026. Selection will be through an online examination followed by a Language Proficiency Test (LPT). The job offers a starting gross salary of around ₹46,000 per month, making it a good opportunity for 10th-pass candidates seeking a central bank job.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Clerk Grade II &amp; Junior Assistant Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-clerk-grade-ii-jr-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2026 11:38:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-clerk-grade-ii-jr-assistant-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) has announced Clerk Grade II and Junior Assistant Recruitment 2026 for a total of 10,644 posts. Candidates who have passed 12th class with a valid computer qualification are eligible to apply. The online application process will be open from 15/01/2026 to 13/02/2026, while the written examination will be conducted on 05/07/2026 and 06/07/2026. Vacancies are available in both Non-Scheduled and Scheduled Areas.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Assistant Town Planner Supervisor ATPS Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-atps-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 12:27:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-atps-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released Advertisement No. 07/2026 for 36 Assistant Town Planner and Town Planning Supervisor posts under the Urban Development &amp;amp; Housing Department, Government of Bihar. Selection will be through a written examination. Candidates with qualifications in Planning, Urban/Regional Planning or GIS can apply online from 14 January 2026 to 05 February 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Constable Answer Key Out 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-answerkey-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:33:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-answerkey-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the Delhi Police Constable (Executive) Recruitment 2025 notification for 7565 vacancies. Both male and female candidates can apply online from 22 September to 21 October 2025. The recruitment process includes a Computer-Based Examination, followed by Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Tests (PE&amp;amp;MT). Eligible candidates must have passed 10+2, and male applicants must hold a valid LMV driving license. The pay scale is Level-3 (₹21,700 – ₹69,100). Reserved categories and women candidates are exempted from the application fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Inter Level Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2026 11:27:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has released the notification for the Inter Level Combined Competitive Exam 2025 with 23,175 vacancies across various departments. Eligible candidates can register online from 15th October 2025 to 25th November 2025, while the final submission deadline is 27th November 2025. The minimum qualification required is Intermediate (10+2) or equivalent along with computer knowledge and typing skills. This is one of the biggest recruitment drives in Bihar offering opportunities for thousands of aspirants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haryana Police Constable Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/haryana-police-constable-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 19:49:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/haryana-police-constable-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Haryana Police Constable Recruitment 2026 is being organized by HSSC under CET Phase-II for 5500 Constable vacancies. Eligible candidates must be CET Group-C qualified. The selection will be carried out through PMT, PST, and Written Knowledge Test. The recruitment process is completely online, no application fee is required, and the pay scale for selected candidates is ₹21,700 under Level-3.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB REET Mains Upper Primary Teacher Level-II Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-upper-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 19:04:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-upper-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the REET Mains Level-II Upper Primary School Teacher Recruitment 2025 for a total of 2123 posts under the Sanskrit Education Department. Eligible candidates can apply online from 07/11/2025 to 06/12/2025 through the official website rsmssb.rajasthan.gov.in. This recruitment includes vacancies for subjects like Sanskrit, Hindi, English, Social Science, and Maths-Science. Applicants must have a Graduation degree with B.Ed/D.El.Ed or 4-Year Integrated B.A./B.Sc. B.Ed as per NCTE norms. The application fee ranges from ₹400 to ₹600, and the exam is expected between 17/01/2026 to 21/01/2026. Interested candidates should check the official notification for eligibility, syllabus, and document requirements before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB REET Mains Primary Teacher Level-1 Vacancy 2025- Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:58:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-primary-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the Rajasthan Primary Teacher Recruitment 2025 notification for a total of 5636 Level-1 posts under the Primary Education Department and Sanskrit Education Department. Eligible candidates who have passed REET Level-1 can apply online from 07/11/2025 to 06/12/2025 through the official website rsmssb.rajasthan.gov.in. The recruitment includes General and Sanskrit teachers for both Non-TSP and TSP areas. Selection will be based on merit and eligibility as per REET qualification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nainital Bank PO, SO &amp; CSA Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nainital-bank-po-so-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:46:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nainital-bank-po-so-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Nainital Bank has released 185 vacancies for CSA, PO and Specialist Officer posts under the 2025 recruitment drive. Applications are open from 12 December 2025 to 01 January 2026, with the exam scheduled for 18 January 2026. Graduates, postgraduates, MBA and CA candidates can apply based on post-specific eligibility.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC NDA 1 Vacancy 2026 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-nda-1-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:40:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-nda-1-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>UPSC NDA 2026 recruitment announces 394 openings across the Army, Navy and Air Force wings. Unmarried male and female candidates meeting the 10+2 eligibility and born between 02 July 2007 and 01 July 2010 can apply online before 30 December 2025. The selection process includes a written exam, SSB interview and medical examination for admission to NDA and Naval Academy courses commencing January 2027.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KVS NVS Teaching &amp; Non-Teaching Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-nvs-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:36:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-nvs-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>KVS NVS Recruitment 2025 offers more than 14967 Teaching and Non-Teaching vacancies under Kendriya Vidyalaya Sangathan and Navodaya Vidyalaya Samiti. Eligible candidates can apply online from 14/11/2025 to 04/12/2025 for posts such as PRT, TGT, PGT, Principal, Clerk, Stenographer, Librarian and others. The application fee is ₹1500 for General, OBC and EWS categories, while SC, ST, PwD and all female candidates are exempted from fees. Qualifications vary by post and include 10th, 12th, Graduation, Post Graduation, B.Ed, D.El.Ed and CTET. The selection process includes a computer-based test followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC GD Constable Vacancy 2026 - Correction Start</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-gd-constable-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:19:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-gd-constable-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>The SSC GD Constable Recruitment 2026 has been announced for a total of 25,487 vacancies across various forces. The online application process will be conducted from 01/12/2025 to 31/12/2025. Candidates must have passed Class 10th (Matriculation) to be eligible. The selection process includes a Computer-Based Examination (CBT), Physical Efficiency Test (PET), Physical Standard Test (PST), and Medical Examination. The application fee is ₹100 for General/OBC/EWS, while SC/ST, Female, and Ex-Servicemen candidates are exempted from the fee. Detailed force-wise vacancies, age limit, physical standards, and exam pattern are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aadhaar Supervisor Operator Online Form 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aadhaar-operator-supervisor-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 18:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aadhaar-operator-supervisor-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Aadhaar Supervisor / Operator – District Recruitment 2025–26 has been released for multiple states across India. Eligible candidates aged 18 years or above with 12th pass, ITI, or Polytechnic qualifications and a valid Aadhaar Operator/Supervisor certificate authorized by UIDAI can apply online. The selection includes certification and authorization approval, and remuneration will be as per state minimum wages for semi-skilled manpower. Applications are open till 31 January 2026 with state-wise apply links available.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Project Manager Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-project-manager-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 17:03:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-project-manager-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of 09 Project Manager posts under the Bihar Industries Service. Eligible candidates can apply online from 10th September 2025 to 6th October 2025. Candidates must hold at least a second-class degree in Engineering, MBA, PG Diploma, Economics, CA, CMA, Pharmacy, or related disciplines. The age limit is 21 to 37 years for UR male candidates, with relaxations applicable for reserved categories as per rules. The selection process will include Preliminary Exam (Objective), Main Written Exam, and Interview. The pay scale is Level–9.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army SSC Tech 67th Women Vacancy 2026 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-women-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 12:22:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-women-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Army has announced SSC (Technical) 67 Women Recruitment 2026 for female engineering candidates. A total of 29 vacancies are available in Civil, Computer Science, Electrical, Electronics &amp;amp; Communication and Mechanical engineering streams. Eligible unmarried women can apply online between 06 January 2026 and 04 February 2026 at joinindianarmy.nic.in. The selection process includes shortlisting, SSB interview, medical examination and preparation of merit list. Selected candidates will undergo 49 weeks of training and will be paid a stipend of ₹56,100 per month during training.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army SSC Technical 67th Men Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-men-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 11:29:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-ssc-tech-67th-men-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Indian Army has announced SSC (Tech) 67 Men Recruitment 2026 for 350 engineering graduate vacancies. Eligible unmarried male candidates aged 20–27 years can apply online between 07/01/2026 and 05/02/2026. Selection includes shortlisting, SSB interview, medical test and merit list. Selected candidates will receive training at OTA Gaya and be appointed as Lieutenant.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RRB Technician Exam Date  2025 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-technician-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:35:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-technician-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the RRB Technician Recruitment 2025 notification for Technician Grade-1 (Signal) and Technician Grade-3 (Open Line) posts. Around 6238 vacancies will be filled. Grade-1 requires a B.Sc, BE/B.Tech or 3-year diploma in Physics, Electronics, Computer Science, IT, or Instrumentation. Grade-3 requires 10th pass with ITI in relevant trade from NCVT/SCVT. Eligible candidates can apply online. Please read the official notification for full details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC CDS 1 Vacancy 2026 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-cds-1-admit-card-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:14:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-cds-1-admit-card-2026/</guid>
      <description>UPSC CDS (I) 2026 announces 451 vacancies for IMA, INA, AFA and OTA courses. Eligible graduates can apply from 10 to 30 December 2025. Selection includes a written exam, SSB interview and detailed medical assessment.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Paramedical Staff 2025 -  Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-paramedical-various-posts-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 19:04:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-paramedical-various-posts-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB), Ministry of Railways, Government of India, has released the Centralized Employment Notice (CEN No. 03/2025) for Paramedical Categories Recruitment 2025 with a total of 434 vacancies across various posts including Nursing Superintendent, Pharmacist, Dialysis Technician, ECG Technician, Radiographer, and Lab Assistant. The online application process will begin on 09 August 2025 and will remain open until 08 September 2025 (11:59 PM). The educational qualifications vary by post, ranging from 10+2 with Diploma/Certificate to B.Sc. in relevant fields, and the age limit is 18 to 40 years as on 01 January 2026. The selected candidates will receive a salary ranging between ₹21,700 and ₹44,900 as per the 7th CPC Pay Matrix (Level 2 to Level 7). The selection process will consist of a Computer Based Test (CBT), Document Verification, and a Medical Examination. Candidates can apply through the official RRB regional websites such as rrbahmedabad.gov.in and others.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSSC Havildar Clerk Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-havildar-clerk-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 18:47:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-havildar-clerk-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Havildar Clerk (Adhinayak Lipik) Recruitment 2026 has been announced by the :contentReference[oaicite:0]{index=0} (BPSSC) for direct recruitment in Bihar Home Guard under the Home Department (Special), Government of Bihar. The recruitment is being conducted for a total of 64 posts. Candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2) are eligible to apply online. The application process is open from 02 January 2026 to 02 February 2026. Selection will be based on a qualifying written examination followed by a Physical Efficiency Test (PET) and document verification. The application fee is ₹100 for all categories as per Advertisement No. 01/2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Forester / Vanpal Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-vanpal-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2026 13:22:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-vanpal-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Forest Guard (Vanpal) Recruitment 2026 notification has been issued for 259 Forest Guard posts by the Rajasthan Forest Department. Candidates who have passed Senior Secondary (10+2) are eligible to apply online through the SSO portal. The recruitment process includes a written test, physical efficiency test and document verification. The online application window is open from 06/01/2026 to 04/02/2026 with category-wise OTR fee.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSSC Home Guard Havildar Clerk Vacancy 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpssc-home-guard-havildar-clerk-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jan 2026 19:40:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpssc-home-guard-havildar-clerk-jan26/</guid>
      <description>BPSSC has issued the official notification for Bihar Home Guard Adhinayak Havildar Recruitment 2026 through Advertisement No. 02/2026. A total of 64 vacancies are available under the Home Guard quota. Candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2), completed at least 5 years of Home Guard service, and are aged between 24 and 50 years as on 01/08/2025 are eligible to apply. The recruitment process consists of a qualifying written examination followed by a Physical Efficiency Test (PET), which will be used to prepare the final merit list. The online application process is open from 05 January 2026 to 05 February 2026 on the official BPSSC website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>EMRS Teaching &amp; Non-Teaching Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/emrs-teaching-non-teaching-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 18:16:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/emrs-teaching-non-teaching-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Education Society for Tribal Students (NESTS) has announced the EMRS Recruitment 2025 (ESSE-2025) notification for a total of 7267 vacancies across teaching and non-teaching posts. The vacancies include Principal, PGT, TGT, Female Staff Nurse, Hostel Warden, Accountant, Junior Secretariat Assistant (JSA), and Lab Attendant. Candidates can apply online until 23rd October 2025, with application fees ranging from ₹500 to ₹2500 depending on the post and category. The eligibility criteria vary by position, requiring qualifications from 10th/12th to Graduate, Postgraduate, B.Ed., CTET, or professional degrees. The age limit is set between 30 to 50 years, with applicable relaxations for reserved categories. This recruitment provides a major opportunity for aspirants seeking teaching and non-teaching jobs in Eklavya Model Residential Schools (EMRS) across India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Head Constable Ministerial Recruitment 2025- Exam City / Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-hc-ministerial-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2026 10:51:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-hc-ministerial-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Head Constable (Ministerial) Recruitment 2025. A total of 509 vacancies (341 male &amp;amp; 168 female) are available. Candidates with 10+2 qualification can apply online from 29/09/2025 to 20/10/2025. The selection process includes Computer Based Examination, Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Test (PE&amp;amp;MT), Typing Test, and Computer Formatting Test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy 10&#43;2 B.Tech Cadet Entry July 2026 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-navy-10-2-btech-cadet-entry-recruitment-jan26/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jan 2026 16:52:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-navy-10-2-btech-cadet-entry-recruitment-jan26/</guid>
      <description>Indian Navy 10+2 (B.Tech) Cadet Entry 2026 offers an opportunity to join the Indian Navy as a Permanent Commissioned Officer after completing a four-year B.Tech program at the Indian Naval Academy, Ezhimala. The recruitment is open to unmarried male and female candidates who appeared in JEE (Main) 2025. Shortlisting is done based on JEE Main CRL, followed by SSB interview and medical examination. A total of 44 vacancies are available, with up to 07 reserved for women. The online application process runs from 03/01/2026 to 19/01/2026, and no application fee is charged.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECGC Probationary Officer Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ecgc-po-recruitment-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 17:40:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ecgc-po-recruitment-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>ECGC Limited, a Government of India enterprise, has released the official notification for the recruitment of 30 Probationary Officers (PO) for FY 2025–26, including 28 Generalist and 2 Specialist (Rajbhasha/Hindi) posts. The online application process will be open from 11 November to 2 December 2025, and the online examination is scheduled for 11 January 2026. Candidates must be graduates (for Generalist) or postgraduates in Hindi/English (for Specialist). The salary package is highly attractive, with a CTC of around ₹20 lakh per annum. Selection will be through online exam and interview, and shortlisted candidates may be posted anywhere in India under ECGC Ltd.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Bank Specialist Officer SO Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-bank-so-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Jan 2026 16:43:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-bank-so-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India has released the Wealth Management Specialist Cadre Officer recruitment for VP Wealth (SRM), AVP Wealth (RM) and Customer Relationship Executive (CRE) posts. Online applications are open from 02 to 23 December 2025. Selection will be based on shortlisting and interview. Eligible candidates with the required qualification, experience and age criteria can apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Constable Driver Answer Key Out 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-driver-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 19:18:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-constable-driver-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Constable (Driver) – Male Recruitment 2025 with 737 vacancies. Applications can be submitted online from 24/09/2025 to 15/10/2025. Candidates must have 10+2 qualification, a valid Heavy Motor Vehicle (HMV) driving license, and knowledge of vehicle maintenance.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DRDO CEPTAM-11 Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/drdo-ceptam-11-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Dec 2025 18:16:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/drdo-ceptam-11-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>DRDO CEPTAM-11 Recruitment 2025 has been announced for a total of 764 vacancies, including 561 posts for Senior Technical Assistant-B and 203 posts for Technician-A. The online application process will begin on 09 December 2025 and is expected to remain open until 08 January 2026. Eligible candidates can apply online after checking the required qualification, age limit, and fee details. The exam date will be notified later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSBC Bihar Constable Driver Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csbc-bihar-constable-driver-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 16:01:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csbc-bihar-constable-driver-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>This recruitment has been announced by RailTel Corporation of India Limited for various posts, where candidates will be selected based on interview and document verification. Interested candidates who fulfill all the required qualifications and experience can apply online. The last date to apply is August 5, 2025. This is a great opportunity for candidates aspiring to build a career in the fields of Electronics, Telecom, IT, and Networking. Before applying, all candidates are advised to carefully read the official notification to avoid any mistakes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Ministerial &amp; Isolated Category Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ministerial-isolated-category-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:24:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ministerial-isolated-category-dec25/</guid>
      <description>RRB Ministerial &amp;amp; Isolated Category Recruitment 2025 has been announced through CEN No. 08/2025 for 311 vacancies in various ministerial and isolated category posts. The recruitment is conducted by Railway Recruitment Boards under the Ministry of Railways. Eligible candidates can apply online from 30/12/2025 to 29/01/2026 and selection will be based on CBT, document verification and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Police Sub Inspector Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-police-si-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 11:19:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-police-si-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Police Subordinate Services Commission (BPSSC) has released the Bihar Police SI Recruitment 2025 (Advt. No. 05/2025) for 1799 Sub-Inspector (SI) vacancies in the Home Department (Police Section), Government of Bihar. The pay scale for the post is Level-6 (₹35,400 – ₹1,12,400/-). Eligible candidates must hold a graduation degree from a recognized university by 01 August 2025. The age limit is 20–37 years for UR male candidates, 20–40 years for UR female/BC/EBC, and 20–42 years for SC/ST. The selection process includes a preliminary exam, main written exam, physical efficiency test, followed by document verification and medical test. The online application process will be open from 26 September 2025 to 26 October 2025, and the application fee is ₹100/- (payable online). Interested candidates can apply through the official website bpssc.bihar.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BPSC AEDO Vacancy 2025 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-bpsc-aedo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:08:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-bpsc-aedo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released the official notification for 935 Assistant Education Development Officer (AEDO) vacancies under the Education Department. The online application process will begin on 27 August 2025 and continue till 26 September 2025. Candidates with a graduate degree from a recognized university are eligible to apply. The salary will be as per Level-5 pay scale (₹29,200 + allowances). Applicants must pay an examination fee of ₹100/- plus bank charges through online mode. Interested candidates should visit the official website bpsc.bihar.gov.in to apply online and check detailed guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC ATP Assistant Town Planner Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-atp-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 16:05:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-atp-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced 35 vacancies for Assistant Town Planner (ATP) under Advertisement No. 89/2025 in the Urban Development &amp;amp; Housing Department. The online application process will be open from 28th August 2025 to 22nd September 2025 on the official BPSC website. Candidates with a Post Graduate degree in Town Planning, Regional/Urban Planning, City Planning, Country/Transport Planning, Housing, or Environmental Planning are eligible to apply. The selection will be based on a written examination and interview, and appointed candidates will receive a salary under Pay Level 09 (₹53,100 – ₹1,67,800) along with allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Constable (GD) Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-sports-quota-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:44:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-sports-quota-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The BSF Constable (GD) Sports Quota Recruitment 2025 offers an opportunity to join the Border Security Force through 549 Sports Quota vacancies across India. Both male and female candidates who are 10th pass and have recognized sports achievements at national or international level can apply online between 27/12/2025 and 15/01/2026 via rectt.bsf.gov.in. The final selection will be based on sports performance marks, PST, document verification, and medical examination as per the official BSF recruitment process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PNB Local Bank Officer LBO Vacancy 2025 - Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pnb-lbo-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Dec 2025 10:25:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pnb-lbo-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Punjab National Bank (PNB) has released the official notification for LBO Recruitment 2025, offering 750 Local Bank Officer (LBO) vacancies across India. Eligible graduates with at least one year of banking experience can apply online from 03/11/2025 to 23/11/2025 through the official website pnbindia.in. The selection process includes an online written test and interview, and the appointment will be made in the Junior Management Grade Scale-I. Candidates are advised to check their eligibility, fees, age limit, and local language proficiency before applying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police SI Confidential, ASI Clerk and Accounts Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-si-confidential-asi-clerk-accounts-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:02:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-si-confidential-asi-clerk-accounts-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has issued the official notification for Police Sub Inspector (Confidential) and Police Assistant Sub Inspector (Clerk and Accounts) posts for the year 2025. Released under Advertisement No. PRPB-B (Cl.)/2025, the recruitment includes a total of 537 vacancies. Online applications will be accepted from 20/12/2025 to 19/01/2026. Selection of candidates will be based on a written examination, followed by skill test wherever applicable, document verification and medical examination. Physical Standard Test (PST) will be conducted, and no Physical Efficiency Test (PET) is included.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHS Bihar ANM Vacancy 2025 Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/shs-bihar-anm-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Dec 2025 14:00:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/shs-bihar-anm-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar SHS is inviting online applications for 5,006 ANM vacancies under HSC, RBSK, and NUHM programs. Only female candidates with a 2-year ANM diploma and BNRC registration are eligible. Applications are open from 14 to 28 August 2025, with selection based on a CBT and document verification. The monthly salary is ₹15,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC CPO SI 2025 - Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-cpo-si-capf-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 09:59:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-cpo-si-capf-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for CPO SI Recruitment 2025, offering 3073 vacancies for Sub-Inspector posts in Delhi Police and CAPFs. Eligible candidates with a bachelor’s degree can apply online from 26 September to 16 October 2025. The selection process includes a Computer-Based Test (Paper-I &amp;amp; II), Physical Tests (PST/PET), Medical Examination, and Document Verification. This recruitment provides an excellent opportunity for graduates to join Delhi Police and CAPFs with a pay scale of Level-6 (₹35,400 – ₹1,12,400).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Protection Officer Vacancy 2025 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-protection-officer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 12:06:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-protection-officer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>RPSC Protection Officer Recruitment 2025–26 offers an opportunity for candidates to apply for 12 Protection Officer vacancies in the Women and Child Development Department, Government of Rajasthan. The online application window will remain open between 24 December 2025 and 22 January 2026. Applicants possessing the prescribed qualification in Law or Social Work are eligible to apply. Selection of candidates will be carried out through a written test and subsequent document verification as per the official recruitment rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Sports Trainer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-sports-trainer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 11:10:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-sports-trainer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has issued the Sports Trainer (क्रीड़ा प्रशिक्षक) Recruitment 2025 notification for 48 posts. Candidates with Graduation and required sports qualification or those who have represented at state or national level in sports are eligible to apply. The online application window will remain open from 22/12/2025 to 22/01/2026. Selection will be carried out through a Computer Based Test (CBT) as per BTSC recruitment rules. This is a valuable opportunity for candidates looking for sports-related government jobs in Bihar.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Section Controller Vacancy 2025- Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-section-controller-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 19:14:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/rrb-section-controller-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has announced 368 vacancies for Section Controller posts through CEN 04/2025. The online application process will be open from 15 September to 14 October 2025. Candidates with a graduation degree and age between 20 to 33 years can apply. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test, skill test (if required), document verification, and medical examination. The post offers a Level 6 pay scale with attractive allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Home Guard Vacancy 2025 - Exam Date</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-home-guard-recruitment-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 19:15:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-home-guard-recruitment-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Home Guard Recruitment 2025 has announced 41,424 vacancies for Home Guard (Male/Female) posts across all districts of the state. The online application process will run from 18 November 2025 to 17 December 2025. Candidates must have passed Class 10 (High School) from a recognized board and must be between 18 to 30 years of age as on 01 July 2025. The selection process includes Physical Standards Test (PST) and Physical Efficiency Test (PET), where male candidates must complete 4.8 km in 28 minutes and female candidates must complete 2.4 km in 16 minutes. The application fee is ₹400 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹300 for SC/ST candidates. The complete district-wise vacancy list and PET/PST rules are provided in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS RRBs CRP XIV Office Assistant Scale-I Mains/ Scale II, III Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-rrbs-crp-xiv-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:59:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-rrbs-crp-xiv-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>IBPS has announced the CRP RRBs XIV Recruitment 2025-26 with 13217 vacancies for Office Assistants and Officers (Scale I, II &amp;amp; III) in Regional Rural Banks. Online applications are open from 1st to 21st September 2025 at ibps.in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Ayush Officer Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-ayush-officer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:43:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-ayush-officer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB), Jaipur has issued Advertisement No. 06/2025 for the recruitment of 1535 Contractual Ayush Officers (Ayurved, Homoeopathy, Unani) under the National Health Mission (NHM), Rajasthan. Eligible candidates can apply online through the SSO Rajasthan Portal from 10 October 2025 to 08 November 2025. The recruitment will be on a one-year contract basis, extendable as per the project duration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Jamadar Grade-II Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-jamadar-grade-ii-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 15:43:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-jamadar-grade-ii-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the official notification for Jamadar Grade-II Recruitment 2025 under the Public Works Department (PWD). A total of 72 posts are available — 64 for Non-Scheduled Area and 8 for Scheduled Area. Eligible candidates who have passed Senior Secondary (12th) and possess a valid computer qualification (like RSCIT, DOEACC “O” Level, COPA, or Diploma in Computer Science) can apply online. The online application process will be active from 17/10/2025 to 15/11/2025, and the OMR-based exam will be conducted on 27/12/2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Computer Operator Grade-A Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-computer-operator-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:15:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-computer-operator-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has released the Police Computer Operator Grade-A Recruitment 2025 notification to fill 1352 posts. This recruitment is open to Intermediate pass candidates with a valid computer qualification certificate. The online application process will remain active from 16 December 2025 to 15 January 2026. The selection process includes a written examination followed by document verification, strictly as per the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Polytechnic Lecturer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-polytechnic-lecturer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Dec 2025 09:15:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-polytechnic-lecturer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC has invited online applications for 513 posts under the Technical Education (Teaching) Service 2025. The recruitment includes Polytechnic Lecturers, Architecture faculty and Workshop Superintendent. Candidates with First Class Engineering degrees or First Class Master’s degrees in relevant subjects can apply. The online form is open from 02 December 2025 to 02 January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL Non-Executive Personnel Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iocl-non-executive-personnel-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 16:23:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iocl-non-executive-personnel-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Indian Oil Corporation Limited has released the IOCL Non-Executive Recruitment 2025 notification for filling multiple non-executive positions in its refinery units across India. The recruitment is open to Diploma and B.Sc qualified candidates for posts including Junior Engineering Assistant, Junior Technical Assistant and Junior Quality Control Analyst. The selection will be carried out through a Computer Based Test followed by a qualifying Skill/Proficiency/Physical Test. Interested candidates can apply online between 20 December 2025 and 09 January 2026. The offered pay scale ranges from ₹25,000 to ₹1,05,000 with standard PSU allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRH Research Officer &amp; Other Posts Answer key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-research-officer-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:08:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-research-officer-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Central Council for Research in Homoeopathy (CCRH), under the Ministry of AYUSH, Government of India, has released the CCRH Recruitment 2025 Notification (Advt. No. 179/2025-26) for 48 vacancies across Group A, B and C posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 05 November 2025 to 26 November 2025 through the official websites - ccrhindia.ayush.gov.in, ccrhonline.in or eapplynow.com. The recruitment includes posts like Research Officer, Junior Librarian, Pharmacist, X-Ray Technician, LDC, and Driver. Selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (CBT) and an interview (for Group-A). Interested applicants should read the full notification for eligibility, qualification, age limit, and application fee details before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CCRH Staff Nurse, MLT, Stenographer &amp; ARO Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-mlt-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 11:05:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ccrh-mlt-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Central Council for Research in Homoeopathy (CCRH) has released the official notification Advt. No. 180/2025-26 for 42 Group B &amp;amp; C vacancies including Staff Nurse, Medical Laboratory Technologist, Junior Stenographer, Junior MLT, and Assistant Research Officer (Pharmacognosy). The online application process will be open from 05/11/2025 to 26/11/2025. Candidates must apply through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ccrhindia.nic.in&#34;&gt;www.ccrhindia.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;. The application fee is ₹500 for UR/OBC/EWS, while SC/ST/PwD/Female candidates are exempted. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOI Credit Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-credit-officer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:22:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-credit-officer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India has announced Credit Officer Recruitment 2025 for 514 posts under GBO Stream. The recruitment includes MMGS-II, MMGS-III and SMGS-IV scales. Selection will be through online exam and interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Jr Engineer Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-engineer-je-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:18:24 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-engineer-je-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for the Junior Engineer (JE) Recruitment 2025. The vacancies are available in various departments such as BRO, CPWD, CWC, MES, NTRO, and others for trades including Civil, Electrical, and Mechanical. Candidates must have a Diploma or Degree in the relevant engineering discipline. Some departments also require two years of work experience. The application process is completely online, and the selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (Paper 1), Paper 2, and Document Verification. This recruitment is open to both male and female candidates across India. Interested applicants can visit the official SSC website &lt;a href=&#34;https://ssc.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://ssc.gov.in&lt;/a&gt; for more details and to apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Village Development Officer VDO Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2025 10:08:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-village-development-officer-vdo-2025/</guid>
      <description>राजस्थान कर्मचारी चयन बोर्ड (RSSB) द्वारा ग्राम विकास अधिकारी (VDO) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी कर दी गई है। इच्छुक और पात्र उम्मीदवार जो भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से स्नातक हैं और जिनके पास O लेवल, COPA, DPCS, कंप्यूटर डिप्लोमा या RS-CIT प्रमाण पत्र है, वे इस भर्ती के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। भर्ती से जुड़ी पात्रता, आयु सीमा, आवेदन तिथि, चयन प्रक्रिया और अन्य जानकारी के लिए आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जरूर पढ़ें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Probationary Officers PO Final Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-probationary-officers-po-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 19:15:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-probationary-officers-po-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>The State Bank of India (SBI) has released the notification for the recruitment of 541 Probationary Officer (PO) posts, including 500 regular posts and 41 backlog posts. Candidates must have a Bachelor’s degree in any stream from a recognized university in India to be eligible. The category-wise distribution of vacancies is as follows: UR – 203, OBC – 135, EWS – 50, SC – 80, and ST – 73. The application process will be conducted online through the official SBI website at sbi.co.in. This is a golden opportunity for graduates seeking a prestigious career in banking with SBI.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BRLPS JEEViKA Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-brlps-jeevika-form-aug25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 10:04:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-brlps-jeevika-form-aug25/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Rural Livelihoods Promotion Society (BRLPS), under the Rural Development Department of the Government of Bihar, has released the official notification for JEEViKA Recruitment 2025. A total of 2747 vacancies have been announced across various posts including Block Project Manager, Livelihood Specialist, Area Coordinator, Accountant, Office Assistant, Community Coordinator, and Block IT Executive. The required educational qualifications vary by post, ranging from Intermediate (for female Community Coordinators) to Graduation, Post-Graduation, Diploma, or B.Tech. The minimum age for applicants is 18 years, while the upper age limit goes up to 42 years depending on the category. The selection process involves a Computer-Based Test (CBT) and a typing test for relevant positions. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://brlps.in&#34;&gt;https://brlps.in&lt;/a&gt; from 30th July to 18th August 2025. This is a great opportunity to contribute to Bihar’s largest rural development mission and support the empowerment of rural communities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Vidhan Parishad Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-vidhan-parishad-office-attendant-driver-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:50:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-vidhan-parishad-office-attendant-driver-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Vidhan Parishad Secretariat has released the official notification for 24 vacancies including 09 Driver and 15 Office Attendant posts. Eligible candidates with a minimum qualification of Matric (10th Pass) can apply online from 29/09/2025 to 20/10/2025. Selection will be based on a written exam, while Driver posts also require a driving skill test. Interested applicants are advised to read the official notification for detailed eligibility, age limit, and application process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Head Constable (RO/RM) PET / PST Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-head-constable-ro-rm-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Dec 2025 09:44:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-head-constable-ro-rm-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>BSF is inviting online applications for 1121 Head Constable (RO &amp;amp; RM) posts under the BSF Head Constable Recruitment 2025. The application process will run from 24 August to 23 September 2025. Candidates with 12th PCM (60% marks) or 10th + ITI in relevant trades can apply. The selection process includes a written test, physical standards test, and medical examination. This is a great opportunity to join the Border Security Force in technical roles.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Assistant Operator Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-assistant-operator-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Dec 2025 12:01:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-assistant-operator-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>UP Police has released the Assistant Operator Recruitment 2025 for 44 posts under the Police Radio Cadre. Eligible 12th PCM passed candidates aged 18–22 years can apply online from 03/12/2025 to 02/01/2026. The selection includes a written exam, PST, PET and document verification. Application fee is ₹500 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹400 for SC/ST.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB Security Assistant/Executive Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-security-assistant-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 19:12:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-security-assistant-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA), has released a notification for the recruitment of Security Assistant/Executive posts for the year 2025. A total of 4987 vacancies are available across various states and Union Territories. Candidates must have passed 10th standard, possess knowledge of the local language/dialect, and hold a domicile certificate of the region applied for. The post offers a Level-3 pay scale (₹21,700 – ₹69,100) along with special allowances. This is a central government Group &amp;lsquo;C&amp;rsquo; non-gazetted, non-ministerial post, offering job security and growth in the intelligence sector. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official portal before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Multi Tasking Staff (MTS) Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-mts-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 11:19:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-mts-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB MTS Recruitment 2025 has been announced for 714 Multi-Tasking Staff (Group-C) posts in various Delhi Government departments. Eligible 10th pass candidates can apply online from 17 December 2025 to 15 January 2026. Selection will be through a CBT exam with negative marking.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Assam Police Constable Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/assam/assam-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 10:29:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/assam/assam-police-constable-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Assam Police ने 1715 Constable (UB &amp;amp; AB) पदों के लिए नई भर्ती अधिसूचना जारी की है। आवेदन प्रक्रिया 16/12/2025 से 16/01/2026 तक ऑनलाइन चलेगी और इसके लिए कोई शुल्क नहीं लिया जाएगा। केवल Assam के स्थायी निवासियों को आवेदन की अनुमति है। योग्यता में UB के लिए 12th pass और AB के लिए 10th pass शामिल है। चयन में PST, PET, Written Test और Viva-Voce शामिल होंगे।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bombay High Court Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bombay-high-court-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Dec 2025 10:29:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bombay-high-court-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bombay High Court Bharti 2025–26 में कुल 2381 पदों पर बड़ी भर्ती जारी की गई है, जिसमें Clerk, Peon, Driver और Stenographer शामिल हैं। आवेदन प्रक्रिया 15 दिसंबर 2025 से 5 जनवरी 2026 तक चलेगी। योग्य उम्मीदवार अपनी शैक्षणिक योग्यता और स्किल्स के अनुसार ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi DDA Recruitment 2025- Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dda-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Dec 2025 11:31:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dda-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Delhi Development Authority (DDA) has released its Recruitment Notification 2025 for a total of 1732 vacancies across various posts including Deputy Director, Assistant Director, Junior Engineer, Stenographer, Patwari, Mali, and Multi Tasking Staff (MTS). The online application process is scheduled from 06 October 2025 to 05 November 2025, and the Computer Based Test (CBT) is expected in December 2025 – January 2026. Candidates can apply online through the official DDA website. The recruitment includes category-wise vacancies (UR, EWS, SC, ST, OBC) and posts for ESM / PwBD candidates. Qualifications vary by post, ranging from 10th/12th pass to Graduate/Degree holders in relevant fields.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IIMC Non-Teaching Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iimc-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 17:34:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iimc-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>IIMC Non-Teaching Recruitment 2025 offers a total of 51 vacancies for various Group A, B and C posts. The selection process includes a written examination, skill test and interview (for Group A posts). Candidates must apply online by 12 January 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RRB Group D Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-group-d-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:50:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-group-d-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has officially announced the RRB Group D Exam Date 2025. The CBT will be conducted from 17 November 2025 to the end of December 2025. City intimation slips will be released around 10 days before the exam and admit cards will be available 4 days prior. Candidates must regularly check their respective RRB regional websites for latest updates and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Pump Operator Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-pump-operator-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 16:40:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-pump-operator-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>BTSC Bihar has released the Pump Operator Recruitment 2025 notification for 191 vacancies. Candidates with 10th (Matric) and ITI qualification in Machinist or Fitter trade can apply online from 12 December 2025 to 12 January 2026. Selection will be based on a Computer Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Dental Hygienist Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-dental-hygienist-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:14:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-dental-hygienist-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has released the Dental Hygienist Recruitment 2025 notification for 702 posts under the Health Department. Eligible candidates with a Diploma in Dental Hygienist can apply online from 10 October to 10 November 2025. Selection will be based on a merit list prepared from academic qualifications. Check eligibility, salary, and application process below.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Hostel Manager Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-hostel-manager-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:14:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-hostel-manager-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has released the Hostel Manager Recruitment 2025 notification for 91 posts under the Backward and Extremely Backward Class Welfare Department. Eligible candidates with a Bachelor’s Degree or Diploma in Hotel Management can apply online through the official website btsc.bihar.gov.in. The selection will be based on a written examination and document verification. Candidates are advised to check the eligibility criteria, age limit, and reservation details before submitting the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Works Supervisor Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-works-supervisor-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:14:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-works-supervisor-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>BTSC Works Supervisor Recruitment 2025 (Advt. 25/2025) is out for 1114 posts under PHED Bihar. Apply online from 10 Oct to 10 Nov 2025. Eligibility: Matric (10th) + ITI in Draughtsman (Civil) / Surveyor / Plumber. Selection via CBT (100 MCQs, 2 hrs, 0.25 negative); Level-2 pay; category-wise and 35% female (horizontal) reservation applicable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Work Inspector Mechanical Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-work-inspector-mechanical-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 15:09:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-work-inspector-mechanical-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has invited online applications for 493 Work Inspector (Mechanical) posts under the 2025 recruitment. Applicants must have passed 10th along with an ITI certificate in relevant mechanical trades. The online application process will remain open from 12 December 2025 to 12 January 2026, and selection will be done through a CBT followed by document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Constable Tradesman PET / PST Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-tradesman-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:26:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-tradesman-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The Border Security Force (BSF) has released a notification for recruitment to various posts. This opportunity is open to both male and female candidates. The posts include Constable, Head Constable, ASI (Steno), and other technical and non-technical categories. Educational qualifications vary by post, such as 10th pass, 12th pass, or a diploma in the relevant trade. Candidates must meet the prescribed physical standards and go through the selection process, which includes a written examination, physical test, document verification, and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Junior Engineer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-junior-engineer-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 14:17:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-junior-engineer-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Technical Service Commission has announced 2809 Junior Engineer posts for Civil, Electrical and Mechanical disciplines. Candidates holding a relevant engineering diploma are eligible to apply online from 12 December 2025 to 11 January 2026. The recruitment process will be conducted through a CBT-based examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IAF AFCAT 01/2026 Batch Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iaf-afcat-01-2026-batch-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:30:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iaf-afcat-01-2026-batch-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Air Force (IAF) has announced the AFCAT 01/2026 Batch Recruitment 2025 for Flying and Ground Duty (Technical &amp;amp; Non-Technical) branches. The online application process will begin on 10 November 2025 and continue till 9 December 2025 through the official website afcat.cdac.in. Candidates holding a graduate or engineering degree with Physics and Mathematics at 10+2 level can apply. The selection process includes an online written test, AFSB interview, and medical examination. Successful candidates will join the AFCAT 01/2026 course commencing in January 2026 as Group-A Gazetted Officers in the Indian Air Force</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR NCL Technician (1) &amp; Technical Assistant Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-ncl-technical-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Dec 2025 10:13:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-ncl-technical-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>CSIR NCL Recruitment 2025 invites applications for 34 Technical posts, including Technician (1) and Technical Assistant. Candidates with ITI, Diploma or B.Sc qualifications can apply between 12 December 2025 and 12 January 2026. The selection process consists of a Trade Test followed by a competitive written examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KVS LDE/LDCE Teaching and Non-Teaching Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-ldce-teaching-and-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 19:03:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/kvs-ldce-teaching-and-non-teaching-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>KVS LDE/DE Recruitment 2026 offers 2499 vacancies for teaching and administrative posts including Principal, Vice-Principal, PGT, TGT, Head Master, Section Officer and Secretariat Assistant. Eligible KVS employees can submit their applications online between 11 December 2025 and 26 December 2025, with verification open till 02 January 2026. The departmental examination will be held on 15 February 2026, and no application fee is applicable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SHS Bihar Ophthalmic Assistant Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bihar-shs-ophthalmic-assistant-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Dec 2025 15:14:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bihar-shs-ophthalmic-assistant-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Health Society Bihar is inviting applications for 220 Ophthalmic Assistant posts under Advt. No. 07/2025. Candidates with 10+2 in Biology/Mathematics and a 2-year Diploma in Optometry or Ophthalmic Assistant are eligible. The application window is open from 14 to 28 August 2025, with a monthly salary of ₹15,000. Selection will be through CBT, document verification, and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Assistant Teacher Bharti 2025 Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-teacher-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 18:36:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-teacher-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Directorate of Medical Education and Research (DMER) has announced a recruitment drive for 7466 Assistant Teacher posts. Candidates must hold a Bachelor’s Degree in the relevant subject from any recognized university in India. Detailed eligibility criteria and subject-wise qualifications will be released soon. Interested applicants are advised to stay updated with the official notification and prepare to apply online as per the given schedule.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS SO XV 15th Mains Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-specialist-officer-so-15th-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2025 17:05:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-specialist-officer-so-15th-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Institute of Banking Personnel Selection (IBPS) has released the notification for the Specialist Officer (SO) CRP SPL-XV Recruitment 2025. A total of 1007 vacancies have been announced for various Scale I posts including IT Officer, Agriculture Field Officer (AFO), Rajbhasha Adhikari, Law Officer, HR/Personnel Officer, and Marketing Officer. The online application process will be open from 1st July 2025 to 21st July 2025. The Preliminary Examination is scheduled for August 2025, followed by the Main Examination in November 2025. Interviews are likely to be conducted in January/February 2026. Applications will be accepted in online mode only. For more details and to apply, visit the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibps.in&#34;&gt;www.ibps.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC 10&#43;2 CHSL 2025 Answer Key Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-chsl-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 18:29:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-chsl-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>कर्मचारी चयन आयोग (SSC) द्वारा CHSL (10+2) भर्ती 2025 का नोटिफिकेशन जारी किया गया है। इस भर्ती के अंतर्गत लोअर डिवीजन क्लर्क (LDC), डाटा एंट्री ऑपरेटर (DEO), डाक सहायक (PA) व छंटाई सहायक (SA) जैसे पदों पर नियुक्तियाँ की जाएंगी। भारत के किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 12वीं (इंटरमीडिएट) उत्तीर्ण उम्मीदवार इसके लिए आवेदन कर सकते हैं। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह ऑनलाइन है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haryana Medical Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/haryana-health-department-mo-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 15:28:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/haryana-health-department-mo-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>Haryana Health Department is inviting applications for 450 Medical Officer (HCMS-I) posts. MBBS candidates can apply online from 08 December 2025 to 07 January 2026. Check eligibility, age limit, fees and full notification details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAI Junior Assistant &amp; Senior Assistant Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aai-ner-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Dec 2025 11:57:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aai-ner-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>AAI NER Recruitment 2025 offers 14 Non-Executive posts. The selection includes CBT, document verification and physical tests for Fire Services. Applications are open online for eligible candidates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB Multi Tasking Staff Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-mts-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Dec 2025 10:18:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-mts-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau has released the IB MTS Recruitment 2025 notification for 362 Multi-Tasking Staff (General) posts across various SIBs in India. Candidates who have passed Class 10 and possess a valid state domicile certificate can apply online from 22/11/2025 to 14/12/2025. The selection process includes a Tier-I objective exam and a Tier-II descriptive exam. Application fees are ₹650 for General/OBC/EWS male applicants and ₹550 for all other categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Delhi Police Head Constable Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-head-constable-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:56:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-delhi-police-head-constable-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the notification for Delhi Police Head Constable (Assistant Wireless Operator/Tele-Printer Operator) Recruitment 2025. A total of 552 vacancies are available, including 370 posts for male candidates and 182 posts for female candidates. The online application process will remain open from 24 September to 15 October 2025. Candidates must have passed 10+2 with Science and Mathematics or hold an NTC in Mechanic-cum-Operator Electronic Communication System. The age limit is 18 to 27 years, with applicable relaxations for reserved categories. The selection process includes a Computer Based Examination, Physical Endurance &amp;amp; Measurement Test (PE&amp;amp;MT), Trade Test, and Computer Proficiency Test. The pay scale is Level-4 (₹25,500 – ₹81,100) as per the 7th CPC.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Sports Officer Exam Date Out 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-sports-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 11:28:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-sports-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced 33 vacancies for the posts of District Sports Officer, Assistant Director (Sports/Youth), and Lecturer (SH &amp;amp; Colleges) under the Bihar Sports Service Cadre through Advt. No. 90/2025. Candidates with a Graduate Degree and a Diploma/PG Diploma in Sports Coaching from a recognized institute are eligible to apply. The online application window will remain open from 02 September 2025 to 30 September 2025, and applicants need to pay a fee of ₹100/- plus bank charges. This is a good opportunity for candidates with sports coaching qualifications to build their career in the Bihar Sports Department.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar PCS 71st Mains Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-71th-exam-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 16:57:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-71th-exam-2025/</guid>
      <description>बिहार लोक सेवा आयोग (BPSC) ने 71वीं संयुक्त प्रतियोगिता परीक्षा (CCE) 2025 का नोटिफिकेशन जारी कर दिया है। यह परीक्षा विभिन्न प्रशासनिक पदों जैसे DSP, SDM, बीडीओ, राजस्व अधिकारी आदि के लिए आयोजित की जाती है। आवेदन प्रक्रिया ऑनलाइन मोड में होगी और सभी भारत के योग्य उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IPPB Executive Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ippb-gds-executive-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:46:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ippb-gds-executive-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>India Post Payments Bank (IPPB) has released the Executive Recruitment 2025 notification for 348 vacancies on engagement from existing Gramin Dak Sevaks (GDS) of the Department of Posts. Eligible GDS employees having a Graduate degree in any discipline can apply online from 09/10/2025 to 29/10/2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ippbonline.com&#34;&gt;www.ippbonline.com&lt;/a&gt;. Selected candidates will receive a monthly salary of ₹30,000, and selection will be based on merit of graduation marks. The recruitment aims to strengthen IPPB’s doorstep banking network across India by engaging trained GDS executives.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Patwari Bharti 2025 Result Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-patwari-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:34:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-patwari-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSMSSB) has released the notification for Patwari Bharti 2025. A total of 3705 vacancies are available, including 522 posts for TSP areas and 3183 posts for Non-TSP areas. Candidates must have a Bachelor’s Degree and a recognized Computer qualification such as NIELIT O Level, COPA, RS-CIT, or a Diploma/Degree in Computer Science/Application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Sub Inspector SI Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-si-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:28:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-police-si-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has announced the UP Police Sub Inspector (SI) Recruitment 2025. The online application process will be open from 12 August 2025 to 11 September 2025, and fee adjustments for submitted payments can be made until 13 September 2025. The application fee is ₹500/- for General, EWS, and OBC candidates, while SC and ST candidates will have to pay ₹400/-. The recruitment is for posts in Uttar Pradesh, and applications must be submitted online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OICL Administrative Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-ao-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Dec 2025 11:12:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-ao-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Oriental Insurance Company Limited (OICL) has released the OICL AO Recruitment 2025 notification for 300 vacancies, including 285 Generalist and 15 Hindi Officer posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 01/12/2025 to 15/12/2025. The selection process includes Prelims, Mains, and Interview. Candidates must check eligibility, age limit, and qualification before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS Probationary Officer PO 15th Mains Result 2025 – Download Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-probationary-officer-po-15th-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Dec 2025 11:19:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-probationary-officer-po-15th-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Institute of Banking Personnel Selection (IBPS) has released the notification for CRP PO/MT-XV Recruitment 2025 for the post of Probationary Officer (PO)/Management Trainee (MT). A total of 5208 vacancies have been announced across 8 participating public sector banks. Candidates who hold a Bachelor’s Degree in any discipline from a recognized university in India are eligible to apply. The recruitment process includes a preliminary exam, main exam, and interview. Applications must be submitted online through the official IBPS website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ibps.in&#34;&gt;www.ibps.in&lt;/a&gt;. Selected candidates will be appointed across various locations in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGPSC Assistant Professor Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cgpsc-assistant-professor-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 18:46:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cgpsc-assistant-professor-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>CGPSC Assistant Professor (Medical Education) Recruitment 2025 के तहत कुल 125 पदों के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन आमंत्रित किए गए हैं। आवेदन 25 नवंबर से 24 दिसंबर 2025 तक स्वीकार किए जाएंगे। इस भर्ती में संबंधित मेडिकल स्पेशलिटी में MD/MS/DNB योग्यता और न्यूनतम 1 वर्ष का Senior Resident अनुभव आवश्यक है। Chhattisgarh domicile उम्मीदवारों के लिए फीस में छूट और परीक्षा में उपस्थित होने पर फीस रिफंड का प्रावधान है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CGPSC SSE Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cgpsc-sse-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 16:46:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cgpsc-sse-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>CGPSC SSE 2025 भर्ती में कुल 238 पद जारी किए गए हैं। आवेदन 01 से 30 दिसंबर 2025 तक ऑनलाइन होंगे। योग्यता स्नातक, आयु सीमा 21–30 वर्ष (CG Domicile: 35 वर्ष) है। चयन प्रक्रिया में Pre, Mains और Interview शामिल हैं। SC/ST/OBC के लिए आवेदन शुल्क ₹300 और अन्य सभी के लिए ₹400 है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Panchayati Raj Block Project Manager Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-panchayati-raj-bpm-recruitment-dec25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Dec 2025 12:24:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/up-panchayati-raj-bpm-recruitment-dec25/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Panchayati Raj Department has released the notification for 826 Block Project Manager (BPM) posts under the RGSA scheme. Eligible graduates with 60% marks and valid computer certificates can apply online from 01/12/2025 to 15/12/2025. No written exam will be conducted; selection will be based on merit, qualifications, and verification. Candidates are advised to read the official notification for detailed eligibility and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Officer Grade B Phase II Admit Card  2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officer-grade-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Nov 2025 14:03:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officer-grade-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced 120 vacancies for Grade B Officers in General, DEPR, and DSIM streams. The application window will remain open from 10 September to 30 September 2025. Phase I examination is scheduled on 18–19 October 2025, while Phase II will be held on 6–7 December 2025. Candidates must carefully read the official notification for detailed eligibility criteria, qualifications, age limit, and application fees before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Computer Assistant Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-computer-assistant-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Nov 2025 17:29:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-computer-assistant-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of Computer Assistant posts in 2025. A total of 13 vacancies have been announced for eligible male and female candidates across India. To apply, candidates must have passed 10+2 (Intermediate) along with either a valid “O” Level certificate from NIELIT or a Diploma in Computer Science. The minimum age required is 18 years, and selected candidates will receive an initial salary in the ₹25,500 – ₹81,100 pay scale (Level-4). The application process is online only and will be available soon on the official website uppsc.up.nic.in. Interested candidates are advised to regularly check the website for the release of the online form and notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC Inter Level Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 18:59:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-inter-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the notification for RRB NTPC Inter Level Recruitment 2025 (CEN 07/2025) with 3050 vacancies under the 10+2 (Undergraduate) category. Eligible candidates who have passed Intermediate (Class 12th) can apply online for posts like Junior Clerk cum Typist, Accounts Clerk cum Typist, Train Clerk, and Commercial cum Ticket Clerk. The application process will start from 28 October 2025 and continue till 27 November 2025. The selection process includes CBT-1, CBT-2, Typing Skill Test (for Clerk/Typist posts), Document Verification, and Medical Examination. The pay scale ranges from ₹19,900 to ₹21,700 (Level-2 &amp;amp; Level-3 as per 7th CPC) with additional allowances. Candidates are advised to check the official notification for complete eligibility, age limit, application fees, and exam details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSPCB JSO &amp; JEE Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rspcb-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Nov 2025 12:56:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rspcb-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>RSPCB has announced 100 vacancies for Junior Scientific Officer and Junior Environmental Engineer. Candidates can apply online from 26 November to 16 December 2025. The notification includes eligibility criteria, age limits, application fees and detailed instructions for uploading documents and completing the online form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR CDRI Technical Assistant &amp; Technician Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-cdri-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2025 15:20:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-cdri-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>CSIR CDRI has released the notification for Technical Assistant and Technician (1) posts under Advt. No. 10/2025 with a total of 44 vacancies. The online application process starts on 25/11/2025 and will remain open till 26/12/2025. Candidates from all over India can apply. The qualification required includes B.Sc./Diploma for Technical Assistant and 10th with ITI for Technician posts. The selection will be based on written examination and skill test as per post requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC Graduate Level Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-graduate-level-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Nov 2025 17:39:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrb-ntpc-graduate-level-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has announced the RRB NTPC Graduate Level Recruitment 2025 (CEN 06/2025) with around 5800 vacancies under the graduate category. Eligible candidates with a Bachelor’s degree can apply online for posts such as Station Master, Goods Guard, Senior Clerk cum Typist, Junior Accounts Assistant, Commercial Apprentice, and Traffic Assistant. The online application window will remain open from 21 October 2025 to 20 November 2025. The selection process includes CBT-1, CBT-2, Computer Based Aptitude Test (for Station Master &amp;amp; Traffic Assistant), Typing Skill Test (for Clerk/Typist posts), Document Verification, and Medical Examination. The salary ranges from ₹25,500 to ₹35,400 (Level-4 to Level-6 as per 7th CPC) along with allowances. Candidates must check the official notification for detailed eligibility, post-wise vacancies, exam pattern, and other important updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IMD Project Scientist Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/imd-project-scientist-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:49:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/imd-project-scientist-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>India Meteorological Department (IMD) has released Advertisement No. 02/2025 for the recruitment of 134 Project Staff posts on a contractual basis under the Mission Mausam Scheme. The vacancies include Project Scientist (E, III, II, I), Scientific Assistant, and Admin Assistant. Eligible M.Sc. and B.Tech candidates from relevant fields can apply online from 24/11/2025 to 14/12/2025. No application fee is mentioned in the notification. The engagement will initially be for one year and may be extended based on performance up to 31 March 2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BSSC 4th Graduate Level Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-4th-graduate-level-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:39:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-4th-graduate-level-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has released the official notification for the 4th Graduate Level Combined Competitive Examination 2025. This recruitment aims to fill 1481 vacancies across various departments of the Bihar Government. The posts include Assistant Branch Officer, Planning Assistant, Junior Statistical Assistant, Data Entry Operator (Grade-C), Auditor in the Finance Department, and Auditor in Cooperative Societies. Candidates must be graduates, with specific subject qualifications required for certain posts. The online application process will be open from 18 August to 19 September 2025. The selection will be done through a Preliminary Exam (objective type and open book with NCERT/BSEB textbooks), followed by a Main Exam and Document Verification. The application fee is ₹540 for General/BC/EBC (male) and outside Bihar candidates, and ₹135 for SC/ST, women (Bihar residents), and PwD candidates. Interested and eligible candidates can apply through the official BSSC website at &lt;a href=&#34;https://bssc.bihar.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://bssc.bihar.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BSSC Office Attendant / Attendant (Special) Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-bihar-office-attendant-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:37:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-bihar-office-attendant-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Office Attendant / Attendant (Special) posts under advertisement number 06/25. A total of 3727 vacancies have been announced across multiple departments of the Bihar government. Candidates who have passed the 10th (Matric) examination from a recognized board are eligible to apply. The online application process will begin on 25th August 2025 and remain open until 26th September 2025. The selection will be done through a preliminary objective-type written examination, followed by a main exam for shortlisted candidates. The minimum age limit is 18 years, and the upper age limit varies by category, with applicable relaxations. Reservation benefits will be given as per Bihar government rules, including 35% horizontal reservation for women and 4% for PwD candidates. The recruitment offers a Level-1 pay scale, and candidates are advised to read the full notification before applying online through the official BSSC website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://bssc.bihar.gov.in&#34;&gt;https://bssc.bihar.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Stenographer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-stenographer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 15:29:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-stenographer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has released the official notification Advt. No. 07/2025 for the recruitment of 432 Stenographer and Stenotypist Grade-III posts in various departments and district offices. The minimum qualification required is Intermediate (10+2) or equivalent along with stenography (Hindi/English), typing, and basic computer knowledge. The selected candidates will get a salary in Pay Level-4 (₹25,500 – ₹81,100/-). The age limit is 18 to 37 years for UR male, 40 years for UR female, OBC and EBC candidates, and 42 years for SC/ST candidates, with 10 years of additional relaxation for PwD candidates. The application fee is ₹100/- to be paid online. The online registration will be open from 25th September 2025 to 5th November 2025, and the last date for fee payment is 3rd November 2025. Interested candidates can apply online only through the official website bssc.bihar.gov.in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Sports Trainer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-sports-trainer-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Nov 2025 11:15:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bssc-sports-trainer-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Staff Selection Commission (BSSC) has announced 379 vacancies for Sports Instructor/Trainer under Advt. No. 08/2025. Eligible candidates with graduation and diploma/PG diploma in sports coaching along with sports achievements can apply. The selection will be based on a written exam (150 marks) and interview (50 marks). Online applications are open from 09/10/2025 to 11/11/2025 at bssc.bihar.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NPCIL Deputy Manager &amp; Jr. Hindi Translator Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/npcil-deputy-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:12:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/npcil-deputy-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Nuclear Power Corporation of India Limited (NPCIL) has released the NPCIL Recruitment 2025 notification for 122 vacancies including Deputy Manager (HR, F&amp;amp;A, C&amp;amp;MM, Legal) and Junior Hindi Translator (JHT). The online application process will be open from 07 November to 27 November 2025 at npcilcareers.co.in. Candidates with MBA, CA, CMA, CFA, LLB, or Postgraduate qualifications can apply online. The selection process includes an Online Test and Interview for Deputy Manager posts and a Preliminary plus Advanced Test for JHT. Selected candidates will receive a salary of up to ₹86,955 per month along with various allowances and benefits. Posting can be anywhere in India under the Department of Atomic Energy.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHA Intelligence Bureau ACIO Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mha-intelligence-bureau-acio-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 14:02:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/mha-intelligence-bureau-acio-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs (MHA), has announced the recruitment of 3717 posts for Assistant Central Intelligence Officer (ACIO) Grade-II / Executive. This is a Group &amp;lsquo;C&amp;rsquo;, Non-Gazetted, and Non-Ministerial post offering candidates a prestigious opportunity to work with India’s internal intelligence agency. Applicants must possess a Bachelor’s Degree in any stream from a recognized university in India. The selection process involves a written examination followed by an interview. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official MHA website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBBPE Assistant Teacher Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbbpe-assistant-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Nov 2025 12:22:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbbpe-assistant-teacher-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The West Bengal Board of Primary Education (WBBPE) has released the official notification for 13,421 Assistant Teacher (Primary) posts in Government and Government-aided schools. The online application process will run from 19 November 2025 (3:00 PM) to 9 December 2025 (11:59 PM). Candidates with 12th + D.El.Ed or B.El.Ed are eligible. The application fee is ₹600 for General, ₹500 for OBC, and ₹300 for SC/ST/PH applicants. Selection will be based on merit, interview, and document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO SDSC SHAR Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-sdsc-shar-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Nov 2025 09:39:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-sdsc-shar-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>ISRO’s Satish Dhawan Space Centre (SDSC SHAR), Sriharikota has released Advertisement No. SDSC SHAR/RMT/01/2025 for 141 vacancies across multiple posts — including Scientist, Engineer, Technical Assistant, Technician, and other roles. The recruitment is conducted under the Department of Space, Government of India. Eligible candidates can apply online from 16/10/2025 to 14/11/2025 at shar.gov.in. The selection process includes a Written Test and Skill Test (as applicable). Applicants are advised to check qualifications, fee refund rules, and eligibility before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOI Specialist Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-so-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Nov 2025 16:24:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/boi-so-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of India has released the Specialist Officer Recruitment 2025 for a total of 115 vacancies in Scale II III and IV. Eligible candidates can apply online from 17/11/2025 to 30/11/2025. The recruitment includes various posts in IT Risk Finance Law Engineering Fintech Data Science and Security fields. Selection will be based on an online test and/or interview. Interested applicants must check the required qualification age limit and fees before submitting the form.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOCL Junior Engineer Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iocl-junior-engineer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 15:45:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iocl-junior-engineer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>IOCL Junior Engineer / Officer (Grade E0) Recruitment 2025 invites applications from Indian nationals with a 3-year diploma in Chemical, Mechanical, Electrical, or Instrumentation Engineering. Candidates must meet the minimum marks criteria (65% for General/EWS/OBC-NCL, 55% for SC/ST/PwBD) and age limits as per category. The selection process includes a Computer Based Test (CBT), followed by document verification and medical examination. Online applications start on 12/09/2025 and close on 28/09/2025. Pay scale for the post is ₹30,000 – ₹1,20,000/-. Reserved category candidates may have relaxations in age and marks.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Clerk (Junior Associate) Mains Admit Card 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-clerk-junior-associate-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Nov 2025 11:11:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-clerk-junior-associate-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India (SBI) has released the official notification for Junior Associate (Customer Support &amp;amp; Sales) recruitment under Advertisement No. CRPD/CR/2025-26/06. A total of 5583 vacancies have been announced, including 5180 regular and 403 backlog posts, to be filled across various states. The online application process will be open from 06 August to 26 August 2025. Candidates must hold a graduation degree in any discipline, with final year students also eligible to apply provisionally. The age limit is 20 to 28 years as on 01 April 2025, with age relaxation applicable as per government rules. The selection process includes an online Preliminary Exam, Main Exam, and a Local Language Proficiency Test (if applicable). The Preliminary exam is expected in September 2025, and the Main exam in November 2025. The starting basic salary is ₹26,730/-, with gross monthly emoluments of around ₹46,000/- in metro cities. The application fee is ₹750/- for General/OBC/EWS, while it is exempted for SC/ST/PwBD/Ex-servicemen. Selected candidates will be posted in the state/circle they apply for, and no inter-state transfer will be allowed. Interested candidates can apply online through the SBI official website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://sbi.co.in/web/careers&#34;&gt;https://sbi.co.in/web/careers&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PFRDA Assistant Manager Phase-II Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pfrda-assistant-manager-am-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Nov 2025 12:26:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pfrda-assistant-manager-am-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Pension Fund Regulatory and Development Authority (PFRDA) has released the notification for the recruitment of 40 Assistant Manager (Grade A) posts in various streams including General, Finance, IT, Research, Legal, Actuary, and Official Language. Eligible candidates with qualifications such as Master’s Degree, BE/B.Tech, LLB, or Chartered Accountancy can apply online. The selection process includes online exams and interviews. Interested candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOB Specialist Officers Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iob-specialist-officers-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Nov 2025 10:36:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iob-specialist-officers-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Overseas Bank (IOB) has released a notification for the recruitment of 127 Specialist Officers in MMG Scale II &amp;amp; III across various departments, including IT, Risk, Information Security, Treasury, Corporate Credit, Software Engineering, and Data Science. Eligible candidates can apply online from 12.09.2025 to 03.10.2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.iob.in&#34;&gt;www.iob.in&lt;/a&gt;. Age, educational qualifications, and post-qualification experience will be considered as on 01.09.2025. Reservation for SC, ST, OBC, EWS, and PwBD candidates will be as per Government norms. Application fees are ₹1000 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹175 for SC/ST/PwBD candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCI Court Master (Shorthand) Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-court-master-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Nov 2025 16:52:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-court-master-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Supreme Court of India has announced 30 vacancies for Court Master (Shorthand) with a salary of ₹67,700/- (Level 11). Eligible graduates with shorthand (120 w.p.m.), typing (40 w.p.m.), and 5 years’ experience can apply online from 30 August to 15 September 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sci.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.sci.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NABARD Assistant Manager Grade A Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-assistant-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 10:08:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nabard-assistant-manager-recruitment-nov-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Bank for Agriculture and Rural Development (NABARD) has released the Grade A Assistant Manager Recruitment 2025 notification for 91 vacancies across various streams including Generalist, Agriculture, IT, Finance, Legal, and Protocol &amp;amp; Security Service. Eligible candidates can apply online from 08 November 2025 to 30 November 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nabard.org&#34;&gt;www.nabard.org&lt;/a&gt;. Applicants must hold a relevant Bachelor’s or Master’s degree depending on the discipline. The selection process includes Preliminary, Main, and Interview rounds. NABARD offers an attractive salary of around ₹ 1 lakh/month (including allowances) and a prestigious career in rural development and agricultural banking. Candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Airforce Agniveervayu Intake 02/2026 Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-airforce-agniveervayu-intake-02-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Nov 2025 11:27:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-airforce-agniveervayu-intake-02-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Air Force has released the notification for Agniveervayu Intake 02/2026 under the Agnipath Scheme. Eligible male and female candidates can apply online for the Agniveer Vayu post. The recruitment is open to candidates from both science and non-science backgrounds. Selection will be based on an online test, physical fitness test, and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SIDBI AM Grade A and B Phase II Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sidbi-assistant-manager-grade-a-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Nov 2025 12:18:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sidbi-assistant-manager-grade-a-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Small Industries Development Bank of India (SIDBI) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Assistant Manager Grade A (General) and Manager Grade B (General, Legal, IT) posts, with a total of 76 vacancies. This is a great opportunity for candidates holding a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in fields like Commerce, Economics, Law, Engineering, Management, or related disciplines. A minimum of 5 years of relevant experience is required for all Grade B positions. The application process will be conducted online, and the postings will be pan-India. Interested candidates are advised to visit the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sidbi.in&#34;&gt;www.sidbi.in&lt;/a&gt; to check complete details and apply. For eligibility criteria, experience requirements, and selection procedure, please refer to the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Motor Vehicle Inspector MVI Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-motor-vehicle-inspector-mvi-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Nov 2025 09:29:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-motor-vehicle-inspector-mvi-2025/</guid>
      <description>बिहार लोक सेवा आयोग (BPSC) द्वारा विज्ञापन संख्या 41/2025 के अंतर्गत 28 मोटर वाहन निरीक्षक (MVI) पदों पर भर्ती का नोटिफिकेशन जारी किया गया है। अभ्यर्थियों के पास 10वीं पास की योग्यता, ऑटोमोबाइल या मैकेनिकल इंजीनियरिंग में डिप्लोमा तथा वैध हल्के मोटर वाहन (LMV) ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस होना आवश्यक है। ऑनलाइन आवेदन की अंतिम तिथि 3 जुलाई 2025 है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHAI Deputy Manager, Accountant &amp; Other Posts Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhai-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 12:31:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhai-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Highways Authority of India (NHAI) has released a notification for direct recruitment 2025 under the Ministry of Road Transport &amp;amp; Highways. Eligible candidates can apply online for various posts including Deputy Manager (Finance &amp;amp; Accounts), Accountant, Stenographer, Library Assistant, and Junior Translation Officer. The application process starts from 30/10/2025 and continues till 15/12/2025. Candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully before applying at nhai.gov.in</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBSSC Clerk &amp; Group D Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbssc-non-teaching-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2025 09:02:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbssc-non-teaching-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>he West Bengal Central School Service Commission (WBSSC) has released the notification for 1st State Level Selection Test (SLST) 2025 to recruit 8477 Non-Teaching Staff including Clerk (Group C) and Group D posts in government-aided schools. Eligible candidates can apply online from 03/11/2025 to 03/12/2025 at westbengalssc.com.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SEBI Assistant Manager Grade A Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sebi-assistant-manager-recruitment-oct-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Oct 2025 15:48:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sebi-assistant-manager-recruitment-oct-2025/</guid>
      <description>Securities and Exchange Board of India (SEBI) has released the SEBI Officer Grade A (Assistant Manager) Recruitment 2025 notification for 110 vacancies across various streams including General, Legal, IT, Research, Official Language, Civil, and Electrical Engineering. The online application process will be open from 30/10/2025 to 28/11/2025. The Phase-I exam is scheduled for 10/01/2026 and Phase-II for 21/02/2026. Candidates must possess a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in relevant disciplines and be below 30 years of age as on 30/09/2025. The selection process consists of Phase-I, Phase-II, and Interview. The pay scale ranges from ₹62,500 to ₹1,26,100 with an approximate gross salary of ₹1.84 lakh per month (without accommodation). Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sebi.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.sebi.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>LIC AE, AAO Generalist Pre Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/lic-ae-aao-specialist-generalist-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:42:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/lic-ae-aao-specialist-generalist-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Life Insurance Corporation of India (LIC) has announced the LIC AE &amp;amp; AAO Recruitment 2025 for a total of 841 vacancies. The recruitment includes posts for Assistant Engineer (Civil/Electrical), Assistant Administrative Officer (AAO Specialist – CA, CS, Actuarial, Legal, Insurance), and AAO Generalist. The online application process is open from 16/08/2025 to 08/09/2025. The Preliminary Exam will be held on 03/10/2025 followed by the Main Exam on 08/11/2025, while the Interview schedule will be announced later. Candidates with a Bachelor’s Degree in the relevant discipline (Engineering, Law, Finance, Actuarial Science, Company Secretary, Insurance, or any stream for Generalist) are eligible to apply. The application fee is ₹700 + GST + charges for General/OBC/EWS candidates and ₹85 + GST + charges for SC/ST/PwBD candidates. The selection process will be conducted in three stages: Prelims, Mains, and Interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RBI Officers Grade A &amp; B Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officers-grade-a-and-b-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Oct 2025 16:35:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rbi-officers-grade-a-and-b-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Reserve Bank of India (RBI) has announced 28 vacancies for various Grade A and B Officer posts under the 2025 recruitment drive. The available posts include Law Officer, Manager (Technical – Civil and Electrical), Assistant Manager (Rajbhasha), and Assistant Manager (Protocol &amp;amp; Security). Candidates applying for these positions must meet the minimum educational qualifications such as LLB, BE/B.Tech, Master’s Degree, or have military experience, along with relevant work experience where required. This is a great opportunity for eligible candidates to join the RBI as an officer and contribute to the nation’s central banking system. Interested applicants can submit their applications through the official RBI website within the given deadline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Coast Guard AC 01/2027 Batch Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-coast-guard-ac-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Oct 2025 10:45:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-coast-guard-ac-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Coast Guard has released the notification for Assistant Commandant Recruitment 2025. A total of 170 vacancies are available under two main branches: General Duty (GD) with 140 posts and Technical (Engineering/Electrical) with 30 posts. Eligible male candidates with a graduate degree and Physics &amp;amp; Maths at 10+2 level can apply for GD, while candidates with an engineering degree in relevant disciplines can apply for the Technical branch. The application process is online through the official website joinindiancoastguard.cdac.in. This is a prestigious Group ‘A’ Gazetted Officer post under the Ministry of Defence, Government of India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Statistical Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-statistical-officer-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Oct 2025 18:59:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-statistical-officer-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released the official notification for Statistical Officer Recruitment 2025 under the Economic &amp;amp; Statistics Department. A total of 113 vacancies have been announced. Eligible candidates with a Master’s Degree in Economics, Statistics, Mathematics, Commerce, or Agriculture Statistics and an RS-CIT Certificate can apply online from 28 October to 26 November 2025 at rpsc.rajasthan.gov.in. Selection will be done through a written examination (150 marks) followed by document verification</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI SCO Wealth Management Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-sco-recruitment-2025-103-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 17:49:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-sco-recruitment-2025-103-post/</guid>
      <description>State Bank of India (SBI) has released the official notification for Wealth Management Recruitment 2025 under the Specialist Cadre Officer (SCO) category. A total of 103 vacancies are available for posts like Head, Zonal Head, Regional Head, Relationship Manager, Investment Specialist, Investment Officer, and others. Eligible candidates can apply online from 27/10/2025 to 17/11/2025 through the official website sbi.bank.in/web/careers. The selection will be based on a personal interview only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB Security Assistant Motor Transport Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-security-assistant-mt-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2025 12:27:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-security-assistant-mt-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB) has invited online applications for 455 Security Assistant (Motor Transport) posts under the Ministry of Home Affairs. Eligible 10th pass candidates with a valid LMV driving license can apply from 6 to 28 September 2025. The selection will be based on an online exam, driving test, and interview, with a salary of ₹21,700–69,100 plus allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO SAC Group C Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-sac-technician-pharmacist-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 11:40:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-sac-technician-pharmacist-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Space Applications Centre (SAC), Ahmedabad – Indian Space Research Organisation (ISRO) has released a recruitment notification for 55 vacancies of Technician ‘B’ and Pharmacist ‘A’ under Group ‘C’ posts. Eligible candidates can apply online through sac.gov.in from 24 October 2025 to 13 November 2025. The recruitment includes various trades such as Fitter, Machinist, Electrician, Electronics Mechanic, IT/ICTSM, Lab Assistant (Chemical Plant) and Refrigeration &amp;amp; Air Conditioning. The selection process consists of a Written Test followed by a Skill Test (qualifying nature). Salary: Level 3 (₹21,700–₹69,100) for Technician B and Level 5 (₹29,200–₹92,300) for Pharmacist A Age Limit: 18–35 years (as on 13/11/2025) Qualification: 10th Pass + ITI/NTC/NAC in relevant trade or Diploma in Pharmacy (First Class)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IB ACIO-II/Tech Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-acio-grade-ii-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Oct 2025 12:54:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ib-acio-grade-ii-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB), under the Ministry of Home Affairs, has released the official notification for IB ACIO-II/Technical Recruitment 2025. A total of 258 vacancies are available for disciplines in Computer Science &amp;amp; Information Technology and Electronics &amp;amp; Communication. Eligible candidates with valid GATE 2023, 2024, or 2025 scores can apply online from 25/10/2025 to 16/11/2025 through &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.mha.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.mha.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;. The recruitment includes Level-7 pay scale (₹44,900–₹1,42,400), with additional security allowances and other benefits. Selection will be based on GATE score, Skill Test, and Interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chandigarh JBT Junior Basic Teacher Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/chandigarh-jbt-junior-basic-teacher-posts-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Oct 2025 17:43:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/chandigarh-jbt-junior-basic-teacher-posts-jul25/</guid>
      <description>Samagra Shiksha, Chandigarh has released a notification for the recruitment of 218 Junior Basic Teacher (JBT) posts for Primary Classes (I to V). Candidates from across India are eligible to apply. The minimum qualification includes a Graduation degree from a recognized university, a 2-year Diploma in Elementary Education (D.El.Ed.) recognized by NCTE, and passing the CTET (Paper-I). The salary for the post is fixed at ₹45,260 per month. The application process is online and will begin on 07 August 2025 and end on 28 August 2025 (5:00 PM), while the last date to pay the fee is 30 August 2025 (2:00 PM). The application fee is ₹1000 for General/OBC/EWS, ₹500 for SC, and exempted for PWD candidates. The selection will be done through a written objective type test of 150 marks, with no interview. Category-wise distribution includes 111 posts for General, 44 for OBC, 41 for SC, and 22 for EWS candidates. Interested applicants must visit the official website ssachd.nic.in to apply and read the full notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MHA IB Junior Intelligence Officer Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2025/ib-jio-junior-intelligence-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 15:51:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2025/ib-jio-junior-intelligence-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Intelligence Bureau (IB) under the Ministry of Home Affairs has announced 394 vacancies for Junior Intelligence Officer (JIO) Grade II/Technical Recruitment 2025. Eligible candidates with Diploma/B.Sc./BCA in relevant fields can apply online from 23 August to 14 September 2025. The selection process includes Online Exam, Descriptive Test, and Interview, with a salary of ₹25,500 – ₹81,100 plus allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bsf-sports-quota-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 09:13:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bsf-sports-quota-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Border Security Force (BSF) under the Ministry of Home Affairs has released the Constable (GD) Sports Quota Recruitment 2025 notification for 391 vacancies. Eligible Indian male and female sportspersons who have participated or won medals in recognized National or International competitions (2023–2025) can apply online from 16 October 2025 to 4 November 2025 at rectt.bsf.gov.in. Candidates must have passed Matriculation (10th) and meet prescribed age, physical, and medical standards. The pay scale is Level-3 (₹21,700 – ₹69,100) as per the 7th CPC with admissible allowances. Application fee is ₹159 for UR/OBC male candidates, while SC/ST and female applicants are exempted. Selection will be based on sports merit, documentation, PST, and medical examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC NER Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-ner-sports-quota-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 17:37:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-ner-sports-quota-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Cell, North Eastern Railway (Gorakhpur) has released the official notification for Sports Quota Recruitment 2025–26 under Employment Notice No. NER/RRC/SQ/2025-26, dated 09 October 2025. A total of 49 vacancies are announced for various sports disciplines in Level-1 to Level-5 posts (Group ‘C’ and erstwhile Group ‘D’). The recruitment will be done through sports trials and evaluation of achievements and qualifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army TES 55 July 2026 Batch Vacancy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-tes-55-july-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Oct 2025 11:58:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-tes-55-july-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Army has released the TES-55 (10+2 Technical Entry Scheme) notification for July 2026 batch. Unmarried male candidates who have passed Class 12 (PCM) with minimum 60% marks and have appeared in JEE (Main) 2025 can apply. A total of 90 vacancies are available under this entry. The online application is open from 14/10/2025 to 13/11/2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joinindianarmy.nic.in&#34;&gt;www.joinindianarmy.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;. Selected candidates will undergo 4 years of training (3 years at CTW + 1 year at IMA Dehradun) and will be commissioned as Lieutenants with a starting pay level of ₹56,100/- (Level 10). No application fee is required — candidates can apply free of cost.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>PowerGrid PGCIL Field Engineer &amp; Supervisor Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pgcil-field-engineer-supervisor-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:37:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/pgcil-field-engineer-supervisor-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Power Grid Corporation of India Limited (PGCIL) has invited applications for 1543 vacancies of Field Engineer and Field Supervisor under the 2025 recruitment drive. Candidates with a B.E./B.Tech/B.Sc in Engineering for Field Engineer posts or a Diploma in relevant discipline for Field Supervisor posts can apply online between 27 August to 17 September 2025. The selection process includes a written test for all posts and an interview for Field Engineers. With attractive pay, allowances, and growth opportunities, this is a great chance to build a career in one of India’s leading Maharatna PSUs under the Ministry of Power.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB Credit Analyst &amp; Relationship Manager Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bob-manager-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 18:30:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bob-manager-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has released the official notification BOB/HRM/REC/ADVT/2025/14 for the recruitment of 50 regular posts in the Corporate &amp;amp; Institutional Credit Department. The vacancies include Manager, Senior Manager, and Chief Manager positions for Credit Analyst and Relationship Manager roles. Eligible candidates having a Post Graduate degree in Finance or CA/CMA/CS/CFA with 3–8 years of experience can apply online from 10/10/2025 to 30/10/2025. The selection process may include an online test, group discussion, and interview. Applications are invited from candidates willing to serve anywhere in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar CID Assistant Director &amp; Scientific Assistant Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-police-cid-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 11:54:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-police-cid-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Crime Investigation Department (CID), Bihar has released Advertisement No. 01/2025 for Bihar Forensic Science Laboratory (FSL) recruitment. A total of 189 contractual posts are available — including Assistant Director (89) and Senior Scientific Assistant (100) in various forensic divisions such as Biology, Chemistry, Toxicology, Physics, Cyber, and Psychology. Eligible candidates with M.Sc., M.Tech., or equivalent qualifications can apply online from 06/10/2025 to 31/10/2025 through cidfslrecruitment.bihar.gov.in. The engagement is purely contract-based for 11 months with a monthly honorarium of ₹50,000 – ₹65,000.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oriental Insurance Assistant Phase-I Result Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-assistant-posts-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2025 09:17:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oicl-assistant-posts-jul25/</guid>
      <description>Oriental Insurance Company Limited (OICL) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Assistants in 2025. Eligible candidates from across India can apply online through the official website. Applicants must hold a graduation degree, and the selection process includes a written examination followed by document verification. Interested candidates should submit their applications before the last date. Selected candidates will receive a competitive salary and will be posted across various locations in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army TGC 143 Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-tgc-143-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 16:36:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-tgc-143-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Army has released the TGC-143 Notification 2025 for Technical Graduate Course (July 2026 Batch). Unmarried male engineering graduates can apply online from 08/10/2025 to 06/11/2025 through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joinindianarmy.nic.in&#34;&gt;www.joinindianarmy.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;. A total of 30 vacancies are available under various engineering streams such as Civil, Mechanical, Electrical, Electronics, and Computer Science. Selected candidates will undergo 12 months of training at the Indian Military Academy (IMA), Dehradun, and will be granted a Permanent Commission as Lieutenant in the Indian Army. The recruitment process includes shortlisting, SSB Interview, Medical Examination, and Merit List preparation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB TGT Teacher Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-tgt-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Oct 2025 09:14:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-tgt-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Delhi Subordinate Services Selection Board (DSSSB) has released Advertisement No. 06/2025 for the recruitment of 5346 teachers in various subjects including Mathematics, English, Science, Social Science, Hindi, Sanskrit, Urdu, Punjabi, Drawing, and Special Education. The online application process begins on 09 October 2025 and continues until 07 November 2025 (11:59 PM) through the official portal &lt;a href=&#34;https://dsssbonline.nic.in&#34;&gt;https://dsssbonline.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;. Eligible candidates must hold a Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in the relevant subject with B.Ed. and CTET (Paper-II) qualification. The pay scale is ₹44,900 – ₹1,42,400 (Level-7, Group B) with a maximum age limit of 30 years, and applicable relaxations as per government rules. The application fee is ₹100 for General/OBC/EWS candidates, while SC/ST/PwBD/Women/Ex-Servicemen are exempted. Selection will be made through a One-Tier Examination (200 Marks) based on subject knowledge and general aptitude. Candidates are advised to read the detailed notification carefully and apply online before the closing date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOM Bank of Maharashtra Generalist Officer Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/bom-generalist-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Oct 2025 15:00:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/bom-generalist-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Maharashtra has released a notification for 500 Generalist Officer Scale II posts in 2025. Eligible candidates with a bachelor’s degree or CA qualification, aged 22–35 years, can apply online from August 13 to August 30, 2025. The selection process includes an online exam and interview, with a salary range of ₹64,820 – ₹93,960 plus allowances. Check eligibility, application fees, important dates, and apply through the official website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSBC Bihar Police Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csbc-bihar-police-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 08:45:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csbc-bihar-police-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Central Selection Board of Constable (CSBC), Bihar has released Advertisement No. 03/2025 for the recruitment of 4128 vacancies including Prohibition Constable, Jail Warder, and Mobile Squad Constable. Eligible candidates who have passed 10+2 (Intermediate) can apply online from 06/10/2025 to 05/11/2025 through the official website csbc.bihar.gov.in. The selection process includes a written exam, physical measurement test, and physical efficiency test (PET). Interested applicants must check the official notification for complete details on eligibility, age limit, application fees, and physical standards before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BHEL Artisan Vacancy 2025 Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bhel-artisan-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Oct 2025 15:40:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bhel-artisan-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bharat Heavy Electricals Limited (BHEL) has announced 515 vacancies for Artisan Grade IV posts under various trades such as Fitter, Welder, Turner, Machinist, Electrician, Electronics Mechanic, and Foundryman for the year 2025. These vacancies are spread across multiple BHEL units like BAP, HPVP, HEEP, TP, and others. Candidates must have passed Class 10th along with ITI (NTC) and NAC in the respective trade. A minimum of 60% marks is required for General and OBC candidates, and 55% for SC/ST in both qualifications. This recruitment offers a great opportunity for skilled ITI holders to join one of India&amp;rsquo;s leading public sector enterprises.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC NDA 2 Result 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-nda-ii-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Oct 2025 11:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-nda-ii-2025/</guid>
      <description>UPSC National Defence Academy and Naval Academy NDA II Examination 2025 Apply Online Form</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Police Constable Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-constable-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Oct 2025 09:10:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-constable-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Police has announced 167 Constable vacancies under the Sports Quota for 2025. Eligible candidates who cleared the Senior Secondary Level CET 2024 can apply online from 12/09/2025 to 01/10/2025. The selection will be based on CET score, sports achievements, and physical standards. Applications can be submitted via E-Mitra kiosks, CSC centers, or the Rajasthan Police website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Engineering Services Examination (ESE) Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-ese-recruitment-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2025 12:26:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-ese-recruitment-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the Engineering Services Examination (ESE) 2026 Notification for 474 vacancies across Civil, Mechanical, Electrical, and Electronics &amp;amp; Telecommunication Engineering disciplines. The online application process starts from 26/09/2025 and will remain open until 16/10/2025 (6:00 PM).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Selection Post Phase 13 Answer Key 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-selection-post-13th-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Sep 2025 09:51:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-selection-post-13th-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the official notification for Selection Post Phase 13 Recruitment 2025, offering a total of 2,423 vacancies across various government departments and ministries. This recruitment drive is open to candidates with Matric (10th), Intermediate (12th), and Graduation level qualifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS CRP Clerk 15th Vacancy Pre Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-crp-clerk-xv-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 10:30:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-crp-clerk-xv-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The IBPS Clerk 2025 (CRP-XV) notification has been released for the recruitment of Clerks (Customer Service Associates) in various Public Sector Banks across India. The application process is online, and the selection will be based on a two-stage examination: Prelims and Mains. Candidates must check the eligibility criteria, exam pattern, important dates, and state-wise vacancies before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Bank Specialist Officers Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-bank-specialist-officers-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 13:58:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-bank-specialist-officers-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Bank has released the Specialist Officers Recruitment 2025 notification for 171 vacancies across 23 posts including IT, Information Security, Credit, Risk, Financial Analyst, Company Secretary, and Chartered Accountant. Online applications are open from 23 September to 13 October 2025. Application fee is ₹1000 for General/OBC/EWS and ₹175 for SC/ST/PWBD. Selection will be through Shortlisting + Interview or Online Test + Interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECR Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ecr-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Sep 2025 18:06:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ecr-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>East Central Railway (ECR), Hajipur is recruiting 56 outstanding sportspersons under Sports Quota 2025-26 for various positions across HQ and five divisions. Vacancies cover sports like Wrestling, Basketball, Kabaddi, Football, Cricket, Badminton, Volleyball, and Hockey. Selection is based on sports trials and document verification. Candidates must meet the age, educational, and sports eligibility criteria. Applications are to be submitted offline before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Union Bank SO (Wealth Manager) Vacancy Admit Card 2025 </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/ubi-wealth-manager-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 18:22:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/ubi-wealth-manager-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>Union Bank of India has announced the Wealth Manager Recruitment 2025 for 250 Specialist Officer (MMGS-II) vacancies. The post offers a pay scale of ₹64,820–₹93,960 plus allowances, with an approximate CTC of ₹21 lakh in Mumbai. Candidates must be between 25 and 35 years of age as on 1 August 2025, hold a full-time 2-year MBA/MMS/PGDBA/PGDBM/PGPM/PGDM from a recognized institution, and have at least 3 years of experience in Wealth Management at the Officer/Manager level. Desirable certifications include NISM, IRDAI, NCFM, or AMFI. The application process will be open from 5 August to 25 August 2025, with fees of ₹177 for SC/ST/PwBD candidates and ₹1,180 for others. The selection process may include an online examination, group discussion, and personal interview. Selected candidates will serve a probation period of 2 years and must sign a service bond to serve the bank for a minimum of 3 years or pay ₹2,50,000 plus taxes if leaving early.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Lab Attendant Vacancy Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-lab-attendant-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Sep 2025 18:13:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-lab-attendant-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) has released the notification for Lab Attendant (Prayogshala Sahayak) Recruitment 2025. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website. This recruitment is a great opportunity for 10th pass candidates seeking government jobs in Rajasthan. Applicants must have a valid domicile of Rajasthan to claim reservation benefits; candidates from other states can apply under the unreserved category (UR). The selection process will include a written examination followed by document verification. Interested candidates are advised to read the official notification carefully and apply before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Assistant Professor Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-assistant-professor-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 16:16:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-assistant-professor-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has announced the recruitment for 574 Assistant Professor posts in the College Education Department across 30 subjects, including Hindi, English, Sanskrit, Botany, Chemistry, Geography, Political Science, and more. The recruitment notification, Advt. No. 10/Exam/Assistant Professor/College Education/EP-1/2025-26, was released on 18th September 2025. Interested candidates can apply online from 20th September 2025 to 19th October 2025 through the official RPSC website or the SSO portal. Applicants must have a Master’s degree in the relevant subject with at least 55% marks along with NET/SLET/SET qualification or a Ph.D. as per UGC regulations. The age limit is 21 to 40 years, with relaxation applicable for reserved categories. The selection will be made based on a written examination scheduled between 1st and 24th December 2025, followed by an interview. Selected candidates will receive a pay level 10 (₹56,100 – ₹1,77,500) with AGP 6000. The application fees are ₹600 for General category and ₹400 for reserved/PwD candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Police Constable Answer Key 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police/constable-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 19:13:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/rajasthan-police/constable-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;table-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;heading&#34;&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल भर्ती पात्रता मानदंड&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;  &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;पद का नाम&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;कुल पद&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;        &lt;th&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल पात्रता&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;    &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल जीडी / ड्राइवर / बैंड नॉन टीएसपी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;6939&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;राजस्थान सीईटी 10+2 स्तर परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;भारत में किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 इंटरमीडिएट परीक्षा&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;ड्राइवर पद के लिए:&lt;/span&gt; एलएमवी / एचएमवी ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस 01/01/2026 तक 1 वर्ष पुराना होना चाहिए&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;अधिक पात्रता विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;      &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल जीडी / ड्राइवर / बैंड टीएसपी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td style=&#34;text-align: center;&#34;&gt;1209&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;td&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;राजस्थान सीईटी 10+2 स्तर परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;भारत में किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 इंटरमीडिएट परीक्षा&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;ड्राइवर पद के लिए:&lt;/span&gt; एलएमवी / एचएमवी ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस 01/01/2026 तक 1 वर्ष पुराना होना चाहिए&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;            &lt;li&gt;अधिक पात्रता विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;      &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;    &lt;h2&gt;&lt;b&gt; राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल: &lt;/b&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt; PET Details/पीईटी विवरण 2025 (सामान्य क्षेत्र)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;    &lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;            &lt;td colspan=&#34;3&#34;&gt;&#xA;                &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;ऊंचाई&lt;/b&gt; पुरुष: 168 सेंटीमीटर और महिला: 152 सेंटीमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;छाती&lt;/b&gt; पुरुष: 81-86 सेंटीमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;li&gt;&lt;b&gt;दौड़: पुरुष:&lt;/b&gt; 25 मिनट में 5 किलोमीटर &lt;b&gt;| महिला:&lt;/b&gt; 35 मिनट में 5 किलोमीटर&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/table&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;h3&gt; ​राजस्थान पुलिस कांस्टेबल भर्ती 2025 से संबंधित महत्तपूर्ण लिंक  (Important Links) &lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;table class=&#34;yp-table&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Important Links&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;    &lt;th&gt;Action&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;     &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Download Answer Key&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://police.rajasthan.gov.in/uploads/CT_2025_Answer_Key_c23936c3ca.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Answer Key&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Download Admit Card&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sso.rajasthan.gov.in/signin&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Admit Card&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;     &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Exam City Details&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://recruitment2.rajasthan.gov.in/knowlocationservlet&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check Exam City&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Dwonload New Exam Date Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://police.rajasthan.gov.in/uploads/C_Tpressnote_2686_9da7aafe1f.pdf&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check New Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;   &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Dwonload Exam Date Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=LzIwMjUvMDYvcnBzYy1yYWphc3Rhbi1wb2xpY2UtZXhhbWRhdGUtbm90aWNlLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Check Notice&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Apply Online&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://sso.rajasthan.gov.in/signin?ru=RECRUITMENT2&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Apply Online&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;📄 Date Extended Notice&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=LzIwMjUvMDUvcmotcG9saWNlLWRhdGUtZXh0ZW5kZWQtbm90aWNlLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;📄 Download Notificiation&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.yojnaportal.com/open/?pdf=L3AvcnBjLmh0bWw=&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Join Whatsapp&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/whatsapp/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Join Telegram&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/telegram/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Click Here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;  &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;Official Source&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;    &lt;td&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.police.rajasthan.gov.in/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;RJ Police Official Website&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;  &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;&lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO Assistant Rajbhasha Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-assistant-rajbhasha-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 15:28:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-assistant-rajbhasha-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>ISRO has invited online applications for Assistant (Rajbhasha) posts through Advertisement No. SAC:02:2025. A total of 07 vacancies are available across ISRO Centres and IIST. Candidates must have a Graduation degree with 60% marks, along with Hindi typing speed of 25 w.p.m. and computer proficiency. The age limit is 18 to 28 years as on 02 October 2025. The online application process is open from 12 September 2025 to 02 October 2025. All candidates must pay ₹500 as the application fee, which will be refunded fully or partially depending on category. Selection will be done through a Written Test and Skill Test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Assistant Teacher (Primary) Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-assistant-teacher-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 14:57:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-assistant-teacher-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Delhi Subordinate Services Selection Board (DSSSB) has released Notification No. 05/2025 for 1180 Assistant Teacher (Primary) posts. Eligible candidates can apply online from 17th September to 16th October 2025. Selection will be done through a computer-based examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Indian Coast Guard Navik/Yantrik CGEPT 2026 Admit Card Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-coast-guard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 12:28:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-coast-guard-2025/</guid>
      <description>भारतीय तटरक्षक बल ने CGEPT 01/2026 और 02/2026 के तहत नविक (GD/DB) और यांत्रिक पदों पर कुल 520 पदों पर भर्ती निकाली है। योग्यता के अनुसार 10वीं, 12वीं (फिजिक्स/मैथ्स) या डिप्लोमा धारक उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं। सभी श्रेणियों के लिए रिक्तियां उपलब्ध हैं। आवेदन प्रक्रिया ऑनलाइन है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ECIL Technical Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ecil-technical-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ecil-technical-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Electronics Corporation of India Limited (ECIL) has invited applications for 160 Technical Officer posts on contract basis through Advt. No. 17/2025. The contract is initially for 9 months and extendable up to 4 years based on project needs. Candidates with BE/B.Tech. in ECE, EEE, CSE, IT, Mechanical and related disciplines with minimum 1-year post-qualification experience are eligible. The salary ranges from ₹25,000 to ₹31,000 per month along with PF, TA/DA, paid leave and medical benefits. The selection will be done on the basis of academic marks, work experience and personal interview (no written exam). The online application window will remain open from 16th September to 22nd September 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.ecil.co.in&#34;&gt;www.ecil.co.in&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC APO Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 17:15:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has released the official notification for Assistant Prosecution Officer (APO) Recruitment 2025 with 182 vacancies. Eligible candidates with a Law degree (LLB) can apply online from 16 September 2025 to 16 October 2025 through the UPPSC portal. The selection process includes Prelims, Mains, and Interview, followed by document verification and medical examination. Applicants must be between 21 to 40 years of age as on 1 July 2025. The pay scale ranges from Rs. 47,600 to Rs. 1,51,100, offering a great career opportunity for law graduates in Uttar Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NFR Sports Quota Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nfr-sports-quota-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 16:15:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nfr-sports-quota-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Northeast Frontier Railway (NFR) has released the notification for Sports Quota Recruitment 2025-26 with a total of 56 vacancies across Level 1 to Level 5 posts. Eligible Indian sportspersons can apply online from 16 September 2025 to 15 October 2025. The recruitment is open in various sports disciplines including athletics, boxing, cricket, football, volleyball, weightlifting, basketball, archery, and more. Candidates will be selected based on their sports performance and trials, as no written exam will be conducted. The application fee is ₹500 for General candidates and ₹250 for SC/ST/Women/Minority/EBC, with partial refund available after appearing in trials.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Manager (Credit Analyst) Vacancy Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-manager-credit-analyst-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:41:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-manager-credit-analyst-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The State Bank of India (SBI) has released the SCO Recruitment 2025 notification for 63 Manager (Credit Analyst) posts in MMGS-III. Eligible candidates with MBA (Finance)/CA/CFA/ICWA and minimum 3 years’ corporate credit experience can apply online from 11th September to 2nd October 2025. Selection will be through shortlisting and interview, with postings anywhere in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army AFMS Medical Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/afms-medical-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:09:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/afms-medical-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Army Armed Forces Medical Services (AFMS) has announced 225 vacancies for Short Service Commission (SSC) Medical Officers in 2025. Eligible MBBS/PG candidates can apply online at join.afms.gov.in between 13 September and 3 October 2025. Selection will be based on NEET PG scores, interview, and medical tests.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC SR Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-sr-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 11:04:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-sr-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Cell (Southern Railway) has released the Sports Quota Recruitment 2025 for Level 1 to 5 posts, with a total of 67 vacancies. Candidates with educational qualifications ranging from 10th Pass/ITI to Graduate are eligible to apply depending on the post. The age limit for applicants is 18–25 years as of 1 January 2026, with age relaxation as per government rules. The application fee is Rs 500 for General/OBC/EWS and Rs 250 for SC/ST/PWD/ESM/Female candidates, which is refundable. Interested candidates must apply online through the official website rrcmas.in. The application process starts on 13 September 2025 and closes on 12 October 2025, while the trials date will be notified later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Lower Division Clerk LDC Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-lower-division-clerk-ldc-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 08:55:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-lower-division-clerk-ldc-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of Lower Division Clerk (LDC) posts with a total of 26 vacancies. Candidates who have passed Intermediate (10+2) in any stream from a recognized board and possess computer operation and typing skills are eligible to apply. This recruitment is primarily for domicile candidates of Bihar, who will receive reservation benefits as per their category. Candidates from other states can also apply but will be considered under the General (Unreserved) category only, without any reservation or age relaxation. The application process is completely online. Out of the total posts, 13 are for General, 3 for EWS, 4 for SC, 1 for ST, 2 for EBC, 2 for BC, and 1 for BC Female.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Manager &amp; Deputy Manager Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-manager-deputy-manager-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Sep 2025 11:28:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-manager-deputy-manager-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The State Bank of India (SBI) has announced the SBI SCO Recruitment 2025 for a total of 59 Specialist Cadre Officer vacancies on a regular basis, including the posts of Manager (MMGS-III) and Deputy Manager (MMGS-II) in the Digital Platforms domain. Candidates must hold a B.E./B.Tech. in IT, Computer Science, Electronics, Electrical, or related fields, or an MCA with at least 60% marks, while an MBA is preferred. Relevant work experience of 5 years for Manager and 3 years for Deputy Manager in Digital Payments, FinTech, CRM, or related fields is mandatory. The age limit is 28–35 years for Manager and 25–32 years for Deputy Manager (as on 31.08.2025). The application fee is ₹750 for General, OBC, and EWS candidates, while SC, ST, and PwBD candidates are exempted. The selection process will be based on shortlisting and interview. Eligible candidates can apply online from 11th September to 2nd October 2025 through the official SBI Careers website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOM Specialist Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bom-specialist-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:26:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bom-specialist-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Maharashtra has announced Specialist Officer Recruitment 2025 (Phase II) for Scale II to VI posts in IT, Credit, Legal, Risk, Treasury, and other departments. Online applications are open from 10th to 30th September 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC ER Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-er-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 10:01:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-er-sports-quota-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>RRC Eastern Railway has announced 50 vacancies under Sports Quota Recruitment 2025-26 for Group C and D posts. Eligible sportspersons can apply online from 10th September to 9th October 2025, and selection will be through field trials and document verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC SR Scouts &amp; Guides Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-sr-scouts-guides-quota-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 19:47:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-sr-scouts-guides-quota-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Southern Railway and Integral Coach Factory (ICF) invite applications from Indian citizens who are active members of Bharat Scouts &amp;amp; Guides for recruitment to Level-1 posts under the Scouts &amp;amp; Guides Quota for the year 2025-26. A total of 14 posts are available—12 in Southern Railway (2 posts each in Chennai, Tiruchchirappalli, Madurai, Palakkad, Thiruvananthapuram, and Salem) and 2 in ICF. Candidates must have a minimum educational qualification of 10th pass, ITI, or National Apprenticeship Certificate (NAC) from NCVT. The age limit varies by category: UR 18–33 years, OBC 18–36 years, and SC/ST 18–38 years as on 01-01-2026. The selection process includes a Written Test / Computer Based Test (CBT). The application fee is Rs. 500 for general candidates and Rs. 250 for reserved categories, refundable after appearing in the exam. These posts are open to all communities, and eligible candidates can apply online from 30.08.2025 to 29.09.2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Assistant Public Sanitation &amp; Waste Management Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-aps-and-wm-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2025 13:19:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-aps-and-wm-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) invites online applications for 54 posts of Assistant Public Sanitation &amp;amp; Waste Management Officer under the Department of Urban Development &amp;amp; Housing, Bihar. Candidates from all states of India, both male and female, are eligible. Required qualifications include a Bachelor’s degree in Chemistry/Environmental Science, B.E./B.Tech in Chemical/Civil/Environmental Science/Public Health Engineering/Biotechnology, or a degree in Planning/Architecture. Age limit (as of 01.08.2025) is 21–37 years for unreserved males, 21–40 years for unreserved females/OBC/EBC, and 21–42 years for SC/ST. Application fee is ₹100 (plus ₹200 biometric fee if Aadhaar is not provided). Apply online between 05.09.2025 and 30.09.2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bpsc.bihar.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.bpsc.bihar.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCI Assistant Manager &amp; Executive Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-assistant-manager-and-executive-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Sep 2025 10:15:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-assistant-manager-and-executive-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Shipping Corporation of India Ltd. (SCI) has invited applications for 75 vacancies of Assistant Manager (E2) and Executive (E0). The online application process will run from 06 September 2025 to 27 September 2025. Maximum age limit is 27 years (with relaxations as per Govt. norms). The selection process includes Online Test, Group Discussion, and Personal Interview. Application fee is ₹500 for UR/OBC-NCL/EWS and ₹100 for SC/ST/PwBD/ESM. Interested candidates can apply online through the official website shipindia.com</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Oil Engineers/Officers Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iocl-engineers-officers-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Sep 2025 15:34:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/iocl-engineers-officers-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Oil Corporation Limited (IOCL) has announced recruitment for Engineers/Officers (Grade A) in Chemical, Electrical, and Instrumentation disciplines through CBT 2025. Eligible candidates with B.Tech./B.E. degrees can apply online from 05/09/2025 to 21/09/2025, admit card will be available from 17/10/2025, and the CBT will be held on 31/10/2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC CDS II Admit Card 2025 Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-cds-ii-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:53:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-cds-ii-2025/</guid>
      <description>Combined Defence Services (CDS) II Exam 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC EPFO Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/upsc/epfo-eo-ao-apfc-posts-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 19:36:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/upsc/epfo-eo-ao-apfc-posts-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the Special Advertisement No. 52/2025 for direct recruitment to a total of 230 vacancies in the Employees’ Provident Fund Organisation (EPFO) under the Ministry of Labour and Employment. These include 156 posts of Enforcement Officer/Accounts Officer (EO/AO) and 74 posts of Assistant Provident Fund Commissioner (APFC). Candidates must hold a Bachelor’s Degree from a recognized university. For the APFC post, qualifications such as a degree in Law, MBA, CA, or equivalent are desirable. The online application process will begin on July 29, 2025, and close on August 18, 2025. Selection will be based on a written examination, and postings will be across India. Interested candidates can apply online at &lt;a href=&#34;https://upsconline.nic.in&#34;&gt;https://upsconline.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Assistant Professor Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-professor-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 16:28:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-assistant-professor-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC has announced Assistant Professor Recruitment 2025 for 1253 posts in Government Degree Colleges. Online applications are open from 4 September to 6 October 2025. Candidates with a PG degree and UGC-NET can apply</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC 1st Grade Teacher Agriculture Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-1st-grade-teacher-agriculture-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:19:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-1st-grade-teacher-agriculture-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has announced the RPSC 1st Grade Teacher (Agriculture) Recruitment 2025 for a total of 500 posts of School Lecturer in the Secondary Education Department. Candidates must have a 4-year Bachelor’s degree in Agriculture or Horticulture, a Postgraduate degree in the relevant subject, and a B.Ed. from an NCTE-recognized institution, along with knowledge of Hindi in Devanagari script and Rajasthani culture. The online application process will be open from 4th September to 3rd October 2025, with the written examination expected between 31st May and 16th June 2026. The selection process will be based on a written test, document verification, and medical examination, and the post carries a salary under Pay Matrix Level L-12 with Grade Pay ₹4800.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Sub Inspector Vacancy 2025 Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-police-si-posts-jul-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 19:38:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-police-si-posts-jul-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released the official notification for Rajasthan Police SI and Platoon Commander Recruitment 2025-26 under advertisement number 05/Exam/SI-PC/RPSC/EP-I/2025-26. A total of 1015 vacancies have been announced for various posts including Sub Inspector (AP, IB, Sahariya, Scheduled Area) and Platoon Commander (RAC). Candidates holding a graduate degree and having knowledge of Hindi in Devanagari script and Rajasthani culture are eligible to apply. The online application process will begin on 10 August 2025 and the last date to apply is 08 September 2025. Applicants from all states of India can apply for general posts, while certain reserved posts are limited to Rajasthan domicile candidates only.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO SAC Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-sac-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 11:18:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-sac-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>SAC, ISRO Ahmedabad has invited online applications for 13 posts of Project Scientist-I and Project Associate-I under Advertisement No. SAC:01:2025. Eligible candidates can apply online from 02 September to 22 September 2025. Selection will be done through interviews in October–November 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NHPC Non-Executive Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhpc-non-executive-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 10:17:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/nhpc-non-executive-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The NHPC Non-Executive Recruitment 2025 has been announced for 248 vacancies including Junior Engineers, Sr. Accountant, Supervisor (IT), Assistant Rajbhasha Officer, and Hindi Translator. Eligible candidates can apply online at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.nhpcindia.com&#34;&gt;www.nhpcindia.com&lt;/a&gt; from 2nd September to 1st October 2025. The selection will be through a Computer-Based Test (CBT)/Written Exam followed by document verification, with pay scales up to ₹1.40 lakh per month.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Polytechnic Department Head Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-hod-department-head-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:46:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-hod-department-head-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has announced 218 vacancies for the post of Department Head in Government and Women Polytechnic Colleges. Eligible candidates with the required academic qualifications and teaching/industry experience can apply online from 02 September 2025 to 30 September 2025. The minimum age is 33 years, there is no upper age limit, and the retirement age is 65 years.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy SSC Officers Vacancy 2025 June 2026 Course</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/join-indian-navy-ssc-officers-vacancy-aug-25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 19:25:22 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/join-indian-navy-ssc-officers-vacancy-aug-25/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Navy is recruiting SSC Officers for Executive, Education, and Technical branches under the June 2026 course at INA Ezhimala. A total of 256 vacancies are open for eligible unmarried candidates. Applications will be accepted online from 9 August to 1 September 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar SHS Lab Technician Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-shs-lab-technician-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 11:27:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-shs-lab-technician-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The State Health Society, Bihar invites online applications for 1075 posts of Laboratory Technicians, including 1068 Lab Technician and 7 Senior Lab Technician (NTEP) vacancies. Candidates must have 10+2 (Physics, Chemistry, Biology) with DMLT/BMLT or relevant M.Sc./B.Sc. qualifications for senior posts. The selection will be based on a Computer-Based Test (CBT) followed by document verification. Application fees range from ₹125 to ₹500 depending on category. Salary offered is ₹15,000 for Lab Technician and ₹24,000 for Senior Lab Technician.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC AES Assistant Environmental Scientist Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-aes-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 11:08:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-aes-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has invited applications for 17 Assistant Environmental Scientist (AES) posts under the Department of Environment, Forest &amp;amp; Climate Change. Eligible candidates with a B.Sc./M.Sc. degree in Environmental Science, Chemistry, Physics, or Life Sciences can apply online from 27 August to 19 September 2025 at bpsc.bihar.gov.in. Selection will be through a written exam and interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AAI Junior Executive JE Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aai-junior-executive-je-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2025 10:13:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aai-junior-executive-je-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The application process for the recruitment will begin on 28 August 2025 and remain open until 27 September 2025. Interested and eligible candidates are advised to complete their registration within the given dates to avoid last-minute issues. Applicants should carefully read the official notification, check the eligibility criteria, and prepare the required documents before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BOB Local Bank Officers LBO Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/bob-lbo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 16:05:01 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/bob-lbo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda (BOB) has announced 2500 vacancies for the post of Local Bank Officer (JMG/S-I) across multiple states. Candidates must hold a graduation degree in any discipline from a recognized university. Professional qualifications like CA, Engineering, or Medical are also accepted. Applicants must have at least 1 year of experience as an officer in a Scheduled Commercial Bank or Regional Rural Bank listed under the Second Schedule of the RBI. Experience in NBFCs, cooperative banks, and fintechs will not be considered. The recruitment is open state-wise with preference for candidates familiar with the local language.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Junior Legal Officer (JLO) Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-jlo-junior-legal-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 11:18:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-jlo-junior-legal-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>RPSC has announced 12 vacancies for the post of Junior Legal Officer (JLO) in the Jaipur Development Authority (JDA) through notification number 11/Exam/JLO/JDA/EP-I/2025-26. Interested and eligible Law graduates can apply online between 27 August 2025 to 25 September 2025. The recruitment process includes a written examination and document verification. Candidates must carefully read the notification for eligibility, application fees, and reservation details before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Oil India Limited Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oil-india-limited-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Aug 2025 10:39:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/oil-india-limited-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Oil India Limited, a Maharatna PSU, has released its Recruitment Notification 2025 for a total of 102 vacancies in Grade A, B, and C posts. The vacancies include positions such as Superintending Engineer, Senior Officers in various disciplines (Chemical, Civil, Electrical, Mechanical, IT, Petroleum, HR, Legal, Finance, Public Affairs, Geology, Geophysics, Electronics &amp;amp; Communication, Fire &amp;amp; Safety, HSE, Security, Company Secretary), along with Confidential Secretary and Hindi Officer. Both male and female candidates are eligible to apply. The application process is completely online, starting from 26 August 2025 and closing on 26 September 2025. Candidates will be selected through Computer Based Test (CBT), Personal Interview, and Skill/Proficiency Test as per the post. The recruitment offers attractive pay scales ranging from ₹50,000 to ₹2,20,000 plus allowances, making it a great opportunity for engineering and non-engineering graduates to build a career with Oil India Limited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Federal Bank Associate Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/federal-bank-ao-associate-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:32:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/federal-bank-ao-associate-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Federal Bank has invited applications for the post of Associate Officer (Sales) under its 2025 recruitment drive. The online application window is open from 25/08/2025 to 03/09/2025. Candidates must be graduates with at least 50% aggregate marks in Class X, Class XII/Diploma, and Graduation, and should also hold a valid two- or four-wheeler driving license. The upper age limit is 27 years (born on or after 01/08/1998), and applicants must be domiciled in Gujarat, Telangana, West Bengal, or Delhi NCR. An application fee of ₹350 (non-refundable) is payable online. The selection process consists of a center-based online aptitude test followed by a personal interview, with selected candidates placed on a one-year probation. The role offers a salary package between ₹4.59 and ₹6.19 LPA, along with additional benefits such as medical coverage, NPS, and career progression opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Chauffeur &amp; Process Server Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-despatch-rider-jobs-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:06:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-despatch-rider-jobs-2025/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB Recruitment 2025 (Advt. No. 04/2025) has been announced for 20 Group C posts of Chauffeur and Despatch Rider-cum-Process Server in Delhi High Court. Eligible 10th pass candidates with a valid driving license and 2 years’ experience can apply online from 26th August to 24th September 2025 at dsssbonline.nic.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Delhi High Court Various Post Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-delhi-high-court-various-post-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 16:03:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-delhi-high-court-various-post-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB has announced 334 vacancies under Advt No. 03/2025 for various posts in the Delhi High Court, including Security Attendant, Court Attendant, and Room Attendant. The online application process will run from 26 August to 24 September 2025. Candidates with 10th pass or ITI qualification are eligible to apply. The recruitment offers a Level-3 pay scale (₹21,700–₹69,100), with an application fee of ₹100 for General/OBC/EWS and exemptions for SC/ST/PwBD/Women/Ex-servicemen. Selection will be through a computer-based test and subsequent stages as per the post.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Prosecutor &amp; Lecturer Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-prosecutor-lecturer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2025 10:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-prosecutor-lecturer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has announced 84 vacancies through Advertisement No. 12/2025. The recruitment includes Assistant Public Prosecutor (19 posts) and Public Prosecutor (25 posts) in CBI as well as 40 Lecturer posts in Botany, Chemistry, Economics, History, Home Science, Physics, Psychology, Sociology, and Zoology under the School Education Department of UT Ladakh. Eligible candidates can apply online between 23/08/2025 to 11/09/2025. The selection will be based on interview or recruitment test followed by interview. This recruitment offers an excellent opportunity for Law Graduates and Postgraduates with B.Ed. to secure government jobs in prestigious departments.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Stenographer Grade C &amp; D Answer Key 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-grade-c-and-d-stenographer-jun2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 20:14:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-grade-c-and-d-stenographer-jun2025/</guid>
      <description>SSC स्टेनोग्राफर ग्रुप C और D भर्ती 2025 के लिए उम्मीदवारों को किसी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 (इंटरमीडिएट) परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण होना चाहिए। ट्रांसक्रिप्शन समय ग्रुप D के लिए अंग्रेज़ी में 50 मिनट और हिंदी में 65 मिनट है, जबकि ग्रुप C के लिए अंग्रेज़ी में 40 मिनट और हिंदी में 55 मिनट निर्धारित है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patna High Court Stenographer Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/patna-hc-steno-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:52:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/patna-hc-steno-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Patna High Court has invited applications for 111 Stenographer posts through its Recruitment 2025 notification. The vacancies include 68 regular and 43 backlog posts. Candidates who have passed Intermediate (12th) with English Shorthand (80 WPM), English Typing (40 WPM) and a 6-month Computer Course are eligible to apply. The online application process will be open from 21st August 2025 to 19th September 2025 on the official website. The selection process will consist of a Written Test, Skill Test, and Interview. Selected candidates will receive a salary in Level-4 (₹25,500 – ₹81,100) with allowances.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy Civilian INCET Vacancy 2025 Admit Card Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-civilian-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 16:23:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-civilian-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Navy has released the INCET 01/2025 notification for the recruitment of 1097 civilian posts under Group B and Group C categories across various naval commands. Eligible candidates can apply online through the official website for posts like Chargeman, Tradesman Mate, Fireman, Pharmacist, Storekeeper, MTS, and more. The selection process includes a written exam and document verification. Applicants must check post-wise qualifications, age limits, and category-wise vacancies before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AFCAT 2 2025 Admit Card – Indian Air Force</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/force/afcat-02-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:58:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/force/afcat-02-2025/</guid>
      <description>Indian Air Force has released the AFCAT 02/2025 notification for the recruitment of Commissioned Officers in Flying and Ground Duty (Technical and Non-Technical) branches. Eligible candidates with a graduate or engineering degree can apply online through the official website. The application process is expected to start in June 2025, with the last date likely in July 2025. The selection will be based on a written exam, AFSB interview, and medical test. Candidates must pay ₹250 as the application fee. For complete details, visit afcat.cdac.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Senior Teacher Grade IV Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-senior-teacher-grade-iv-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 19:54:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-senior-teacher-grade-iv-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released the notification for Senior Teacher Recruitment 2025 under the Secondary Education Department. A total of 6500 vacancies are available in 10 subjects including Hindi, English, Maths, Science, Sanskrit, and more. Eligible candidates can apply online from 19 August to 17 September 2025. Candidates from all states can apply, but reservation and age relaxation are applicable only for Rajasthan domicile candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Delhi Various Post Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-non-teaching-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 09:24:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-non-teaching-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>Delhi Subordinate Services Selection Board (DSSSB) has announced 615 vacancies through Advertisement No. 02/2025 for various Non-Teaching posts across multiple departments under the Government of NCT of Delhi. The recruitment includes Group B and C positions such as Statistical Clerk, Junior Engineer, Mason, Forest Guard, TGT (Special Education), Music Teacher, Naib Tehsildar, and others. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online from 18 August 2025 to 16 September 2025 via the official website. The notification provides detailed information on post-wise eligibility, pay level, age limit, and selection criteria.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WBSSC Assistant Teacher Admit Card 2025 – Download Hall Ticket</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbssc-assistant-teacher-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 19:39:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/wbssc-assistant-teacher-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The West Bengal Central School Service Commission (WBSSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of 35,726 Assistant Teachers for classes 9 to 12 in government schools. Eligible candidates with a minimum of 50% marks in Graduation/Post Graduation and a B.Ed or equivalent degree can apply online within the specified dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Enforcement Sub Inspector Exam Notice 2025 – Download PDF &amp; Full Details</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-enforcement-si-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2025 10:44:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/bpssc-enforcement-si-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Police Subordinate Services Commission (BPSSC)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Bihar Nursing Tutor Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-bihar-nursing-tutor-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 18:42:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/btsc-bihar-nursing-tutor-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has released a notification for the recruitment of 498 Nursing Tutors under the Health Department, Government of Bihar. Candidates holding M.Sc Nursing, B.Sc Nursing (Basic/Post Basic), or a Diploma in Nursing Education &amp;amp; Administration (DNEA) are eligible to apply. The selection process includes eligibility verification and document scrutiny as per INC and Bihar Nursing Council norms. 35% of the vacancies are reserved for female candidates. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official BTSC website within the given time frame.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC School Lecturer Vacancy 2025 Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-school-lecturer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:08:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-school-lecturer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released a recruitment notification for 3225 vacancies for the post of School Lecturer (Grade-I) in various subjects including Hindi, English, Political Science, Geography, History, Physics, Chemistry, Commerce, Drawing, Physical Education, Music, and Sports Coaching categories like Athletics, Basketball, etc. Candidates must possess a Postgraduate degree in the relevant subject along with B.Ed. or an equivalent teaching qualification. The application process will be conducted online through the official RPSC portal from 14 August 2025 to 12 September 2025. Applicants from all Indian states are eligible to apply; however, only Rajasthan state candidates will receive category-based reservation and fee relaxation. Candidates from other states will be considered under the General category.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HP JBT Teacher Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hp-junior-basic-teacher-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 10:01:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hp-junior-basic-teacher-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Himachal Pradesh Rajya Chayan Aayog (HPRCA) has announced the HP JBT Teacher Recruitment 2025 for Junior Basic Teacher (Job Trainee) posts under the Elementary Education Department. The online application process will start on 14 August 2025 and close on 17 September 2025. Eligible candidates with the required educational qualifications and TET certificate can apply through the official website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC GIC Lecturer Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-gic-lecturer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 14:13:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-gic-lecturer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission (UPPSC) has announced the UPPSC GIC Lecturer Recruitment 2025 for a total of 1,518 vacancies in various Government Inter Colleges across the state. The vacancies include 777 posts in the Male Branch, 694 posts in the Female Branch, 45 posts in Sparsh Government Inter College for Special Education, and 2 posts in the Uttar Pradesh Jail Training School (Teaching Staff). Candidates must possess a Post Graduate degree in the relevant subject along with a B.Ed. from an NCTE-recognized institution, with additional qualifications required for special and jail training school posts. The online application process will run from 12 August 2025 to 12 September 2025, and selection will be conducted through a Preliminary Examination, Main Written Examination, and Document Verification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPSC Assistant District Attorney ADA Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hpsc-assistant-district-attorney-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 10:42:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hpsc-assistant-district-attorney-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>HPSC has announced 255 Assistant District Attorney (ADA) vacancies under Advt. No. 18/2025. The online application process will run from 13 August to 2 September 2025 through the official website hpsc.gov.in. Candidates must hold an LLB degree and meet the age criteria of 21–42 years. The selection process includes a screening test and a subject knowledge test. The post carries a pay scale of FPL-9 (₹53,100–₹1,67,800).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPSC AE, Municipal Engineer &amp; Sub Divisional Engineer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hpsc-ae-me-sd-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 20:44:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hpsc-ae-me-sd-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Haryana Public Service Commission (HPSC) has announced 153 Civil Engineer vacancies in various departments including Public Works (B&amp;amp;R), Municipal Corporation, and Panchayati Raj. The posts include Assistant Engineer, Municipal Engineer, and Sub Divisional Engineer for candidates holding a B.E./B.Tech in Civil Engineering (AICTE approved). The online application process will start from 12 August 2025 and will remain open until 1 September 2025, 5:00 PM. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official HPSC website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda Sales Manager &amp; Agriculture Officer Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bob-sales-manager-officer-vacancy-aug-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 10:27:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bob-sales-manager-officer-vacancy-aug-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has announced its Recruitment Drive 2025 for a total of 417 vacancies across two departments—Retail Liabilities and Rural &amp;amp; Agri Banking. The available posts include Manager – Sales, Officer – Agriculture Sales, and Manager – Agriculture Sales. The online application process begins on 6th August 2025 and closes on 26th August 2025. Candidates must hold relevant educational qualifications such as a graduation degree (with preference for MBA/PGDM in Sales/Marketing) or a 4-year degree in Agriculture-related fields. Prior work experience in sales or agri-sales (preferably in the BFSI sector) is mandatory. The selection process may include an online test, psychometric assessment, group discussion, and/or interview. Selected candidates will be posted anywhere in India and must commit to a 3-year service bond. Interested applicants are advised to visit the official Bank of Baroda website to read the full notification and apply online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Veterinary Officer Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/psc-veterinary-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 15:30:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/psc-veterinary-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has announced 1100 vacancies for the post of Veterinary Officer under the Animal Husbandry Department. The recruitment is open to candidates holding a Bachelor’s Degree in Veterinary Science and Animal Husbandry or its equivalent from a recognized university in India, along with knowledge of Hindi in Devanagari script and Rajasthani culture. The application process will be conducted online, starting from 5 August 2025 and closing on 3 September 2025. The vacancies are distributed among various categories, including General (360), SC (198), ST (183), OBC (209), MBC (50), and EWS (100), with a total of 1100 posts available</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haryana HPSC ADO Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hpsc-ado-posts-aug25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2025 14:23:17 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hpsc-ado-posts-aug25/</guid>
      <description>Haryana Public Service Commission (HPSC) has released the notification for the recruitment of 785 Agricultural Development Officer (ADO) posts under the Administrative Cadre (Group-B) in the Agriculture and Farmers Welfare Department, Haryana. Candidates possessing a B.Sc. (Hons) in Agriculture and having studied Hindi or Sanskrit up to Matric or higher are eligible to apply. The online application process will begin on 5th August 2025 and will remain open until 25th August 2025 (up to 5:00 PM). Applicants must be between 18 to 42 years of age as on 01 July 2025. The selected candidates will be placed in Pay Level-6 of the 7th CPC pay matrix, with a salary range of ₹35,400 to ₹1,12,400. All 27 PwBD reserved posts are included in the total of 785 vacancies. Interested candidates can apply through the official HPSC website at hpsc.gov.in. Category-wise vacancy breakup, reservation rules, fee details, and application instructions are available in the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRC Western Railway Sports Quota Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-western-railway-sports-quota-posts-aug25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Aug 2025 13:13:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rrc-western-railway-sports-quota-posts-aug25/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Cell (RRC), Western Railway has released a notification for Sports Quota Recruitment 2025-26, inviting online applications from eligible sportspersons across India. A total of 64 vacancies will be filled, which include 5 posts under Level 5/4 (Group C) for graduates, 16 posts under Level 3/2 (Group C) for candidates with 12th pass, ITI, Diploma, or Apprenticeship, and 43 posts under Level 1 (Group D) for candidates who have passed 10th, ITI, NAC, or hold a Diploma. The recruitment is open for various disciplines such as Cricket, Kabaddi, Wrestling, Athletics, Football, Basketball, and more. The selection will be based on sports achievements and trial performance—no written exam will be conducted. The online application process begins on 30 July 2025 and will close on 29 August 2025 via the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.rrc-wr.com&#34;&gt;www.rrc-wr.com&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy SSC Executive (IT) Vacancy Jan 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-ssc-executive-it-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Aug 2025 09:49:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-navy-ssc-executive-it-jul25/</guid>
      <description>Commission (SSC) in Information Technology (Executive Branch) for the January 2026 course. A total of 15 vacancies are available. Applicants must hold a degree in BE/B.Tech/M.Tech/MCA/MSc in Computer Science, Information Technology, Artificial Intelligence, Cyber Security, or related fields with a minimum of 60% marks, along with at least 60% marks in English in Class 10 or 12. Eligible candidates should be born between 02 January 2001 and 01 July 2006 (both dates inclusive). The online application window opens on 02 August 2025 and closes on 17 August 2025. The selection process includes shortlisting based on normalized marks, SSB interview, medical examination, and merit list. Selected candidates will be appointed as Sub Lieutenants and undergo training at the Indian Naval Academy (INA), Ezhimala, Kerala. The initial service tenure is 10 years, which may be extended up to 14 years (10+2+2) based on performance and service requirements. The basic pay starts at ₹56,100/- plus applicable allowances. For more details and to apply online, visit the official website: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joinindiannavy.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.joinindiannavy.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda BOB Varios Post Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/bob-dm-am-avp-posts-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 20:34:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/bob-dm-am-avp-posts-jul25/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has announced the recruitment of 330 contractual officers for various departments including Digital Banking, MSME Sales, and Risk Management. The online application process is open from 30th July to 19th August 2025. The posts include Assistant Manager, Deputy Manager, and AVP roles, requiring relevant educational qualifications and work experience. The selection will be based on shortlisting and personal interviews. Candidates must maintain a minimum CIBIL score of 680 and be willing to work anywhere in India.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC Combined Translator Exam 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-combined-translator-jun2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 16:55:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc-junior-combined-translator-jun2025/</guid>
      <description>कर्मचारी चयन आयोग (SSC) ने जूनियर हिंदी अनुवादक (JHT), सीनियर हिंदी अनुवादक (SHT) और अन्य पदों पर भर्ती हेतु अधिसूचना जारी की है। पात्र अभ्यर्थी ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCI Court Master Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-court-master-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 19:51:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-court-master-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The Supreme Court of India has invited online applications for 30 posts of Court Master (Shorthand) in 2025. Eligible candidates must be between 30 to 45 years of age and hold a graduate degree with shorthand speed of 120 w.p.m. and computer typing speed of 40 w.p.m., along with at least 5 years of experience in a relevant government or public sector post. The selection process includes a Shorthand Test, Written Test, Typing Speed Test, and Interview. Candidates with a law degree will receive additional weightage. Applications can be submitted online through the official website of the Supreme Court at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.sci.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.sci.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Assistant Agriculture Engineer AAE Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-assistant-agriculture-engineer-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 09:13:58 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rpsc-assistant-agriculture-engineer-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released the notification for the recruitment of Assistant Agriculture Engineer (AAE) 2025 with a total of 281 vacancies. Candidates must hold a Bachelor’s Degree in Agricultural Engineering from a recognized university to be eligible. Additionally, applicants should have a working knowledge of Hindi written in Devanagari script and a good understanding of Rajasthan’s culture. The online application process will be open from 28 July 2025 to 26 August 2025. Vacancies are distributed across various categories including General, OBC, SC, ST, EWS, and MBC. Candidates are advised to check the detailed notification and ensure they meet the eligibility criteria before applying</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Assistant Director (Systems) Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-assistant-director-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 18:48:44 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-assistant-director-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released Advertisement No. 10/2025 inviting online applications for the post of Assistant Director (Systems) in the Directorate of Income Tax (Systems), Department of Revenue, Ministry of Finance. A total of 45 vacancies are available under various categories including UR, EWS, OBC, SC, ST, and PwBD. The position is classified as Group ‘A’ Gazetted, Non-Ministerial and offers a Level-10 pay scale under the 7th CPC. Candidates with qualifications such as BE/B.Tech, M.Tech, MCA, or equivalent in Computer Science/Applications along with relevant experience in electronic data processing are eligible to apply. The role involves software development, debugging, maintenance, and supervision of technical staff. The headquarters is in New Delhi, but the selected candidates can be posted anywhere in India. The last date to apply online is 14 August 2025, and applications must be submitted through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://upsconline.gov.in/ora/&#34;&gt;https://upsconline.gov.in/ora/&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Army Agniveer CEE Result Declared 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/army-agniveer-cee-mar25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:18:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/army-agniveer-cee-mar25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;Indian Army Common Entrance Exam CEE Exam 2025-26&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Join Indian Army (Bhartiya Sena)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification Army Agniveer Rally Exam 2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-content&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;       &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application Begin: &lt;strong&gt;12/03/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Date for Apply Online: &lt;strong style=&#34;color:rgb(224, 86, 22);&#34;&gt;25/04/2025 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Agniveer Exam Date: &lt;strong&gt;June 2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available: &lt;strong&gt;Before Exam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Result Available: &lt;strong&gt;26/07/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General / OBC / EWS: &lt;strong&gt;250/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SC / ST: &lt;strong&gt;250/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Pay the Examination Fee Through Debit Card / Credit Card / Net Banking.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;       &#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Age Limit Details 2025&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For Agniveer GD / Technical / Assistant / Tradesman: &lt;strong&gt;17.5 to 21 Years&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For Soldier Technical: &lt;strong&gt;17.5 to 23 Years (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For Sepoy Pharma: &lt;strong&gt;19-25 Years (&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;For JCO Religious Teacher: &lt;strong&gt;25-34 Years as on 01/10/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;JCO Catering: &lt;strong&gt;21-27 Years as on 01/10/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Havildar: &lt;strong&gt;20-25 Years as on 01/10/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            &lt;span class=&#34;job-important&#34;&gt;Age relaxation as per rules of Army Agniveer Rally Exam 2025.&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSF Constable Sports Quota Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-sports-quota-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 10:29:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/bsf-constable-sports-quota-jul25/</guid>
      <description>Border Security Force (BSF) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Constable (General Duty) under Sports Quota 2025. A total of 241 vacancies are available for meritorious male and female sportspersons who have participated at national or international levels. Candidates must have passed Class 10th (Matric) from a recognized board and must possess valid sports certificates. The application process is completely online and starts from 25 July 2025. Eligible candidates can apply before the last date, 20 August 2025. This is a golden opportunity for young sportspersons to serve in BSF with pride.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join Indian Army SSC Tech Men (66) April 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-ssc-tech-men-66-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 20:12:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-ssc-tech-men-66-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Army has invited applications for the 66th Short Service Commission (Technical) Men Entry for the course commencing in April 2026. A total of 350 vacancies are available for unmarried male engineering graduates in various disciplines including Civil, Mechanical, Electrical, Computer Science, and others. Candidates must be between 20 to 27 years of age as on 01 April 2026. Final year students who will complete their degree before April 2026 are also eligible to apply. The selection process includes shortlisting of applications, SSB interview, medical examination, and merit list preparation. Selected candidates will undergo 49 weeks of training at the Officers Training Academy (OTA), Chennai, and will be commissioned as Lieutenants. During training, cadets will receive a stipend of ₹56,100 per month. The online application process will be open from 24 July 2025 to 22 August 2025 on the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.joinindianarmy.nic.in&#34;&gt;www.joinindianarmy.nic.in&lt;/a&gt;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army SSCW Tech Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-sscw-tech-non-tech-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 17:58:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/indian-army-sscw-tech-non-tech-jul25/</guid>
      <description>ndian Army has announced SSCW (Tech) 66 Women Recruitment 2025, offering 31 vacancies for women candidates including engineering graduates and widows of Defence Personnel. Eligible unmarried women and widows can apply online from 23 July 2025 to 21 August 2025. The course will begin in April 2026 at Officers Training Academy (OTA), and selected candidates will undergo 49 weeks of training before commissioning as Lieutenants.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSSB Platoon Commander Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-platoon-commander-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 11:30:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rssb-platoon-commander-jul25/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Staff Selection Board (RSSB) has invited online applications for the post of Platoon Commander under the Rajasthan Home Guard Department. A total of 84 vacancies are available for this Group B, non-gazetted government job. Candidates must possess a graduation degree, along with knowledge of Hindi written in Devanagari script and familiarity with Rajasthan&amp;rsquo;s culture. Only those who have appeared in the CET (Graduation Level) 2024 exam are eligible to apply. Selected candidates will be placed under a 2-year probation period with fixed monthly remuneration. The pay scale is as per Pay Matrix Level-10 (₹9300–34800 + Grade Pay ₹3600). Applications are accepted online only through the official RSSB portal.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bank of Baroda Various Posts Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/bob-various-posts-jul25/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 18:48:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/bob-various-posts-jul25/</guid>
      <description>Bank of Baroda has released the official notification for the recruitment of 41 Specialist Officer posts on a regular basis across various departments including Digital Banking, Information Technology, Information Security, and Fire &amp;amp; Safety. The available positions include Manager, Senior Manager, Chief Manager, and Fire Safety Officer. Candidates must possess qualifications such as BE/B.Tech, MCA, or M.Sc in relevant disciplines, along with specific certifications like CEH, CISSP, or CISA for select roles. The application process is completely online and starts from 23 July 2025, with the last date being 12 August 2025. The selection may include an online test followed by a group discussion or personal interview. The jobs are regular and full-time, with postings across India. Interested candidates can apply through the official website &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.bankofbaroda.in&#34;&gt;www.bankofbaroda.in&lt;/a&gt;. Category-wise vacancy details (UR/SC/ST/OBC/EWS) have not been disclosed in the notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SGPGI Nursing Officer &amp; Non Teaching Post 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sgpgi-nursing-officer-and-non-teaching-post-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2025 16:24:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sgpgi-nursing-officer-and-non-teaching-post-2025/</guid>
      <description>SGPGI लखनऊ द्वारा वर्ष 2025 में नर्सिंग ऑफिसर एवं विभिन्न गैर-शिक्षण पदों पर भर्ती हेतु अधिसूचना जारी की गई है। इस भर्ती के अंतर्गत कुल 1479 पदों पर भर्तियाँ की जाएंगी, जिनमें नर्सिंग ऑफिसर, हॉस्पिटल अटेंडेंट, स्टेनोग्राफर, अकाउंट्स ऑफिसर, टेक्निकल ऑफिसर, OT असिस्टेंट, CSSD असिस्टेंट, मेडिकल सोशल सर्विस ऑफिसर जैसे ग्रुप B एवं C श्रेणी के पद शामिल हैं। आवेदन हेतु शैक्षणिक योग्यता 10वीं, 12वीं, स्नातक, डिप्लोमा, B.Sc, B.Com, आदि मांगी गई है, साथ ही कुछ पदों के लिए कार्यानुभव भी आवश्यक है। इस भर्ती के लिए भारत के सभी राज्यों के उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं, लेकिन आरक्षण का लाभ केवल उत्तर प्रदेश के मूल निवासियों को मिलेगा। आवेदन प्रक्रिया केवल ऑनलाइन होगी, और वेतनमान पद के अनुसार निर्धारित होगा। इच्छुक उम्मीदवार विस्तृत जानकारी के लिए आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़ें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aadhaar Operator / Supervisor Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aadhaar-supervisor-vacancy-july-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 20:40:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aadhaar-supervisor-vacancy-july-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Aadhaar Operator/Supervisor recruitment 2025 has been announced for various states across India. Eligible candidates with UIDAI certification can apply online through the official CSC Cloud Career portal. This opportunity is ideal for candidates looking to work at district levels in Aadhaar enrollment and update centers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HRRL Various Posts Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hrrl-various-posts-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 17:39:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hrrl-various-posts-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Hindustan Petroleum Rajasthan Refinery Limited (HRRL) has released a recruitment notification for 131 vacancies across various departments including Engineering (Chemical, Mechanical, Electrical, Civil, Instrumentation), HR, Finance, Legal, Fire &amp;amp; Safety, and Medical.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army SSC Tech Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-ssc-tech-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Jul 2025 12:00:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-army-ssc-tech-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Army has released the short notification for SSC Technical Entry 66th Course for Men and Women. A total of 379 vacancies are available, including 350 for men and 29 for women. The course will commence in April 2026 at Officers Training Academy (OTA), Chennai. Candidates with a Degree in Engineering (B.E. / B.Tech) in relevant disciplines are eligible to apply. The online application process will begin on 16 July 2025 and continue until 14 August 2025 through the official website joinindianarmy.nic.in. This is a great opportunity for aspiring engineers to join the Indian Army as Short Service Commission Officers.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chandigarh High Court Reader (Legal) Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/chandigarh-high-court-reader-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 19:42:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/chandigarh-high-court-reader-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Punjab and Haryana High Court, Chandigarh has invited online applications for 60 posts of Reader (Legal). Eligible candidates must have 10+2 with 60% marks in English, an LL.B. degree, and computer proficiency. The selection process includes a written exam, computer proficiency test, and viva-voce. The application process is open from 14 July 2025 to 04 August 2025. Candidates are advised to check the official notification for detailed eligibility, syllabus, and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Chandigarh High Court Peon Vacancy 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/chandigarh-high-court-peon-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Jul 2025 18:47:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/chandigarh-high-court-peon-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Chandigarh High Court has invited online applications for 75 posts of Peon (Residential). Eligible candidates with 10th pass qualification, 1-year diploma in cooking/culinary arts, and 3 years of cooking experience can apply from 14 July to 4 August 2025 at &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.highcourtchd.gov.in&#34;&gt;www.highcourtchd.gov.in&lt;/a&gt;. Applicants from all states are eligible, but reservation and fee relaxation are available only for residents of Punjab, Haryana, and Chandigarh. Selection will be based on a practical test (80 marks) and interview (20 marks). Application fee is ₹700 for general and ₹600 for reserved categories.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jharkhand SSC ANM Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jharkhand-ssc-anm-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 18:27:16 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jharkhand-ssc-anm-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Jharkhand Staff Selection Commission (JSSC) has released the official notification for the recruitment of Female Health Workers (A.N.M.) under the Regular and Backlog vacancies for the year 2025. A total of 3,181 posts are available, including 3,020 regular and 161 backlog vacancies. Only female candidates who are domicile of Jharkhand and have completed 10th (Matric) with at least 45% marks, along with 18 months A.N.M. training and registration in Jharkhand State Nursing Council, are eligible to apply. The application process will be conducted online through the official JSSC website. Interested and eligible candidates must read the official notification thoroughly and apply within the specified dates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI CBO 2025 Exam Date/ Admitcard</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-circle-based-officers-cbo-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 12:31:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sbi-circle-based-officers-cbo-2025/</guid>
      <description>SBI ने 2025 के लिए सर्कल बेस्ड ऑफिसर (CBO) भर्ती का नोटिफिकेशन जारी किया है। उम्मीदवारों को किसी भी विषय में स्नातक होना चाहिए और किसी बैंक में अधिकारी पद पर कम से कम 2 साल का अनुभव जरूरी है। आवेदनकर्ता को उस सर्कल की स्थानीय भाषा का ज्ञान होना चाहिए जिसमें वे आवेदन कर रहे हैं। चयन प्रक्रिया में ऑनलाइन परीक्षा, स्क्रीनिंग, इंटरव्यू और (जरूरत पड़ने पर) भाषा परीक्षण शामिल हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSBC Bihar Police Constable Admitcard Available 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/csbc-bp-constable-01-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 11:19:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/csbc-bp-constable-01-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;CSBC Bihar Police Constable Recruitment 2025&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Central Selection Board of Constable CSBC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification Bihar Police Advt No. : 01/2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-content&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;       &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application Begin: &lt;strong&gt;18/03/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Date for Apply Online: &lt;strong style=&#34;color:red;&#34;&gt;25/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay Exam Fee Last Date: &lt;strong&gt;25/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam Date: &lt;strong&gt;16/07/2025 to 03/08/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available: &lt;strong&gt;09/07/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available : &lt;strong&gt;7 July 2025 (10 Days before Exam)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam date: 13 July to 6 August 2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General / OBC / EWS / Other State: &lt;strong&gt;675/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SC / ST: &lt;strong&gt;180/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:blue;&#34;&gt;Pay the Examination Fee Through Debit Card, Credit Card, Net Banking or Pay Offline Fee Payment Through E Challan Mode Only&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;       &#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Age Limit Details&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Age: &lt;strong&gt;18 Years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age: &lt;strong&gt;25 Years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            &lt;span class=&#34;job-important&#34;&gt;Age relaxation as per rules of Bihar Police Advt No. : 01/2025.&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IOB Local Bank Officer 2025 Admit Card Donwnload</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bank/iob-local-bank-officer-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:51:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bank/iob-local-bank-officer-2025/</guid>
      <description>IOB ने लोकल बैंक अधिकारी (LBO) भर्ती 2025 के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की है। इच्छुक उम्मीदवार 12/05/2025 से 31/05/2025 तक ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। पात्रता, चयन प्रक्रिया, वेतन और अन्य विवरण जानें Yojna Portal पर।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB 2025: Apply for Various Posts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-various-post-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 09:36:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/dsssb-various-post-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB Various Post Recruitment 2025 has been announced for multiple vacancies in different departments under the Delhi Government, including posts like Malaria Inspector, Ayurvedic Pharmacist, PGT Teachers, Warder, Technician, and Laboratory Assistant. The minimum qualification ranges from Class 10th pass to Master’s degree, with specific experience and course requirements depending on the post. Eligible candidates from any state in India can apply online through dsssbonline.nic.in from 8th July 2025 to 7th August 2025. The job postings will be within Delhi only. The exam dates and admit cards will be released as per schedule, so applicants should read the official notification carefully and submit their applications before the last date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Home Guard Result Declared 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bihar-home-guard-01-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 16:37:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bihar-home-guard-01-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;Bihar Home Guard Recruitment 2025&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt; Bihar Home Guard Department&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification Bihar HG Advt No. : 01/2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-content&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;       &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application Begin: &lt;strong&gt;27/03/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Date for Apply Online: &lt;strong style=&#34;color:red;&#34;&gt;16/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay Exam Fee Last Date: &lt;strong&gt;16/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam Date: &lt;strong&gt;30/04/2025 to 05/06/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available: &lt;strong&gt;24/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Result Available: &lt;strong&gt;04/07/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General / OBC / EWS: &lt;strong&gt;200/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SC / ST: &lt;strong&gt;100/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All Category Female: &lt;strong&gt;100/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Pay the Examination Fee Through Debit Card, Credit Card, Net Banking or Pay Offline Fee Payment Through E Challan Mode Only&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;       &#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Age Limit as on 01/01/2025&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Age: &lt;strong&gt;19 Years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age: &lt;strong&gt;40 Years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Age Relaxation Extra as per Bihar Home Guard Advt No. 01/2025 Recruitment 2025.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            &lt;span class=&#34;job-important&#34;&gt;Age relaxation as per rules of Bihar HG Advt No. : 01/2025.&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPSC Assistant Public Prosecutor APO Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jh/jpsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 10:31:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jh/jpsc-apo-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>Jharkhand Public Service Commission (JPSC) has released the notification for 134 vacancies of Assistant Public Prosecutor (APO) for the year 2025. Candidates holding a Bachelor’s Degree in Law (LLB) from any recognized university in India are eligible to apply. The selection process will include written examinations and interviews. Interested candidates can apply online within the specified application dates. Category-wise vacancies are available for UR, BC-I, BC-II, EWS, SC, and ST candidates. For complete eligibility criteria and application details, refer to the official notification.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IBPS Hindi Officer Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-hindi-officer-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 09:58:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ibps-hindi-officer-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Institute of Banking Personnel Selection (IBPS) has released the notification for Hindi Officer (Rajbhasha Adhikari) Recruitment 2025 under Specialist Officer (SO) cadre. Eligible candidates with a Master’s degree in Hindi or English with the relevant language combination can apply online through the official IBPS website. The application process includes registration, form filling, and fee payment. Applicants are expected to have desirable translation experience in a banking or financial institution and proficiency in MS Word and Excel. The online registration, eligibility criteria, important dates, and complete details are available in the official notification. Interested candidates are advised to apply within the given timeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy Agniveer MR Musician Vacancy 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-navy-agniveer-mr-musician-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 09:37:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-navy-agniveer-mr-musician-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Indian Navy has invited online applications for the post of Agniveer MR Musician 2025. Candidates must have passed Class 10 (Matric) with at least 50% marks and possess musical ability as specified in the official notification. The physical fitness test includes a 1.6 km run, squats (uthak baithak), push-ups, and bent knee sit-ups with separate benchmarks for male and female candidates. Interested aspirants are advised to check the complete eligibility criteria before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Bihar Special School Teacher 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-bihar-special-school-teacher-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Jul 2025 12:03:39 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bpsc-bihar-special-school-teacher-2025/</guid>
      <description>BPSC Bihar Special School Teacher Recruitment 2025 में भारत के सभी राज्यों के योग्य उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं। यह भर्ती बिहार लोक सेवा आयोग (BPSC) द्वारा आयोजित की जा रही है, और आवेदन के लिए अभ्यर्थी भारतीय नागरिक होना चाहिए। हालांकि, आरक्षण का लाभ केवल बिहार के मूल निवासियों को ही मिलेगा। अन्य राज्यों से आने वाले उम्मीदवारों को अनारक्षित (सामान्य) श्रेणी में माना जाएगा, भले ही वे अपने राज्य में आरक्षित वर्ग (SC/ST/OBC) में आते हों। आवेदन के लिए संबंधित शैक्षणिक योग्यता के साथ-साथ विशेष शिक्षा में RCI (Rehabilitation Council of India) से मान्यता प्राप्त डिप्लोमा या डिग्री तथा छह माह का विशेष प्रशिक्षण अनिवार्य है। इस प्रकार, सभी योग्य उम्मीदवार, चाहे वे बिहार से हों या किसी अन्य राज्य से, इस भर्ती प्रक्रिया में भाग ले सकते हैं, बशर्ते वे सभी निर्धारित शर्तों को पूरा करते हों।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy B.Tech Officer Entry Scheme Jan 2026 Batch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-navy-b.tech-officer-entry-scheme-jan-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:50:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/indian-navy-b.tech-officer-entry-scheme-jan-2026/</guid>
      <description>Indian Navy has invited online applications for the 10+2 B.Tech Cadet Entry Scheme (January 2026 Batch). Eligible unmarried male and female candidates who have passed 12th with 70% marks in PCM and 50% in English can apply. Selected candidates will undergo a four-year B.Tech course at the Indian Naval Academy, Ezhimala, Kerala.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CG Vyapam Peon Bharti 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cg-vyapam-peon-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 11:12:43 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cg-vyapam-peon-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>Chhattisgarh Professional Examination Board (CG Vyapam) has released the MLV125 Recruitment 2025 notification for various Group D posts under the Department of Printing and Stationery, Raipur. A total of 19 vacancies are available for positions such as Darkroom Assistant, Pasting Boy, Auxiliary, Inkman/Inker, Junior Binder, Hamal, Sweeper, Watchman, Mortuary Attendant, and Helper. Candidates who have passed 5th or 8th class and possess relevant experience (as per the post) are eligible to apply. Both male and female candidates can submit their applications online through the official website of CG Vyapam. The online application process is open from 27 June 2025 to 25 July 2025. Applicants must ensure to review the official notification carefully and complete the form, including uploading documents and paying the fee online. The written exam is tentatively scheduled for 31 August 2025 at district centers like Raipur, Durg, and Bilaspur.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HVF Junior Technician Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hvf-junior-technician-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 20:47:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/hvf-junior-technician-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>Qualification: ITI (NAC/NTC/STC) in relevant trade or Class 10th with 2 years of experience (for some posts)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JSSC Secondary Teacher 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jssc-secondary-teacher-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 09:26:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jssc-secondary-teacher-2025/</guid>
      <description>JSSC Secondary Teacher Recruitment 2025 के लिए झारखंड राज्य के स्थायी निवासी एवं अन्य राज्य के पात्र अभ्यर्थी ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। झारखंड के निवासी आरक्षण का लाभ प्राप्त करेंगे, जबकि अन्य राज्य के उम्मीदवार अनारक्षित श्रेणी में माने जाएंगे। सभी अभ्यर्थियों को संबंधित विषय में स्नातकोत्तर डिग्री के साथ B.Ed., M.Ed., या समकक्ष योग्यताएं अनिवार्य हैं। तकनीकी विषयों के लिए MCA, M.Tech जैसी डिग्री के साथ B.Ed. आवश्यक है। आवेदन केवल JSSC की आधिकारिक वेबसाइट jssc.nic.in पर ऑनलाइन मोड से किया जा सकता है। स्थानीय भाषा की जानकारी और परीक्षा उत्तीर्ण करना आवश्यक होगा।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan High Court Class IV (Peon) Vacancy 2025 - Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-group-d-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 13:07:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-group-d-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan High Court Class IV (Peon) Recruitment 2025 के अंतर्गत राजस्थान उच्च न्यायालय द्वारा चपरासी (Class IV) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की गई है (विज्ञापन संख्या: रा.उ.न्या.जो./परीक्षा प्रकोष्ठ/अधीनस्थ न्यायालय/च.श्रे.क./2025/2349)। इस भर्ती के लिए अभ्यर्थी को किसी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10वीं (माध्यमिक) उत्तीर्ण होना आवश्यक है। साथ ही देवनागरी लिपि में हिंदी का व्यावहारिक ज्ञान और राजस्थान की संस्कृति की जानकारी भी अनिवार्य है। इस भर्ती में राजस्थान राज्य के अभ्यर्थी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, साथ ही अन्य राज्यों के उम्मीदवार भी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, लेकिन उन्हें अनारक्षित श्रेणी (Unreserved Category) में माना जाएगा और किसी प्रकार का आरक्षण प्राप्त नहीं होगा। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह ऑनलाइन होगी और विस्तृत जानकारी व आवेदन के लिए आधिकारिक वेबसाइट hcraj.nic.in पर विज़िट करें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WCDC Bihar Various Post 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-wcdc-various-post-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 18:35:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-wcdc-various-post-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Women and Child Development Corporation (WCDC), Bihar has released the WCDC Bihar Various Post Recruitment 2025 notification for a total of 77 contractual vacancies. These include posts like Central Administrator, Case Worker, Para Legal Personnel / Lawyer, Para Medical Personnel, Psycho-Social Counsellor, and Office Assistant (with computer knowledge). Except for the Office Assistant post, all other posts are reserved exclusively for female candidates. Only women who are residents of Bihar are eligible to apply (male/female both can apply for Office Assistant). The application process is completely online and will remain open from 26 June 2025 to 18 July 2025 (up to 6:00 PM). Interested candidates can visit the official website wdc.bihar.gov.in for eligibility, category-wise vacancy details, and to submit their application.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC GD Constable Recruitment 2024, Download Result/Answerkey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc/2024/ssc-gd-constable-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jun 2025 17:55:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc/2024/ssc-gd-constable-2024/</guid>
      <description>Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has relased General Duty GD Constable Notification 2024. Those candidates who are interested in this SSC GD Constable CAPFs, NIA, SSF and Rifleman (GD) in Assam Rifles Examination,2025 can apply online from Dates 05/09/2024 to 14/10/2024. Read the SSC GD Constable 2024 SSC GD Constable 2024 Exam City Details</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JPSC Project Manager 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jpsc-project-manager-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 09:03:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/jpsc-project-manager-2025/</guid>
      <description>JPSC Project Manager Online Form 2025 invites applications from eligible candidates for 30 posts under Jharkhand Public Service Commission. Applicants must have a Bachelor&amp;rsquo;s Degree in Engineering/Technology or in subjects like Economics, Statistics, Science, Commerce, Cost Accountancy, Sericulture, Food Technology, or Management from a recognized institution. This recruitment is primarily for residents of Jharkhand. The application process is completely online through the official website jpsc.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AIIMS Delhi Junior Resident July 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aiims-delhi-junior-resident-07-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 20:08:13 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/aiims-delhi-junior-resident-07-2025/</guid>
      <description>अखिल भारतीय आयुर्विज्ञान संस्थान (AIIMS), नई दिल्ली द्वारा जूनियर रेजिडेंट (Junior Resident – Non-Academic) पदों पर भर्ती के लिए जुलाई 2025 सत्र हेतु आवेदन आमंत्रित किए गए हैं। इस भर्ती में भारत के सभी राज्यों के MBBS या BDS डिग्रीधारी उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं, बशर्ते कि उन्होंने 30 जून 2025 तक अपनी इंटर्नशिप पूरी कर ली हो और संबंधित मेडिकल/डेंटल काउंसिल में पंजीकृत हों। आवेदन प्रक्रिया ऑनलाइन माध्यम से की जाएगी और चयन मेरिट आधारित होगा।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ISRO NRSC Recruitment 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-nrsc-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 16:55:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/isro-nrsc-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>ISRO NRSC भर्ती 2025 के तहत भारतीय अंतरिक्ष अनुसंधान संगठन के राष्ट्रीय सुदूर संवेदन केंद्र (NRSC) द्वारा विभिन्न पदों पर भर्तियां निकाली गई हैं। कुल 12 प्रकार के पदों के लिए 34 रिक्तियाँ घोषित की गई हैं। इसमें अनुसंधान वैज्ञानिक (Research Scientist), प्रोजेक्ट साइंटिस्ट-I एवं B, प्रोजेक्ट एसोसिएट-I और जूनियर रिसर्च फेलो (JRF) शामिल हैं। इन पदों के लिए न्यूनतम योग्यता ME/M.Tech, MSc/M.Sc Tech, BE/B.Tech, या B.Sc रखी गई है, जो रिमोट सेंसिंग, जीआईएस, जियोइन्फॉर्मेटिक्स, भूविज्ञान, कृषि, वन विज्ञान, जलवायु विज्ञान, पर्यावरण विज्ञान, भौतिकी, कंप्यूटर साइंस आदि संबंधित विषयों में होनी चाहिए। कुछ पदों के लिए डॉक्टरेट डिग्री (PhD) की भी आवश्यकता है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSCB Bihar State Co-Operative Bank Assistant 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bscb-bihar-state-co-operative-bank-assistant-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 20:11:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bscb-bihar-state-co-operative-bank-assistant-2025/</guid>
      <description>बिहार स्टेट को-ऑपरेटिव बैंक लिमिटेड (BSCB) द्वारा ऑफिस असिस्टेंट (मल्टीपर्पस) के कुल 257 पदों पर भर्ती हेतु अधिसूचना जारी की गई है। इस भर्ती के लिए उम्मीदवारों के पास किसी भी मान्यता प्राप्त विश्वविद्यालय से किसी भी स्ट्रीम में स्नातक डिग्री होनी चाहिए। आवेदन प्रक्रिया ऑनलाइन माध्यम से होगी, जिसकी प्रारंभिक और अंतिम तिथि जल्द ही आधिकारिक वेबसाइट पर जारी की जाएगी। इस भर्ती में बिहार राज्य के साथ-साथ अन्य राज्यों के पात्र अभ्यर्थी भी आवेदन कर सकते हैं, लेकिन आरक्षण का लाभ केवल बिहार के मूल निवासियों को ही मिलेगा। आयु सीमा, चयन प्रक्रिया और अन्य विवरण आधिकारिक अधिसूचना में स्पष्ट रूप से दिए जाएंगे।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CG Fire Department Recruitment 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cg-fire-department-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 15:47:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cg-fire-department-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>CG Fire Department Recruitment 2025 के अंतर्गत छत्तीसगढ़ अग्निशमन एवं आपातकालीन सेवा विभाग द्वारा फायरमैन, ड्राइवर एवं अन्य पदों पर भर्ती की जाएगी। इस भर्ती में केवल छत्तीसगढ़ राज्य के मूल निवासी ही आवेदन के पात्र होंगे। अभ्यर्थियों को न्यूनतम 10वीं पास होना अनिवार्य है, जबकि ड्राइवर पद के लिए वैध ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस भी आवश्यक होगा। आयु सीमा 01 जनवरी 2025 को आधार मानते हुए 18 से 35 वर्ष के बीच निर्धारित की गई है। चयन प्रक्रिया में शारीरिक परीक्षण, लिखित परीक्षा एवं दस्तावेज़ सत्यापन शामिल होंगे।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Statistics Officer, Assistant Geologist 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-statistics-officer-assistant-geologist-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 15:35:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-statistics-officer-assistant-geologist-2025/</guid>
      <description>उत्तर प्रदेश लोक सेवा आयोग (UPPSC) ने सांख्यिकी अधिकारी और सहायक भूवैज्ञानिक पदों के लिए भर्ती अधिसूचना 2025 जारी की है। कुल 6 पदों पर भर्ती की जाएगी, जिसमें 4 पद सांख्यिकी अधिकारी और 2 पद सहायक भूवैज्ञानिक के लिए आरक्षित हैं। इन पदों के लिए अभ्यर्थियों के पास संबंधित विषय में मास्टर डिग्री या डिप्लोमा होना अनिवार्य है, जिसमें न्यूनतम अंकों की शर्तें लागू हैं (जैसे सांख्यिकी अधिकारी के लिए 55% अंक, और भूविज्ञान में 50%)। आवेदन प्रक्रिया पूरी तरह से ऑनलाइन होगी और भारत के सभी राज्यों के पात्र उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं, हालांकि आरक्षण एवं आयु में छूट का लाभ केवल उत्तर प्रदेश के मूल निवासियों को ही मिलेगा। अधिक जानकारी के लिए अभ्यर्थियों को आधिकारिक अधिसूचना अवश्य पढ़नी चाहिए।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan HC Driver Recruitment 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-driver-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 13:20:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/rajasthan-high-court-driver-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan High Court has officially released the notification for Driver Recruitment 2025, inviting applications for a total of 58 vacancies. Interested and eligible candidates can apply online through the official website hcraj.nic.in from 18 June to 7 July 2025. This recruitment drive offers a great opportunity for candidates seeking government jobs in the driving sector under the Rajasthan judiciary. Applicants are advised to carefully read the eligibility criteria, application process, and important dates mentioned in the official notification before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Navy PC Officer Recruitment Cadet Scheme Jan 2026 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/force/navy-cadet-entry-scheme-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jun 2025 19:00:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/force/navy-cadet-entry-scheme-2025/</guid>
      <description>उम्मीदवारों को किसी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 (फिजिक्स, केमिस्ट्री, मैथ्स) में न्यूनतम 70% अंक और अंग्रेज़ी में कम से कम 50% अंक (10वीं या 12वीं में) होना अनिवार्य है। आवेदन वही अभ्यर्थी कर सकते हैं जिन्होंने JEE (Main) 2025 की परीक्षा दी है और जिनका नाम NTA द्वारा जारी All India Common Rank List (CRL) 2025 में शामिल है। चयन SSB कॉल अप के माध्यम से JEE रैंक के आधार पर किया जाएगा।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CG Abkari Aarakshak Bharti 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cg-abkari-aarakshak-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jun 2025 09:56:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/cg-abkari-aarakshak-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>CG Abkari Aarakshak Bharti 2025 invites applications for 200 Excise Constable posts. Eligible candidates who have passed 12th can apply online from June 4 to June 27, 2025. The written exam will be held on July 27, 2025. Applicants from all Indian states can apply, but only Chhattisgarh residents will receive reservation and age relaxation benefits. The recruitment will be conducted by CG Vyapam, and the selection process includes a written test and physical eligibility test.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SCI Programmer Vacancy 2025 Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-court-assistant-junior-senior-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jun 2025 11:56:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/sci-court-assistant-junior-senior-2025/</guid>
      <description>Shipping Corporation of India (SCI) द्वारा Senior Court Assistant-cum-Senior Programmer और Junior Court Assistant-cum-Junior Programmer पदों पर भर्ती हेतु अधिसूचना जारी की गई है। कुल 26 पद हैं। सीनियर पद के लिए बी.टेक/एमसीए + 6 साल का अनुभव और जूनियर पद के लिए बी.टेक/बीसीए जैसी योग्यता मांगी गई है। चयनित अभ्यर्थियों को Level 6 और Level 8 के अनुसार वेतनमान मिलेगा। इच्छुक उम्मीदवार SCI की वेबसाइट पर जाकर ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Field Assistant 2025 Apply Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/bihar/field-assistant-vacancy-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 19:33:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/bihar/field-assistant-vacancy-2025/</guid>
      <description>फील्ड असिस्टेंट (कृषि विभाग) भर्ती 2025</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar PRD Technical Assistant Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-zp-technical-assistant-june25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:19:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar-zp-technical-assistant-june25/</guid>
      <description>Only Bihar residents may be eligible for the Zila Parishad Technical Assistant 2025 post. Check the official notification for domicile rules.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC Staff Nurse (Unani) Online Application Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-staff-nurse-unani-june25/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Jun 2025 13:14:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/uppsc-staff-nurse-unani-june25/</guid>
      <description>उत्तर प्रदेश लोक सेवा आयोग (UPPSC) द्वारा स्टाफ नर्स यूनानी भर्ती 2025 के लिए ऑनलाइन आवेदन आमंत्रित किए गए हैं। इस भर्ती में योग्य पुरुष एवं महिला अभ्यर्थी यूनानी नर्सिंग से संबंधित योग्यता के आधार पर आवेदन कर सकते हैं। उत्तर प्रदेश के निवासी अभ्यर्थियों को आरक्षण का लाभ मिलेगा, जबकि अन्य राज्य के उम्मीदवार अनारक्षित श्रेणी में आवेदन कर सकते हैं। इच्छुक अभ्यर्थी निर्धारित तिथि से पहले आधिकारिक वेबसाइट के माध्यम से ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apply for UPSC ORA Vacancy 2025 – Operation Officer &amp; Other Posts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-ora-06-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jun 2025 19:35:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/upsc-ora-06-2025/</guid>
      <description>संघ लोक सेवा आयोग (UPSC) ने ORA भर्ती 2025 के तहत ऑपरेशन ऑफिसर और अन्य विभिन्न पदों के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की है। आवेदन प्रक्रिया जून 2025 से शुरू होने की संभावना है और अंतिम तिथि जुलाई 2025 रहेगी। योग्य उम्मीदवार आधिकारिक वेबसाइट upsc.gov.in पर ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। भर्ती से संबंधित योग्यता, आयु सीमा और अन्य विवरण के लिए आधिकारिक नोटिफिकेशन जरूर पढ़ें।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Laboratory Assistant Recruitment 2025 – Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/bssc-laboratory-asst-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 17:09:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/bssc-laboratory-asst-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar BSSC 10+2 Laboratory Assistant Recruitment 2025 के अंतर्गत बिहार कर्मचारी चयन आयोग (BSSC) ने कुल 143 लैबोरेटरी असिस्टेंट पदों के लिए भर्ती अधिसूचना जारी की है। इस भर्ती के लिए वे सभी उम्मीदवार आवेदन कर सकते हैं जिन्होंने किसी मान्यता प्राप्त बोर्ड से 10+2 (इंटरमीडिएट) विज्ञान संकाय से उत्तीर्ण किया हो। आवेदन प्रक्रिया 15 मई 2025 से शुरू हो चुकी है और अंतिम तिथि 14 जून 2025 निर्धारित की गई है। इस पद के लिए न्यूनतम आयु सीमा 18 वर्ष है और अधिकतम आयु सीमा श्रेणी के अनुसार 37 से 42 वर्ष तक निर्धारित की गई है। सामान्य, ओबीसी और अन्य राज्य के उम्मीदवारों के लिए आवेदन शुल्क ₹540 है, जबकि बिहार के SC, ST, महिला और दिव्यांग अभ्यर्थियों के लिए ₹135 है। चयन प्रक्रिया में प्रारंभिक परीक्षा (यदि आवेदन संख्या 40,000 से अधिक हो), मुख्य परीक्षा और दस्तावेज़ सत्यापन शामिल होंगे। चयनित उम्मीदवारों को ₹25,500 से ₹81,100 (पे लेवल 4) के वेतनमान पर नियुक्त किया जाएगा। इच्छुक अभ्यर्थी onlinebssc.com वेबसाइट के माध्यम से ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar SHS Medical Officer Recruitment 2025 – Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/shs-medical-officer-bhiar-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 May 2025 13:09:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/shs-medical-officer-bhiar-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;style&gt;&#xA;        th, td {&#xA;            border: 1px solid #34495e;&#xA;            padding: 12px;&#xA;            text-align: left;&#xA;            vertical-align: top;&#xA;        }&#xA;        &#xA;        th {&#xA;            background-color: #3498db;&#xA;            color: white;&#xA;            font-weight: bold;&#xA;            text-align: center;&#xA;        }&#xA;    .post-name {&#xA;            background-color: #ecf0f1;&#xA;            font-weight: bold;&#xA;            text-align: center;&#xA;            width: 25%;&#xA;        }&#xA;        &#xA;        .total {&#xA;            background-color: #e8f5e8;&#xA;            font-weight: bold;&#xA;            text-align: center;&#xA;            width: 15%;&#xA;            font-size: 16px;&#xA;        }&#xA;        &#xA;        .eligibility1 {&#xA;            width: 60%;&#xA;            line-height: 1.6;&#xA;        }&#xA;        &#xA;        .eligibility1 ul {&#xA;            margin: 0;&#xA;            padding-left: 20px;&#xA;        }&#xA;        &#xA;        .eligibility1 li {&#xA;            margin-bottom: 8px;&#xA;        }&#xA;        &#xA;        .highlight {&#xA;            background-color: #fff3cd;&#xA;            padding: 2px 4px;&#xA;            border-radius: 3px;&#xA;        }&#xA;&lt;/style&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;yp-table-wrapper&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;h1&gt;बिहार एसएचएस चिकित्सा अधिकारी पद विवरण&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;        &#xA;        &lt;table&gt;&#xA;            &lt;thead&gt;&#xA;                &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;th&gt;पद का नाम&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;th&gt;कुल संख्या&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;th&gt;बिहार एसएचएस चिकित्सा अधिकारी पात्रता&lt;/th&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/thead&gt;&#xA;            &lt;tbody&gt;&#xA;                &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;post-name&#34;&gt;चिकित्सा अधिकारी&lt;br&gt;आयुर्वेद&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;total&#34;&gt;1411&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;eligibility1&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;BAMS डिग्री&lt;/span&gt; भारत की किसी मान्यता प्राप्त संस्था से&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;इंटर्नशिप प्रशिक्षण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;बिहार राज्य आयुर्वेद और यूनानी चिकित्सा परिषद में पंजीकरण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;                &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;post-name&#34;&gt;चिकित्सा अधिकारी&lt;br&gt;होम्योपैथिक&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;total&#34;&gt;706&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;eligibility1&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;BHMS डिग्री&lt;/span&gt; भारत की किसी मान्यता प्राप्त संस्था से&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;इंटर्नशिप प्रशिक्षण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;बिहार राज्य आयुर्वेद और यूनानी चिकित्सा परिषद में पंजीकरण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;                &lt;tr&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;post-name&#34;&gt;चिकित्सा अधिकारी&lt;br&gt;यूनानी&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;total&#34;&gt;502&lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;td class=&#34;eligibility1&#34;&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;ul&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;BUMS डिग्री&lt;/span&gt; भारत की किसी मान्यता प्राप्त संस्था से&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;इंटर्नशिप प्रशिक्षण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                            &lt;li&gt;बिहार राज्य आयुर्वेद और यूनानी चिकित्सा परिषद में पंजीकरण&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;                        &lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;                    &lt;/td&gt;&#xA;                &lt;/tr&gt;&#xA;            &lt;/tbody&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/table&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB ALP Bharti 2025 – Railway Assistant Loco Pilot Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/railway/assistant-loco-pilot-bharti-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 08:48:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/railway/assistant-loco-pilot-bharti-2025/</guid>
      <description>रेलवे सहायक लोको पायलट भर्ती 2025 – अधिसूचना एवं आवेदन फॉर्म</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ASRB NET, ARS, SMS, STO Recruitment 2025 – Apply Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/asrb-net-ars-sms-sto-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 May 2025 16:00:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/asrb-net-ars-sms-sto-2025/</guid>
      <description>ASRB ने NET, ARS, SMS और STO पदों के लिए 582 रिक्तियों की घोषणा की है। आवेदन प्रक्रिया 22 अप्रैल से शुरू होकर 21 मई 2025 तक चलेगी। पात्र उम्मीदवार ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। परीक्षा सितंबर और दिसंबर 2025 में आयोजित की जाएगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR NBRI Lucknow Jobs 2025 – Apply for Various Vacancies</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-nbri-recruitment-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 16:46:48 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/csir-nbri-recruitment-2025/</guid>
      <description>CSIR NBRI लखनऊ ने 2025 में टेक्निकल असिस्टेंट, टेक्नीशियन और JSA पदों पर भर्ती के लिए अधिसूचना जारी की है। आवेदन की अंतिम तिथि 02 जून 2025 है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>India Post GDS Online Form 2025 (2st List)</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/2025/05/india-post-gds-jan25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 08:27:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/2025/05/india-post-gds-jan25/</guid>
      <description>India Post Gramin Dak Sevaks GDS Schedule I January Recruitment 2025 Apply Online for 21413 Post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BSSC Sub and Block Statistical Officer Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bssc-statistical-01-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 10:59:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bssc-statistical-01-2025/</guid>
      <description>&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;Bihar Sub Statistical Officer/Block Statistical Officer Recruitment 2025&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Bihar Staff Selection Commission BSSC&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification BSSC Advt No. : 01/2025&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-content&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;       &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application Begin: &lt;strong&gt;01/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay Exam Fee Last Date: &lt;strong style=&#34;color:rgb(250, 18, 10);&#34;&gt;19/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Date for Apply Online: &lt;strong&gt;19/04/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam Date: &lt;strong&gt;As per Schedule&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General / OBC / EWS: &lt;strong&gt;540/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SC / ST / PH: &lt;strong&gt;135/-&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Pay the Exam Fee Through Debit Card / Credit Card / Net Banking Mode Only.&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;       &#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p style=&#34;color:green;&#34;&gt;Age Limit as on 01/08/2024&lt;p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Age: &lt;strong&gt;21 Years.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age: &lt;strong&gt;37 Years. for Male&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age: &lt;strong&gt;40 Years. for Female&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            &lt;span class=&#34;job-important&#34;&gt;Age relaxation as per rules of BSSC Advt No. : 01/2025.&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CSIR CDRI Junior Secretariat Assistant, Steno Online Form 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/2025/05/csir-cdri-jsa-steno-feb25/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 18:19:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/2025/05/csir-cdri-jsa-steno-feb25/</guid>
      <description>CSIR Central Drug Research Institute CDRI Lucknow Junior Secretariat Assistant JSA and Junior Stenographer Recruitment 2025 Apply Online for 11 Post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC 70th Exam 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bpsc-70th-exam-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2025 17:28:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bpsc-70th-exam-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;\css\job-posts.css&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released the notification for the recruitment of 1957 Post 70th Combined Competitive Examination and other examinations 2024. Those Candidates Are Interested to the Following Vacancy Can Download Result. See the advertisement for information related to age limit, syllabus, Department wise post, selection procedure, pay scale in BPSC Pre 70th Recruitment 2024.  PlayMute Fullscreen   Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) BPSC 70th Combined Pre Exam CCE / CDPO Recruitment 2024 BPSC 70 Exam 2024 : Short Details of Notification WWW.SARKARIRESULT.COM Important Dates Application Begin : 28/09/2024 Last Date for Apply Online : 04/11/2024 Pay Exam Fee Last Date : 04/11/2024 Correction Date : 19/10/2024 to 04/11/2024 Exam Date : 13/12/2024 Admit Card Available : 06/12/2024 Answer Key Available : 09/01/2025 Final Answer Key Available : 17/01/2025 Pre Result Available : 23/01/2025 Application Fee General / OBC/ Other State : 600/- SC / ST / PH : 150/- Female Candidate (Bihar Dom.) : 150/- Pay the Exam Fee Through Online / Offline Fee Mode Only BPSC 70 Exam Notification 2024 : Age Limit as on 01/08/2024 Minimum Age : 20,21 OR 22 Years (Post Wise) Maximum Age : 37 Male Maximum Age : 40 Female Age Relaxation Extra as per BPSC 70 Pre Examination Rules. BPSC 70th Recruitment 2024 : Vacancy Details Total : 1957 Post Post Name  Total Post  BPSC 70th Exam Eligibility  Bihar BPSC Various Post Under 70th Pre 2024  1945  Bachelor Degree in Any Stream in Any Recognized University in India. For Post Wise Eligibility Details Read the Notification Child Development Project Officer  12  Bachelor Degree with Home Science, Psychology, Social Science &amp; Labor and Social Welfare. More Eligibility Details Read the Notification. BPSC 70 Notification 2024 : Category Wise Vacancy Details General (UR)  EWS  E BC  BC  BC Female  SC  ST  Total  1082  246  427  315  59  403  22  1957  BPSC 70 Notification 2024 : Post Wise Vacancy Details Post / Service Name  UR  EWS  EBC  BC  BC Female  SC  ST  Total  Sub-Divisional Officer/Senior Deputy Collector  80  20  36  24  06  32  02  200  Deputy Superintendent of Police  52  13  24  12  06  28  01  136  District Commandant Bihar Home Guards Service  05  01  01  02  01  02  0  12  Jail Superintendent  01  0  02  0  0  0  0  03  Assistant Commissioner of State Taxes  65  16  26  25  04  31  01  168  Assistant Registrar / Joint Assistant Registrar, Prohibition  09  01  0  01  0  0  0  11  Assistant Election Officer  03  01  0  04  0  04  0  12  Bihar  Education Service  12  03  13  08  01  13  0  50  Assistant Director (Social Security Branch)  05  01  03  01  0  02  0  12  Assistant Director (Disability Empowerment Branch)  04  01  0  02  0  02  0  09  Assistant Director (Child Protection Service)  07  01  0  0  01  0  0  09  District Minority Welfare Officer  02  01  0  02  01  0  0  06  Cane Officer, Sugarcane Industry Department  01  0  0  0  0  0  0  01  Planning Officer / District Planning Officer  05  01  04  01  0  03  0  14  Assistant Planning Officer / Assistant Director  14  02  04  03  0  0  0  23  Bihar Transport Service  02  0  01  0  0  01  0  04  Municipal Executive Officer  32  06  08  01  09  01  59  Rural Development Officer  161  39  72  47  13  56  05  393  Revenue Officer and equivalent  99  24  53  56  05  47  03  287  Labour Enforcement Officer  26  07  08  11  03  12  0  67  Block Panchayat Raj Officer  45  08  10  04  0  16  0  83  Supply Inspector  89  22  39  29  13  37  04  233  Block SC and ST Welfare Officer  71  13  13  14  02  10  02  125  Block Minority Welfare Officer  15  03  05  0  01  03  01  28  Child Development Project Officer  10  01  0  01  0  0  0  12  How to Fill Bihar BPSC 70 Pre Exam Online Form 2024 Bihar Public Service Commission BPSC Are Issued 70th Combined (Preliminary) Competitive Examination 2024. Notification and Invited Online Application Form for the BPSC 70 Recruitment 2024 Candidate Can Apply Online for 28/09/2024 to 04/11/2024. Candidate Read the Notification Before Apply the BPSC Latest Recruitment 2024 Application Form in  Sarkari Result Recruitment Latest Job Section. Kindly Check and Collect the All Document - Hand Writing, Eligibility, ID Proof, Address Details, Basic Details. Kindly Ready Scan Document Related to Recruitment Form - Photo, Sign, ID, Thumb, Proof, Etc. Before Submit the Application Form Must Check the Preview and All Column Carefully. If Candidate Required to Paying the Application Fee Must Submit. If You have Not the Required Application Fees Your Form is Not Completed. Take A Print Out of Final Submitted Form. Interested Candidates Can Read the Full Notification Before Apply Online. Download Mobile Apps for the Latest Updates Android Apps Apple IOS Apps Some Useful Important Links Download Pre Result List 1 | List 2 | List 3 Download OMR Sheet Click Here Download OMR Sheet Notice Click Here Download GS Final Answer Key Exam 13/12/2024 | Exam 04/01/2025 Download GS Answer Key Exam 13/12/2024 | Exam 04/01/2025 Download Answer Key Notice Click Here Download Admit Card Click Here How to Download Admit Card (Video Hindi) Click Here Download Admit Card Notice Click Here Apply Online Click Here How to One Time Registration OTR (Video Hindi) Click Here Download Pre Exam Notice Click Here Download Date Extended &amp; Correction Notice Click Here Download Notification Click Here Document and Details Required for BPSC 70th Form Filling Click Here Download Syllabus (Pre / Mains) Click Here Signature Resizer, PDF Compress, Age Calculator and More Tools Sarkari Result Tools Join Sarkari Result Channel Telegram | WhatsApp Official Website BPSC Official Website  Sarkari Result Bihar BPSC 70th Pre Recruitment 2024  , Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC), BPSC 70 Exam 2024 :&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;BPSC 70th Combined Pre Exam CCE / CDPO Recruitment 2024&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;BPSC 70th Combined Pre Exam CCE / CDPO Recruitment 2024&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification BPSC 70 Exam 2024 :&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bpsc School Teacher Tre3 Feb24</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bpsc-school-teacher-tre3-feb24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jan 2025 17:30:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bpsc-school-teacher-tre3-feb24/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;\css\job-posts.css&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) School Teacher TRE 3.0 Recruitment 2024. Those candidates who are interested in this BPSC School Teacher Primary, Middle, Secondary, TGT, PGT ( for Class 1 to 5, Class 6 to 8, Class 9 to 10, Class 11 to 12 and Special School Teacher for Class 9 to 10 under  Education Department and (II) for Class 1 to 5, Class 6 to 10 and Class 11 to 12 under SC &amp; ST Welfare Dept., , Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC), Bihar Teacher Bharti TRE 3 Advt No. 22/2024:&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;BPSC Bihar School Teacher TRE 3.0 Recruitment 2024&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;BPSC Bihar School Teacher TRE 3.0 Recruitment 2024&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification Bihar Teacher Bharti TRE 3 Advt No. 22/2024:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Gram Ktchahary Sachiv Jan25</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bihar-gram-ktchahary-sachiv-jan25/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 10:24:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bihar-gram-ktchahary-sachiv-jan25/</guid>
      <description>bihar jobs,Gram Katchahary Sachiv (Samvida)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DDA Various Post 02 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/delhi/2025/06/dda-various-post-02-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 15:45:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/delhi/2025/06/dda-various-post-02-2023/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;\css\job-posts.css&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;&#x9;Delhi Development Authority (DDA) Has released the notification of Various Post (Junior Engineer, JSA, Naib Tehsildar, Patwari and Other Post Advt No 02/2023. Any candidate who is interested in the recruitment of Delhi DDA and fulfills the eligibility can Download the Stage II Exam Admit Card., Delhi Development Authority (DDA), DDA Advt No. : 02/2023/Rectt. Cell/Pers./DDA&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;DDA Delhi Various Post Recruitment 2023&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;DDA Delhi Various Post Recruitment 2023&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Delhi Development Authority (DDA)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification DDA Advt No. : 02/2023/Rectt. Cell/Pers./DDA&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Vidhan 02 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bihar-vidhan-02-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 14:56:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bihar/2025/05/bihar-vidhan-02-2024/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Legislative Council Vidhan Parishad Sachivalaya Assistant Branch Officer, DEO and Stenographer Recruitment 2024 Exam Result for 26 Post</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC CGL 2024 Tier II Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc/2024/ssc-cgl-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 10:28:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/ssc/2024/ssc-cgl-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;\css\job-posts.css&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has relased Combined Graduate Level CGL Examination 2024 Notification. Those candidates who are interested in this SSC Combined Graduate Level CGL Recruitment 2024 can Download Tier I Marks, Staff Selection Commission (SSC), SSC CGL 2024 Exam&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;SSC Combined Graduate Level CGL Recruitment 2024&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;SSC Combined Graduate Level CGL Recruitment 2024&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;Staff Selection Commission (SSC)&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification SSC CGL 2024 Exam&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-content&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;       &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application Begin : 24/06/2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Date for Apply Online : 27/07/2024 upto 11 PM Only&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Online Fee Payment Last Date :  28/07/2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Correction Date : 10-11 August 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam Date Tier I :  09-26 September 2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available : Before Exam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tier I Answer Key Released : 03/10/2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tier I Result Available : 05/12/2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tier I Marks Available : 16/12/2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Tier II Exam Date : 18-20 January 2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam City Available : 09/01/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available : 14/01/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General / OBC / EWS: 100/-&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SC / ST / PH : 0/- (Nil)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;All Category Female : 0/- (Exempted)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Correction Fee First Time : 200/-&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Correction Fee Second Time : 500/-&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay the Examination Fee Through Debit Card, Credit Card, Net Banking, UPI Fee Mode Only.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;       &#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Age Limit as on 01/08/2024&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Age : 18 Years.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age : 27-32 Years (Post Wise)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            &lt;span class=&#34;job-important&#34;&gt;Age relaxation as per rules of SSC CGL 2024 Exam.&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CBSE Board Superintendent &amp; Junior Assistant Recruitment 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/2025/05/cbse-jr-assistant-jan25/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 10:56:28 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/2025/05/cbse-jr-assistant-jan25/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt;&#xA;&lt;html lang=&#34;en&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;head&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta charset=&#34;UTF-8&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;meta name=&#34;viewport&#34; content=&#34;width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;link rel=&#34;stylesheet&#34; href=&#34;\css\job-posts.css&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;meta name=&#34;description&#34; content=&#34;, CBSE Board Superintendent &amp; Junior Assistant Recruitment 2025, CBSE Advt No. : CBSE/Rectt.Cell/14/(87)/SA/2024:&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;title&gt;CBSE Board Superintendent &amp; Junior Assistant Recruitment 2025&lt;/title&gt;&#xA;&lt;/head&gt;&#xA;&lt;body&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div class=&#34;job-container&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-header&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h1 class=&#34;job-main-title&#34;&gt;Central Board of Secondary Education (CBSE)&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;      &lt;h2 class=&#34;job-sub-title&#34;&gt;CBSE Board Superintendent &amp; Junior Assistant Recruitment 2025&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;      &lt;p class=&#34;notification&#34;&gt;Short Details of Notification CBSE Advt No. : CBSE/Rectt.Cell/14/(87)/SA/2024:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;    &lt;div class=&#34;job-content&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;       &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Important Dates&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Application Begin : &lt;strong&gt; 01/01/2025 &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Last Date : &lt;b&gt; 31/01/2025 &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay Exam Fee Last Date : &lt;strong&gt; 31/01/2025&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exam Date : As per Schedule&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Admit Card Available : Before Exam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Application Fee&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;General UR / OBC / EWS : &lt;strong&gt;800/-&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SC / ST / PH / Female :&lt;strong&gt; 0/-&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pay the Exam Fee , Debit Card, Credit Card, Net Banking, UPI Mode Only.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;        &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;       &#xA;      &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;      &lt;div class=&#34;job-section&#34;&gt;&#xA;        &lt;div class=&#34;job-card&#34;&gt;&#xA;          &lt;h3&gt;Eligibility&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;          &lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Age Limit as on 31/01/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimum Age : 18 Years&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age : 30 Years for Superintendent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maximum Age : 27 Years for Junior Assistant&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;          &lt;p&gt;&#xA;            &lt;span class=&#34;job-important&#34;&gt;Age relaxation as per rules of CBSE Advt No. : CBSE/Rectt.Cell/14/(87)/SA/2024:.&lt;/span&gt;&#xA;          &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SBI Probationary Officers PO Recruitment 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/2025/05/sbi-po-dec24/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 10:09:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/jobs/bank/2025/05/sbi-po-dec24/</guid>
      <description>SBI has relased Probationary Officers PO Recruitment 2024. Those candidates Are Interested to the Following SBI PO Recruitment 2024</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
