<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Otrs on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Otrs on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:13:18 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RPSC OTR Registration 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/rj/rpsc-otr-one-time-registration-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:13:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/rj/rpsc-otr-one-time-registration-online/</guid>
      <description>RPSC OTR (One Time Registration) is a permanent registration system started by the Rajasthan Public Service Commission, where candidates need to register only once using their SSO ID. After completing the OTR, applicants can easily apply for any RPSC recruitment without filling in their details repeatedly. This process saves time and ensures accuracy in applications, while also allowing candidates to update their profile whenever required.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC One-Time Registration Guide 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/bihar/bpsc-otr-one-time-registration-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:41:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/bihar/bpsc-otr-one-time-registration-online/</guid>
      <description>BPSC (Bihar Public Service Commission) requires a one-time registration. Once registered, you can use the same login ID and password to apply for all BPSC exams. This guide provides a step-by-step registration process, required documents, eligibility criteria, and the latest exam updates to help you apply online easily.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB OTR One-Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/delhi/dsssb-otr-one-time-registration-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 20:24:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/delhi/dsssb-otr-one-time-registration-online/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB One-Time Registration (OARS) allows candidates to create a unique login to apply for multiple posts under the Delhi Subordinate Services Selection Board. The registration process requires personal, academic, and ID details, along with uploading photograph and signature. Once registered, candidates can easily apply for DSSSB vacancies online, check application status, and retrieve login credentials if needed.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SSC OTR 2025 – One Time Registration</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/ssc-otr-online-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 19:38:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/ssc-otr-online-form/</guid>
      <description>SSC OTR 2025 allows candidates to create a single profile for multiple SSC exams. Register online once, fill personal and educational details, upload documents, and easily apply for upcoming SSC exams. Check eligibility, important dates, fees, and registration steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police One Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/up-police-otr-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:26:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/up-police-otr-online/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has launched the One Time Registration (OTR) 2025 process for all aspiring candidates. This OTR is mandatory for those who wish to apply for any upcoming UP Police recruitment exams. By completing the OTR once, candidates will not need to repeatedly enter their details for each application. This system ensures a faster, more transparent, and convenient application process. Interested candidates can register online at uppbpb.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC OTR One Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/uppsc-otr-portal-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:54:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/otr/uppsc-otr-portal-form/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC OTR (One Time Registration) is an online registration system launched by the Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission to simplify the application process for various state-level exams. Candidates need to register only once by providing their personal, educational, and ID details. Once registered, they can apply for future UPPSC recruitments without filling in their details again. This system saves time, reduces errors, and ensures accuracy in applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NSP One Time Registration (OTR) 2025</title>
      <link>https://www.yojnaportal.com/student/nsp-otr-scholarship-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jul 2025 13:49:19 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://www.yojnaportal.com/student/nsp-otr-scholarship-form/</guid>
      <description>NSP OTR (One Time Registration) is a new mandatory process introduced on the National Scholarship Portal (NSP) from the academic year 2025 onwards. All students must create an OTR ID using their Aadhaar-linked mobile number before applying for any scholarship. This ensures a unique and secure identity for every applicant, prevents duplication, and streamlines the scholarship process.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
