<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Baner Poster Update /edit on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/edit-baner/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Baner Poster Update /edit on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:32:32 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/edit-baner/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Animal Husbandry ADDET 2025 Result Declared</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/mpesb-animal-husbandry-addet-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 18:32:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/mpesb-animal-husbandry-addet-2025/</guid>
      <description>Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board (MPESB) has released the ADDET 2025 Result for the Animal Husbandry and Dairy Technology Diploma Entrance Test. Candidates who appeared in the exam can now check their scores, download the result PDF, and view the merit list and cutoff details on the official MPESB website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Territorial Army Officer Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/territorial-army-officer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 16:31:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/territorial-army-officer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Territorial Army has released the Officer Admit Card 2025 on its official website. Registered candidates can download their admit card using their login credentials. The written examination will be conducted as per the scheduled date mentioned on the admit card. It is mandatory to carry the admit card and a valid photo ID to the exam center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Staff Nurse Exam Dates Announced</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/btsc-staff-nurse-exam-dates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:45:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/btsc-staff-nurse-exam-dates/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has officially announced the Staff Nurse Computer-Based Test (CBT) schedule under Advt. No. 23/2025. The exam will be conducted on 30 July, 31 July, 1 August, and 3 August 2025 across multiple shifts. Candidates who have applied for over 11,000 Staff Nurse posts should prepare accordingly. The admit card will be released soon on the official website btsc.bihar.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA UGC NET June 2025 Result Date Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/ugc-net-june-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jul 2025 11:03:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/ugc-net-june-2025/</guid>
      <description>NTA ने UGC NET June 2025 परीक्षा के लिए एडमिट कार्ड जारी कर दिए हैं। अभ्यर्थी अपना हॉल टिकट आधिकारिक वेबसाइट ugcnet.nta.nic.in से एप्लिकेशन नंबर और जन्म तिथि की मदद से डाउनलोड कर सकते हैं। परीक्षा निर्धारित तिथि पर देशभर में आयोजित की जाएगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BPSC Bihar Assistant Engineer 2025 Admit Card</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bpsc-bihar-assistant-engineer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jul 2025 18:05:11 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bpsc-bihar-assistant-engineer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar Public Service Commission (BPSC) has released the Admit Card for the Assistant Engineer (AE) Recruitment 2025 under Advertisement Nos. 29/2025, 30/2025, and 31/2025. The exam is scheduled to be held from 17th to 19th July 2025, and candidates can download their admit cards from 14th July 2025 by visiting the official website bpsc.bihar.gov.in. The admit card is a mandatory document to appear in the exam, and it contains key details like exam date, time, venue, and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HPSC Assistant Professor Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/hpsc-assistant-professor-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jul 2025 19:03:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/hpsc-assistant-professor-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Haryana Public Service Commission (HPSC) has declared the final result for Assistant Professor Recruitment 2025 on July 11. A total of 2,424 vacancies across multiple subjects have been filled. Candidates can now check their roll numbers in the final selection list PDF available on the official website hpsc.gov.in. The recruitment included a written test and document verification process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Assistant Loco Pilot ALP CBAT Admitcard 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-alp-cbat-exam-city-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 13:22:02 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-alp-cbat-exam-city-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the Exam City Intimation Slip for the Assistant Loco Pilot (ALP) CBAT 2025. Candidates can now check their allotted exam city and centre details through the official RRB regional websites. This information helps applicants plan their travel and exam preparations accordingly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Central Bank ZBO Exam Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/cbi-zbo-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 17:52:26 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/cbi-zbo-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>Central Bank of India has officially released the Zone Based Officer (ZBO) Result 2025. Candidates who appeared for the exam can now check their results, download the merit list PDF, and verify their selection status. The result includes zone-wise shortlisted candidates based on written exam and interview performance. Visit the official website or use the direct link provided here to check your result, cutoff marks, and other important updates</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan HC Civil Judge Pre Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rajasthan-hc-civil-judge-pre-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Jul 2025 09:11:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rajasthan-hc-civil-judge-pre-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan High Court has released the Admit Card for Civil Judge Prelims Exam 2025. Candidates can now download their hall ticket from the official website. The exam aims to recruit Civil Judges across Rajasthan. Admit card includes exam date, time, and venue details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Ladli Bahna 26th Installment Date 2025: Payment Status, List &amp; Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/ladli-behna-yojna-26th-kist/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Jul 2025 10:43:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/ladli-behna-yojna-26th-kist/</guid>
      <description> लाड़ली बहना योजना संबंधित महत्तपूर्ण लिंक Important Links Action Ladi Bahna Yojna Status Check Status Ladi Bahna Yojna Official Check Official Follow For Latest Update WhatsApp | Telegram Official Website CM LBY Official Website </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Research Assistant Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-research-assistant-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 20:19:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-research-assistant-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released the Research Assistant Admit Card 2025 on its official website. Candidates who have applied for the examination can now download their admit card by visiting rpsc.rajasthan.gov.in. The admit card contains important details such as exam date, time, center, and instructions. Candidates must carry a valid ID proof along with the admit card to the exam center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB NTPC 10&#43;2 Under Graduate Level Exam Date/ Application Status 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-ntpc-10&#43;2-under-graduate-level-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 19:46:55 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-ntpc-10&#43;2-under-graduate-level-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has officially released the exam dates for the NTPC 10+2 (Under Graduate) level posts. The Computer Based Test (CBT 1) will be conducted from 7 August to 8 September 2025. Candidates who have applied for the RRB NTPC UG posts can check the detailed exam schedule on the official RRB websites. This exam is conducted for 12th-pass candidates applying for various undergraduate-level posts in Indian Railways.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JHC Jharkhand High Court Assistant Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/jhc-assistant-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jul 2025 11:39:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/jhc-assistant-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Jharkhand High Court (JHC) has officially released the Assistant Admit Card 2025 for the upcoming recruitment examination. Candidates who applied for the post of Assistant can now download their hall ticket from the official website jhc.org.in. The examination is scheduled to be held on 20th July 2025. The admit card contains important details such as exam date, time, venue, and candidate information. It is mandatory to carry a printed copy of the admit card along with a valid photo ID to the examination center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar Vidhan Sabha Security Guard Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-vidhan-sabha-security-guard-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jul 2025 09:56:38 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-vidhan-sabha-security-guard-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Vidhan Sabha has released the admit card for the Security Guard Recruitment Exam 2025. Candidates can download the hall ticket from the official website to check their exam date, time, and center details.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Pm Kisan Samman Nidhi Ki Kisht</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/pm-kisan-samman-nidhi-ki-kisht/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jul 2025 18:05:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/pm-kisan-samman-nidhi-ki-kisht/</guid>
      <description>🌾 PM Kisan 20वीं किस्त कब आएगी? जानिए पूरी जानकारी 📢 बड़ी खबर: पीएम किसान सम्मान निधि योजना की 20वीं किस्त जल्द ही किसानों के खातों में आने वाली है। जानिए संभावित तिथि और जरूरी अपडेट! 🗓️ 20वीं किस्त की संभावित तिथि सरकारी सूत्रों के अनुसार, PM-Kisan की 20वीं किस्त 18 जुलाई 2025 को पीएम मोदी का बिहार दौरा 18 जुलाई को मोतीहारी से किसानों के खातों में भेजी जा सकती है।, हालाकि ऑफिसियल ऐसी कोई भी जानकारी सामने नही है</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA CUET UG Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/nta-cuet-ug-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 14:15:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/nta-cuet-ug-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Testing Agency (NTA) has officially declared the CUET UG 2025 results. Candidates who appeared for the Common University Entrance Test can now check their scorecards on the official website – cuet.samarth.ac.in. The result includes detailed marks, percentiles, and overall performance. Students need their application number and date of birth to log in and view the result. Based on the scores, universities will proceed with their admission processes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Various Vacancy Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-various-vacancy-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jul 2025 10:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-various-vacancy-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Public Service Commission (RPSC) has released the admit card for various posts under its 2025 recruitment drive. Candidates can now download their hall tickets from the official RPSC website. The admit card includes important details such as exam date, time, venue, and candidate information. All applicants must carry a printed copy of the admit card along with a valid ID proof to the examination center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RRB ALP CEN 01/2024 Stage II Result with Marks 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/railway-rrb-alp-stage-ii-result-with-marks-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jul 2025 14:39:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/railway-rrb-alp-stage-ii-result-with-marks-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has declared the Stage II Result for the ALP CEN 01/2024 recruitment. Candidates who appeared in the exam can now check their marks and download the official scorecard. The result includes cutoff details and merit list for further selection.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BSPHCL Technician Gr-III Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-technician-gr-iii-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:31:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-technician-gr-iii-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar State Power Holding Company Limited (BSPHCL) has officially released the exam dates for the Technician Grade III recruitment 2025. The Computer-Based Test (CBT) is scheduled to be conducted from 11 July to 22 July 2025. Candidates who have applied for the post can check the detailed exam schedule on the official BSPHCL website. Admit cards will be released prior to the exam date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jharkhand ACF Pre Exam Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/jharkhand-acf-pre-exam-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:43:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/jharkhand-acf-pre-exam-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Jharkhand Public Service Commission (JPSC) has released the Preliminary Admit Card for the post of Assistant Conservator of Forest (ACF) 2025. Candidates who have applied for the exam can now download their hall ticket from the official website. The admit card includes important details such as exam date, time, venue, and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Admit Card 2025 Released for Various Post Codes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-post-admit-card-2025-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:47:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-post-admit-card-2025-released/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB has released the admit cards for various post code examinations scheduled between June 23 to July 9, 2025. Candidates can download their hall tickets from the official website dsssb.delhi.gov.in by entering their application number and date of birth. The admit card contains exam date, shift, venue, and important instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Patna HC Translator Final Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/patna-hc-translator-final-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:47:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/patna-hc-translator-final-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Patna High Court has announced the final result for the Translator and Translator-cum-Proof Reader Recruitment 2025. A total of 80 candidates have been selected under Advertisement No. PHC/01/2024. The merit list is available on the official website. Candidates who appeared in the exam can now check their selection status online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFCCIL MTS, Executive &amp; Jr. Manager Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dfccil-mts-executive-jr-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:36:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dfccil-mts-executive-jr-2025/</guid>
      <description>DFCCIL has announced the exam dates for MTS, Executive, and Junior Manager posts under its 2025 recruitment. The CBT will be conducted in multiple phases. Candidates can visit the official website at dfccil.com to check the complete schedule and updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police Radio Head Operator 2022 Final Result PDF Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/up-police-radio-head-operator-2022-final-result/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 12:49:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/up-police-radio-head-operator-2022-final-result/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has declared the final result for the UP Police Radio Cadre Head Operator Recruitment 2022. Candidates can now download the final merit list PDF and check their selection status for the year 2025.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB ALP CBAT Exam Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-alp-cbat-exam-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:15:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-alp-cbat-exam-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has officially announced the exam date for the Computer-Based Aptitude Test (CBAT) under the Assistant Loco Pilot (ALP) recruitment, CEN 01/2024. The CBAT exam is scheduled to be held on 15th July 2025. Candidates who qualified in CBT-2 are eligible to appear for this final stage. The City Intimation Slip is expected to be released from 5th July 2025, and the admit cards will likely be available from 11th July 2025. Aadhaar-based biometric verification will be mandatory on the exam day. For more details, candidates are advised to visit the official RRB website at rrbcdg.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC CPF Assistant Commandant Final Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/upsc-cpf-assistant-commandant-final-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 16:00:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/upsc-cpf-assistant-commandant-final-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the Final Result for the Central Armed Police Forces (Assistant Commandants) Examination 2025. Candidates who appeared in the recruitment process can now download the Final Selection List (Merit List PDF) from the official website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPCATET Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/upcatet-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:45:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/upcatet-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The UPCATET Result 2025 has been officially released on June 24, 2025, by Chandra Shekhar Azad University of Agriculture &amp;amp; Technology. Candidates who appeared for the UG, PG, and PhD entrance exams can now check and download their scorecard and rank card from the official website upcatet.net using their registration credentials. The result includes subject-wise marks, group rank, and category rank. The counselling process will begin soon for qualified candidates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSSSC Junior Assistant Mains Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/upsssc-junior-assistant-mains-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:36:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/upsssc-junior-assistant-mains-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Subordinate Services Selection Commission (UPSSSC) has released the Mains Admit Card for the Junior Assistant Recruitment 2025. Candidates who qualified for the preliminary exam can now download their admit card from the official website, upsssc.gov.in. The admit card contains important details like exam date, reporting time, exam center, and instructions. It is mandatory to carry a printed copy of the admit card along with a valid ID proof on the exam day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rajasthan Cooperative Bank Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/rajasthan-cooperative-bank-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 16:59:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/rajasthan-cooperative-bank-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Rajasthan Cooperative Recruitment Board (RCRB) has declared the result for various posts including Clerk, Junior Assistant, Salesman, Manager, and others. Candidates who appeared in the examination can now check their results, merit list, and cutoff marks through the official website. The selection is based on written exam performance and document verification. Candidates are advised to download the result PDF and keep a copy for future reference.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BTSC GMO Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/bihar-btsc-gmo-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 11:28:25 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/bihar-btsc-gmo-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar Technical Service Commission (BTSC) has officially released the GMO (General Medical Officer) Result 2025. Candidates who appeared for the examination can now check their results, merit list, and cut-off marks on the official BTSC website. The result PDF is available for download, and shortlisted candidates will be called for further procedures as per the official notice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BSPHCL JCA Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-jca-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:19:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-jca-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar State Power Holding Company Limited (BSPHCL) has released the admit card for the Junior Customer Assistant (JCA) Recruitment Exam 2025. Candidates can download their hall ticket from the official website. The admit card includes important details such as exam date, time, venue, and instructions. Carrying the admit card along with a valid photo ID is mandatory to appear in the examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Punjab National Bank PNB Specialist Officer Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/pnb-specialist-officer-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jun 2025 09:31:45 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/pnb-specialist-officer-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>Punjab National Bank (PNB) has declared the Specialist Officer (SO) Result 2025 for various posts. A total of 1,836 candidates have been shortlisted for the interview round. Candidates who appeared for the written examination can now download the merit list PDF from the official website pnbindia.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BTSC Bihar Insect Collector Result 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/btsc-bihar-insect-collector-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Jun 2025 16:04:42 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/btsc-bihar-insect-collector-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>BTSC बिहार कीट संग्राहक परिणाम 2025 बिहार तकनीकी सेवा आयोग द्वारा आधिकारिक रूप से जारी कर दिया गया है। परीक्षा में शामिल अभ्यर्थी अब मेरिट लिस्ट और कट-ऑफ मार्क्स आधिकारिक वेबसाइट से डाउनलोड कर सकते हैं। चयन सूची PDF में चयनित अभ्यर्थियों के रोल नंबर शामिल हैं। आगे की प्रक्रिया जैसे दस्तावेज़ सत्यापन या साक्षात्कार की जानकारी भी जल्द जारी की जाएगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RSKMP 5th &amp; 8th Re-Exam Result Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/rskmp-5th-8th-re-exam-results-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 19:22:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/rskmp-5th-8th-re-exam-results-2025/</guid>
      <description>RSKMP Re-Exam Result 2025 कक्षा 5वीं और 8वीं के लिए घोषित कर दिया गया है। जिन छात्रों ने पुनः परीक्षा दी थी, वे अब अपना रिजल्ट आधिकारिक वेबसाइट rskmp.in पर जाकर रोल नंबर की सहायता से ऑनलाइन देख सकते हैं। यह रिजल्ट जून 2025 में जारी किया गया है और छात्र इसे PDF फॉर्मेट में डाउनलोड भी कर सकते हैं। रिजल्ट चेक करने के लिए रोल नंबर और कभी-कभी जन्म तिथि की आवश्यकता हो सकती है। रिजल्ट की डायरेक्ट लिंक, मार्कशीट डाउनलोड और अन्य आवश्यक जानकारी इस पेज पर उपलब्ध है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC School Lecturer Admit Card 2025 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-school-lecturer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:41:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-school-lecturer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>यह रहा RPSC School Lecturer Admit Card 2025 (PGT Exam) के लिए एक संक्षिप्त सारांश (Summary), जिसे आप पोस्ट की शुरुआत में या एक जानकारी वाले बॉक्स में उपयोग कर सकते हैं:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RPF Constable Result 2025 Declared</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/result/railway-rpf-constable-result-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:50:21 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/result/railway-rpf-constable-result-2025/</guid>
      <description>रेलवे सुरक्षा बल (RPF) द्वारा आयोजित कांस्टेबल भर्ती परीक्षा 2025 का परिणाम 19 जून 2025 को आधिकारिक रूप से घोषित कर दिया गया है। यह परिणाम कंप्यूटर आधारित परीक्षा (CBT) के लिए जारी किया गया है, जिसमें लाखों अभ्यर्थियों ने भाग लिया था। चयनित उम्मीदवारों की सूची पीडीएफ फॉर्मेट में जारी की गई है, जिसमें रोल नंबर के अनुसार नाम शामिल हैं। जो उम्मीदवार CBT में सफल हुए हैं, उन्हें अब PET (शारीरिक दक्षता परीक्षण) और PMT (शारीरिक माप परीक्षण) के लिए बुलाया जाएगा।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>लाड़ली बहनों को दिवाली से ₹1500 प्रतिमाह मिलेंगे – सीएम मोहन यादव का ऐलान</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/ladli-bahna-yojna-1500-per-month/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 16:28:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/ladli-bahna-yojna-1500-per-month/</guid>
      <description> दिवाली से मिलेंगे लाड़ली बहनों को ₹1500 प्रतिमाह – डॉ. मोहन यादव का बड़ा ऐलान 📢 मध्य प्रदेश की लाड़ली बहना योजना के तहत बहनों को अब बड़ी सौगात मिलने वाली है। मुख्यमंत्री डॉ. मोहन यादव ने घोषणा की है कि दिवाली से लाड़ली बहनों को ₹1500 प्रतिमाह</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Various Posts Admit Card June 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-posts-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:28:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-posts-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB has released the admit cards for the Various Post Exam scheduled in June 2025. Candidates can download their hall tickets from the official website dsssb.delhi.gov.in. The admit card contains details like exam date, time, and exam center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army Agniveer Admit Card Download 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/indian-army-agniveer-admitcard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:45:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/indian-army-agniveer-admitcard/</guid>
      <description>Indian Army has released the Agniveer GD Admit Card 2025 on June 16. Candidates can download it from joinindianarmy.nic.in. The Common Entrance Exam (CEE) for General Duty posts will be held from June 30 to July 3, 2025. Admit cards for other categories like Tradesmen, Technical, and Clerk/SKT will be available from June 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Ladli Bahna 25th Installment Date 2025: Payment Status, List &amp; Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/ladli-behna-yojna-25th-kist/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jun 2025 07:43:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/ladli-behna-yojna-25th-kist/</guid>
      <description> लाड़ली बहना योजना संबंधित महत्तपूर्ण लिंक Important Links Action Ladi Bahna Yojna Status Check Status Ladi Bahna Yojna Speech Check Official Follow For Latest Update WhatsApp | Telegram Official Website CM LBY Official Website </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CM Laptop Yojana 2025-26 , MP</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/cm-laptop-yojna-mp/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 May 2025 09:55:35 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/cm-laptop-yojna-mp/</guid>
      <description> Important Links Action Check Status MP Laptop Yojna Details Check DBT Check Bank eKYC Details Download Notification Check Sourses For Latest Update Join WhatsApp Join Telegram Official Website MP Shikshaportal Official Website </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RRB NTPC Graduate Level Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-ntpc-ug-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 10:45:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-ntpc-ug-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>RRB NTPC Graduate Level Admit Card 2025 जारी कर दिया गया है। उम्मीदवार अपने क्षेत्रीय RRB की वेबसाइट से लॉगिन करके प्रवेश पत्र डाउनलोड कर सकते हैं। इसमें परीक्षा की तिथि, समय और केंद्र की जानकारी शामिल है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Ladli Bahna Yojna May 2025 Payment News – Check 24th Installment Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mp/ladli-bahna-yojna-24th/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2025 16:36:14 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mp/ladli-bahna-yojna-24th/</guid>
      <description> लाड़ली बहना योजना संबंधित महत्तपूर्ण लिंक Important Links Action Ladi Bahna Yojna Status Check Status Ladi Bahna Yojna Aadesh Downlaod Follow For Latest Update WhatsApp | Telegram Official Website CM LBY Official Website </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP krishi yantra anudan yojana 2025 online apply</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/mpdage/ekrishi-yantra-anudan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 09:43:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/mpdage/ekrishi-yantra-anudan/</guid>
      <description> कृषि यंत्रो हेतु ऑनलाइन आवेदन (Date: 13/05/2025 अनुसार सारणी) क्रमांक यंत्र का नाम योजना का नाम अंतिम तिथि 1 बलराम ताल निर्माण प्रधानमंत्री कृषि सिंचाई योजना (अदर इंटरवेंशन) 31/05/2025 23:59 2 ड्रिप सिस्टम प्रधानमंत्री कृषि सिंचाई योजना (माइक्रो इरीगेशन) 15/05/2025 23:59 3 स्प्रिंकलर सेट प्रधानमंत्री कृषि सिंचाई योजना (माइक्रो इरीगेशन) 15/05/2025 23:59 Important Links Action Apply Online Registration / Login Application Status Check Status Registration List Check List Subsidy Calculator Calculate Subsidy Farmer Dashboard Farmer mpdage Dashboard Pay Dashboard Pay mpdage Dashboard Follow for New Update Whatsapp | Telegram MP Dage Official MP Dage Official Website Official Webisite MP Krishi Official Website </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
