<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Profiles on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Profiles on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 20:17:41 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/profile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPTAAS Profile Registration 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/mptaas-profile-otr-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 20:17:41 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/profile/mptaas-profile-otr-update/</guid>
      <description>MPTAAS Profile Registration 2025 is a mandatory process for SC, ST, and OBC students in Madhya Pradesh to apply for Post Matric Scholarships. The profile is created on the Tribal Affairs portal, enabling students to apply for schemes, track status, and receive benefits via DBT (Direct Benefit Transfer). Important documents like Aadhaar, Samagra ID, caste certificate, domicile proof, and bank details are required. Once registered, students can log in and apply for scholarships online.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Rojgar Panjiyan Online Registration 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/mp-rojgar-otr-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 14:03:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/profile/mp-rojgar-otr-form/</guid>
      <description>MP Rojgar Panjiyan 2025 is the official employment registration system launched by the Government of Madhya Pradesh. Through this portal (mprojgar.gov.in), job seekers can register for free, get notified about government and private job opportunities, participate in job fairs, and renew their registration every 3 years. The process is fully online, and applicants need to provide basic personal information, educational documents, and Aadhaar details to complete their profile.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Candidate Profiling / Profile Panjiyan Form Online</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/mpesb-candidate-profile-panjiyan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/profile/mpesb-candidate-profile-panjiyan/</guid>
      <description>To apply for any government recruitment under the Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board (MPESB), all candidates must complete the Candidate Profile Registration process. This is a one-time mandatory step where applicants register using Aadhaar eKYC, upload personal and academic details, and receive a unique Profile ID. This ID is required for all future MPESB applications. The process is simple, online, and essential for anyone seeking government jobs in Madhya Pradesh.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IFMS Profile Update, Karmchari Profile ekyc</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/profile/mp-ifms-profile/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jan 2025 11:07:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/profile/mp-ifms-profile/</guid>
      <description>Karmchari hitgrahi ekyc, IFMS Profile ekyc, कर्मचारी हितग्राही प्रोफाइल पंजीयन</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
