<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calendars on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calendars on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/calendar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>RRB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:00:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has released the official RRB Exam Calendar 2026 outlining the recruitment planning schedule for various railway posts. The calendar includes major categories such as Assistant Loco Pilot (ALP), Technicians, NTPC (Graduate and Under Graduate), Junior Engineer (JE), Paramedical, Ministerial &amp;amp; Isolated posts, Section Controller, and Level-1 (Group D). It provides a clear timeline for vacancy assessment, OIRMS assessment, indenting process, and draft CEN preparation across different quarters of 2026. This calendar helps candidates understand the expected recruitment cycle; however, actual notifications and exam dates will be released separately through individual CENs by the respective RRBs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:48:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>UPSC has released the official Examination and Recruitment Tests Calendar 2026 detailing the complete schedule of Civil Services, NDA, CDS, CAPF, IES/ISS, CMS, Indian Forest Service and other UPSC exams. The calendar includes important dates such as notification, application deadline and exam duration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:47:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 has been officially released by the Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission. As per the calendar, major examinations such as State Service Exam 2025 (Main), Assistant Professor Exam 2025 &amp;amp; 2026, State Engineering Service Exam 2025, State Service &amp;amp; Forest Service Preliminary Exam 2026 and Main Exams 2026 are scheduled between January 2026 and September 2026. Candidates preparing for MPPSC recruitment exams can use this calendar to plan their preparation, while final dates may be changed as per administrative or court decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:11:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026 outlines the tentative schedule of recruitment, entrance and eligibility examinations to be conducted by the Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board. As per the calendar, various exams including Group-1, Group-2, Group-3, Group-4, Police Constable, Staff Nurse, ITI Training Officer, Nursing, Agriculture and Teacher Eligibility Tests are scheduled between February 2026 and October 2026. Candidates preparing for MP government jobs and entrance examinations can use this calendar to plan their preparation in advance, while final dates will be confirmed through official notifications issued by MPESB.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
