<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calendars on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calendars on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:40:30 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/calendar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:40:30 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The Union Public Service Commission (UPSC) has released the official Programme of Examinations / Recruitment Tests (RTs) Calendar 2026. The calendar includes the complete schedule of major UPSC examinations such as Civil Services (Preliminary &amp;amp; Main), NDA &amp;amp; NA (I &amp;amp; II), CDS (I &amp;amp; II), CAPF (ACs), IES/ISS, Combined Medical Services (CMS), Indian Forest Service, Engineering Services, Geo-Scientist Exams, and several Reserved Recruitment Tests. It provides important details including notification dates, last dates to apply, exam commencement dates, and duration of each examination. Candidates preparing for UPSC exams in 2026 are advised to regularly check official updates, as dates are subject to change based on administrative requirements.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:47:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 has been officially released by the Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission. As per the calendar, major examinations such as State Service Exam 2025 (Main), Assistant Professor Exam 2025 &amp;amp; 2026, State Engineering Service Exam 2025, State Service &amp;amp; Forest Service Preliminary Exam 2026 and Main Exams 2026 are scheduled between January 2026 and September 2026. Candidates preparing for MPPSC recruitment exams can use this calendar to plan their preparation, while final dates may be changed as per administrative or court decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:11:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026 outlines the tentative schedule of recruitment, entrance and eligibility examinations to be conducted by the Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board. As per the calendar, various exams including Group-1, Group-2, Group-3, Group-4, Police Constable, Staff Nurse, ITI Training Officer, Nursing, Agriculture and Teacher Eligibility Tests are scheduled between February 2026 and October 2026. Candidates preparing for MP government jobs and entrance examinations can use this calendar to plan their preparation in advance, while final dates will be confirmed through official notifications issued by MPESB.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
