<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Calendars on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Calendars on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:25:07 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/calendar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/ssc-exam-calendar-2026-27/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2026 15:25:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/ssc-exam-calendar-2026-27/</guid>
      <description>Staff Selection Commission (SSC) has released the SSC Exam Calendar 2026. The calendar includes notification dates, last dates to apply, and exam months for CGL, CHSL, MTS, GD, JE, Stenographer, Hindi Translator and other SSC exams.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 19:08:54 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rpsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>Rajasthan Public Service Commission has published the RPSC Exam Calendar 2026 outlining the tentative examination timeline for multiple recruitment posts. The schedule includes Deputy Commandant, Lecturer, Sub Inspector, Veterinary Officer, Assistant Engineer, Senior Teacher, Junior Legal Officer, Statistical Officer and other examinations planned from January to December 2026. Some exams will be conducted through CBRT mode, while detailed admit card and exam shift information will be released separately as per RPSC guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Dec 2025 15:29:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/rrb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>The official RRB Exam Calendar 2026 has been issued by the Railway Recruitment Board to outline the annual recruitment planning for upcoming railway vacancies. The calendar covers key posts including Assistant Loco Pilot, Technicians, NTPC Graduate and Undergraduate posts, Junior Engineer, Paramedical staff, Ministerial and Isolated categories, Section Controller, and Level-1 Group D. It explains the quarterly schedule for vacancy assessment, OIRMS processing, indent submission, and draft CEN preparation. Candidates should note that this calendar indicates the planning cycle only, while detailed notifications and exam dates will be announced separately through individual CEN notifications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2025 15:48:12 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/upsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>UPSC has released the official Examination and Recruitment Tests Calendar 2026 detailing the complete schedule of Civil Services, NDA, CDS, CAPF, IES/ISS, CMS, Indian Forest Service and other UPSC exams. The calendar includes important dates such as notification, application deadline and exam duration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:47:23 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mppsc-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPPSC Exam Calendar 2026 has been officially released by the Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission. As per the calendar, major examinations such as State Service Exam 2025 (Main), Assistant Professor Exam 2025 &amp;amp; 2026, State Engineering Service Exam 2025, State Service &amp;amp; Forest Service Preliminary Exam 2026 and Main Exams 2026 are scheduled between January 2026 and September 2026. Candidates preparing for MPPSC recruitment exams can use this calendar to plan their preparation, while final dates may be changed as per administrative or court decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Dec 2025 16:11:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/calendar/mpesb-exam-calendar-2026/</guid>
      <description>MPESB Exam Calendar 2026 outlines the tentative schedule of recruitment, entrance and eligibility examinations to be conducted by the Madhya Pradesh Employees Selection Board. As per the calendar, various exams including Group-1, Group-2, Group-3, Group-4, Police Constable, Staff Nurse, ITI Training Officer, Nursing, Agriculture and Teacher Eligibility Tests are scheduled between February 2026 and October 2026. Candidates preparing for MP government jobs and entrance examinations can use this calendar to plan their preparation in advance, while final dates will be confirmed through official notifications issued by MPESB.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
