<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Otrs on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Otrs on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 19:38:15 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/otr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SSC OTR 2025 – One Time Registration</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/ssc-otr-online-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Aug 2025 19:38:15 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/ssc-otr-online-form/</guid>
      <description>SSC OTR 2025 allows candidates to create a single profile for multiple SSC exams. Register online once, fill personal and educational details, upload documents, and easily apply for upcoming SSC exams. Check eligibility, important dates, fees, and registration steps.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UP Police One Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/up-police-otr-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 17:26:33 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/up-police-otr-online/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Police Recruitment and Promotion Board (UPPRPB) has launched the One Time Registration (OTR) 2025 process for all aspiring candidates. This OTR is mandatory for those who wish to apply for any upcoming UP Police recruitment exams. By completing the OTR once, candidates will not need to repeatedly enter their details for each application. This system ensures a faster, more transparent, and convenient application process. Interested candidates can register online at uppbpb.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPPSC OTR One Time Registration 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/otr/uppsc-otr-portal-form/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 09:54:57 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/otr/uppsc-otr-portal-form/</guid>
      <description>UPPSC OTR (One Time Registration) is an online registration system launched by the Uttar Pradesh Public Service Commission to simplify the application process for various state-level exams. Candidates need to register only once by providing their personal, educational, and ID details. Once registered, they can apply for future UPPSC recruitments without filling in their details again. This system saves time, reduces errors, and ensures accuracy in applications.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
