<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Latest Admitcard on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Latest Admitcard on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:31:29 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/admitcard/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BSPHCL Technician Gr-III Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-technician-gr-iii-exam-date-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 19:31:29 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-technician-gr-iii-exam-date-2025/</guid>
      <description>Bihar State Power Holding Company Limited (BSPHCL) has officially released the exam dates for the Technician Grade III recruitment 2025. The Computer-Based Test (CBT) is scheduled to be conducted from 11 July to 22 July 2025. Candidates who have applied for the post can check the detailed exam schedule on the official BSPHCL website. Admit cards will be released prior to the exam date.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jharkhand ACF Pre Exam Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/jharkhand-acf-pre-exam-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2025 16:43:20 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/jharkhand-acf-pre-exam-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>Jharkhand Public Service Commission (JPSC) has released the Preliminary Admit Card for the post of Assistant Conservator of Forest (ACF) 2025. Candidates who have applied for the exam can now download their hall ticket from the official website. The admit card includes important details such as exam date, time, venue, and instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Admit Card 2025 Released for Various Post Codes</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-post-admit-card-2025-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jun 2025 20:47:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-post-admit-card-2025-released/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB has released the admit cards for various post code examinations scheduled between June 23 to July 9, 2025. Candidates can download their hall tickets from the official website dsssb.delhi.gov.in by entering their application number and date of birth. The admit card contains exam date, shift, venue, and important instructions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DFCCIL MTS, Executive &amp; Jr. Manager Exam Date 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dfccil-mts-executive-jr-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 15:36:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dfccil-mts-executive-jr-2025/</guid>
      <description>DFCCIL has announced the exam dates for MTS, Executive, and Junior Manager posts under its 2025 recruitment. The CBT will be conducted in multiple phases. Candidates can visit the official website at dfccil.com to check the complete schedule and updates.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RRB ALP CBAT Exam Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-alp-cbat-exam-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jun 2025 18:15:27 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-alp-cbat-exam-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Railway Recruitment Board (RRB) has officially announced the exam date for the Computer-Based Aptitude Test (CBAT) under the Assistant Loco Pilot (ALP) recruitment, CEN 01/2024. The CBAT exam is scheduled to be held on 15th July 2025. Candidates who qualified in CBT-2 are eligible to appear for this final stage. The City Intimation Slip is expected to be released from 5th July 2025, and the admit cards will likely be available from 11th July 2025. Aadhaar-based biometric verification will be mandatory on the exam day. For more details, candidates are advised to visit the official RRB website at rrbcdg.gov.in.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UPSSSC Junior Assistant Mains Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/upsssc-junior-assistant-mains-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jun 2025 20:36:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/upsssc-junior-assistant-mains-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Uttar Pradesh Subordinate Services Selection Commission (UPSSSC) has released the Mains Admit Card for the Junior Assistant Recruitment 2025. Candidates who qualified for the preliminary exam can now download their admit card from the official website, upsssc.gov.in. The admit card contains important details like exam date, reporting time, exam center, and instructions. It is mandatory to carry a printed copy of the admit card along with a valid ID proof on the exam day.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bihar BSPHCL JCA Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-jca-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 13:19:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/bihar-bsphcl-jca-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Bihar State Power Holding Company Limited (BSPHCL) has released the admit card for the Junior Customer Assistant (JCA) Recruitment Exam 2025. Candidates can download their hall ticket from the official website. The admit card includes important details such as exam date, time, venue, and instructions. Carrying the admit card along with a valid photo ID is mandatory to appear in the examination.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UGC NET June 2025 Admit Card Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/ugc-net-june-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jun 2025 15:30:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/ugc-net-june-2025/</guid>
      <description>NTA ने UGC NET June 2025 परीक्षा के लिए एडमिट कार्ड जारी कर दिए हैं। अभ्यर्थी अपना हॉल टिकट आधिकारिक वेबसाइट ugcnet.nta.nic.in से एप्लिकेशन नंबर और जन्म तिथि की मदद से डाउनलोड कर सकते हैं। परीक्षा निर्धारित तिथि पर देशभर में आयोजित की जाएगी।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>RPSC School Lecturer Admit Card 2025 Released</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-school-lecturer-admit-card-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jun 2025 18:41:32 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rpsc-school-lecturer-admit-card-2025/</guid>
      <description>यह रहा RPSC School Lecturer Admit Card 2025 (PGT Exam) के लिए एक संक्षिप्त सारांश (Summary), जिसे आप पोस्ट की शुरुआत में या एक जानकारी वाले बॉक्स में उपयोग कर सकते हैं:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DSSSB Various Posts Admit Card June 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-posts-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jun 2025 10:28:06 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/dsssb-various-posts-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>DSSSB has released the admit cards for the Various Post Exam scheduled in June 2025. Candidates can download their hall tickets from the official website dsssb.delhi.gov.in. The admit card contains details like exam date, time, and exam center.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Indian Army Agniveer Admit Card Download 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/indian-army-agniveer-admitcard/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jun 2025 10:45:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/indian-army-agniveer-admitcard/</guid>
      <description>Indian Army has released the Agniveer GD Admit Card 2025 on June 16. Candidates can download it from joinindianarmy.nic.in. The Common Entrance Exam (CEE) for General Duty posts will be held from June 30 to July 3, 2025. Admit cards for other categories like Tradesmen, Technical, and Clerk/SKT will be available from June 18.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Railway RRB NTPC Graduate Level Admit Card 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-ntpc-ug-admitcard-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 May 2025 10:45:37 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admitcard/rrb-ntpc-ug-admitcard-2025/</guid>
      <description>RRB NTPC Graduate Level Admit Card 2025 जारी कर दिया गया है। उम्मीदवार अपने क्षेत्रीय RRB की वेबसाइट से लॉगिन करके प्रवेश पत्र डाउनलोड कर सकते हैं। इसमें परीक्षा की तिथि, समय और केंद्र की जानकारी शामिल है।</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
