<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eligibilty on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/</link>
    <description>Recent content in eligibilty on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:26:08 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/eligibility/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>MPPSC SET Exam 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-set-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Nov 2025 16:26:08 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-set-2025/</guid>
      <description>The Madhya Pradesh State Eligibility Test (MP SET 2025) is conducted by the Madhya Pradesh Public Service Commission (MPPSC) to determine the eligibility of candidates for the post of Assistant Professor in universities and colleges of Madhya Pradesh. Applications will be accepted online from 25/10/2025 to 20/11/2025, and the exam will be held on 11/01/2026.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA UGC NET December 2025 Exam</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-ugc-net-december-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Oct 2025 15:13:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-ugc-net-december-2025/</guid>
      <description>The UGC NET December 2025 Notification has been released by the National Testing Agency (NTA) for determining the eligibility of candidates for Assistant Professor and Junior Research Fellowship (JRF) in Indian universities and colleges. Candidates with a Master’s degree (55% marks for General and 50% for reserved categories) can apply online from 07 October to 07 November 2025 at ugcnet.nta.nic.in. The exam will be conducted in Computer Based Test (CBT) mode across multiple subjects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA CSIR NET June 2025 Admitcard Available</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-csir-june-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 09:08:46 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/nta-csir-june-2025/</guid>
      <description>The National Testing Agency (NTA) has released the CSIR UGC NET June 2025 notification for Junior Research Fellowship (JRF) and Lectureship/Assistant Professor in various science subjects. Eligible candidates can apply online at csirnet.nta.nic.in. Check important dates, eligibility, syllabus, and exam pattern before applying.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Proficiency Certification Test (CPCT) Apply Online Now</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-cpct-apply-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jun 2025 10:23:52 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/eligibility/mp-cpct-apply-2025/</guid>
      <description>CPCT (Computer Proficiency Certification Test) मध्यप्रदेश सरकार द्वारा आयोजित एक पात्रता परीक्षा है, जिसका उद्देश्य कंप्यूटर और टाइपिंग कौशल का मूल्यांकन करना है। यह परीक्षा MPSEDC (Madhya Pradesh State Electronics Development Corporation) द्वारा संचालित की जाती है और विभिन्न सरकारी पदों जैसे डाटा एंट्री ऑपरेटर, क्लर्क आदि के लिए अनिवार्य है। इच्छुक अभ्यर्थी cpct.mp.gov.in पर जाकर ऑनलाइन आवेदन कर सकते हैं। परीक्षा में कंप्यूटर ज्ञान, हिंदी/अंग्रेज़ी टाइपिंग टेस्ट और वस्तुनिष्ठ प्रश्न पूछे जाते हैं। आवेदन शुल्क ₹660/- है और प्रमाणपत्र की वैधता 7 वर्ष होती है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>NTA UGC NET June 2025 Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/admission/nta-ugc-net-june-2025/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Apr 2025 11:52:40 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/admission/nta-ugc-net-june-2025/</guid>
      <description>यूजीसी नेट जेआरएफ पात्रता परीक्षा जून 2025</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
