<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>document on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/document/</link>
    <description>Recent content in document on YOJNA PORTAL 2025 - Govt Schemes &amp; Sarkari Job Updates Daily</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:13:04 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/document/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Driving Licence Apply, Status Check &amp; Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/driving-licence-apply-parivahan/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Sep 2025 10:13:04 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/driving-licence-apply-parivahan/</guid>
      <description>ड्राइविंग लाइसेंस एक वैध और अनिवार्य दस्तावेज़ है जो व्यक्ति को कानूनी रूप से वाहन चलाने की अनुमति देता है। यह न केवल वाहन चालक की योग्यता को प्रमाणित करता है, बल्कि सड़क सुरक्षा और ट्रैफिक नियमों के पालन को भी सुनिश्चित करता है। लाइसेंस प्राप्त करने के लिए निर्धारित आयु, दस्तावेज़ और ड्राइविंग टेस्ट की प्रक्रिया होती है। यह पहचान पत्र के रूप में भी उपयोगी है और रोजगार के अवसरों को बढ़ावा देता है। आजकल इसकी ऑनलाइन आवेदन, स्थिति जांच और डाउनलोड प्रक्रिया सरल और सुविधाजनक हो गई है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Keerti Card: Special Benefits and Recognition for Daughters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/scheme/mp-rewashakti-keerti-card-online-apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 17:47:59 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/scheme/mp-rewashakti-keerti-card-online-apply/</guid>
      <description>MP Keerti Card मध्य प्रदेश सरकार की एक विशेष पहल है, जो बेटियों वाले परिवारों को प्रोत्साहन और सम्मान देने के लिए शुरू की गई है। इस कार्ड के माध्यम से परिवारों को सरकारी सेवाओं में प्राथमिकता, शिक्षा व स्वास्थ्य सुविधाओं में छूट, और स्थानीय व्यापारों में विशेष लाभ मिलता है। इसका उद्देश्य लिंगानुपात सुधारना, बेटियों के प्रति सम्मान बढ़ाना और परिवारों को प्रोत्साहित करना है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Bhulekh (WebGis 2.0) 2025 - Khasra, B1, Naksha Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/webgis2-mpbhulekh-digital-certificate-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 18:12:18 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/webgis2-mpbhulekh-digital-certificate-online/</guid>
      <description>MP Bhulekh (WebGis 2.0) 2025 is an official online portal developed by the Revenue Department of the Government of Madhya Pradesh. It allows citizens to access digital land records such as Khasra, B1, and Land Maps (Naksha) in PDF format. Through this platform, users can search by district, tehsil, village, or landowner name, and download digitally signed documents. The portal also provides an option to apply online for a Digital Land Ownership Certificate, ensuring transparency and easy access to verified land details. Services are available in both Hindi and English, making it citizen-friendly and accessible to all.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MSME Udyam Registration 2025- Online Form</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/msme-udyam-reg-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 10:10:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/msme-udyam-reg-online/</guid>
      <description>Udyam Registration is an official government process under the Ministry of MSME (Micro, Small and Medium Enterprises) in India. It allows small business owners, startups, manufacturers, and service providers to register their businesses and get recognized as an MSME. The registration is completely free, online, and requires only basic documents like Aadhaar and PAN. Once registered, businesses get access to government benefits such as subsidies, low-interest loans, tax exemptions, and priority in tenders. It is mandatory for businesses that want to avail of MSME schemes and participate in government opportunities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>APAAR ID / ABC ID card Online Apply &amp; Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/apaar-or-abc-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 13:01:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/apaar-or-abc-id/</guid>
      <description>The Apaar ID (also called ABC ID) is a unique 12-digit identification number issued by the Ministry of Education, Government of India under the National Education Policy (NEP) 2020. It is designed for school and college students across India to digitally store their academic records, credits, and certificates. The card facilitates seamless credit transfer and academic mobility through platforms like DigiLocker and the Academic Bank of Credits (ABC Portal). Students can apply online using their Aadhaar and basic educational details. The card is available to all students from Class 1 onward and can be downloaded from DigiLocker or the ABC portal after registration.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Vehicle Registration Certificate (RC) –  Download &amp; Details</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/vahan-rc-card-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Jul 2025 15:48:09 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/vahan-rc-card-online/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is UDID Card? Unique Disability ID Benefits and How to Apply</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/udid-disability-certificate/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 20:26:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/udid-disability-certificate/</guid>
      <description>UDID परियोजना का उद्देश्य देशभर में दिव्यांगजनों का राष्ट्रीय डेटाबेस बनाना है। इसके तहत राज्य/केंद्र शासित प्रदेशों द्वारा अधिकृत चिकित्सा प्राधिकरणों के माध्यम से दिव्यांग प्रमाण पत्र और यूनिक दिव्यांग पहचान पत्र जारी किए जाते हैं। यह परियोजना सरकारी लाभों के वितरण में पारदर्शिता और दक्षता बढ़ाने पर केंद्रित है।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Voter ID Online Apply, Correction, Status &amp; Form List 2025</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/voter-card-online-form-details/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jun 2025 18:52:03 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/voter-card-online-form-details/</guid>
      <description>वोटर कार्ड भारत निर्वाचन आयोग द्वारा जारी एक पहचान पत्र है, जो 18 वर्ष या उससे अधिक आयु के भारतीय नागरिकों को दिया जाता है। यह चुनावों में मतदान का अधिकार प्राप्त करने और पहचान प्रमाण के रूप में कार्य करता है। वोटर कार्ड बनवाने, सुधार, नाम हटाने, या डुप्लीकेट कार्ड पाने के लिए Form 6, 7, 8, 6A, 001A आदि फॉर्म होते हैं।</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ration Card e-KYC Mobile Se Kare </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/update/ration-card-ekyc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 May 2025 11:10:53 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/update/ration-card-ekyc/</guid>
      <description>राशन कार्ड eKYC ऑनलाइन</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MP Sambal Card Apply Online 2025 – फॉर्म, पात्रता, लाभ और आवश्यक दस्तावेज</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/mp-sambal-yojna-apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 18:41:05 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/mp-sambal-yojna-apply/</guid>
      <description>मुख्य मंत्री जनकल्याण (संबल कार्ड) योजना ऑनलाइन आवेदन</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eshram Card Apply, Update and Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/document/eshram-card-apply/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Apr 2025 12:45:34 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/document/eshram-card-apply/</guid>
      <description>ई-श्रम कार्ड योजना - ऑनलाइन आवेदन</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Annadata Card Farmer Id Apply &amp; Download</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/schemes/farmer-id-annadata-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 10:27:31 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/schemes/farmer-id-annadata-card/</guid>
      <description>अन्नदाता कार्ड / फार्मर आई डी आवेदन &amp;amp; डाउनलोड</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
